風花雪月汉化组译制，更多众筹作品与音声汉化相关加接待企鹅1-
594349181或群1011027379，转载请注明，谢谢配合
Finally, it's here, senpai
First time I met you,
my name is Ariki
Do you know why you called
senpai to the sports warehouse?
It's really outrageous
Calling me a faggot
and telling other people behind my back
that I was definitely doing it with a man
Obviously I haven't said a few
words to my seniors so far
and saying such unbelievable
things, I'm still hurt
I don't like to have such
a boyish face either
Speaking of which, the seniors who say other people are gay
and then do it with men are the ones who are gay, right?
Is this school an all boys
school or is it all residential
Seeing a cute boy like me
makes your heart flutter
Just be honest
Senpai, let's be honest~
That would be boring!
Then again, I won't forgive
you even if you apologize
Is it possible to say so many bad things about
someone and then apologize and be forgiven?
Like that, it only worked
when you were a kid
I wasn't a good kid either
If something was done to me,
I wanted to get back at him
And then you want to
play some fun games
The content is simple
I'll jerk off the
former Eugene King
If you can hold it in without cumming,
you're forgiven for badmouthing me
And accordingly, if you can't
hold back your ejaculation
Please admit you're
a faggot, senpai~
Nah, what's up?
Senpai, you're going to
join this game, right?
That's it!
Just take off your
trousers like that
Senpai's Ojinjin is so
much cuter than I thought
Does it get bigger
if I jerk you off?
How does it feel to be jerked
off by a man with a rod?
It's really comfortable~
In that case, how about this?
You haven't been
licked yet, have you?
Obviously I've never even
licked a girl's breast
Is it humiliating to have your pussy
licked by a man or something?
Being jerked off by cute me and having
my nipples licked at the same time
Although for some interested
people it would be nice
but senpai is not
a faggot at all
In that case, if you don't have something
exciting to do, you won't cum at all
But, Alle? That's weird.
Senpai's Ojinjin is already hard
No way, it's not a faggot,
it's being caressed by a man!
Which side is the
faggot, seriously?
Making cute girlie noises eh
Senpai, that's disgusting!
If you're such a disgusting senpai, you'll
feel it when you get your ear licked, right?
You're panting just from
licking your ear, huh?
Ojinjin has absolutely
no patience either
It looks so happy
From the front flowed
the first go juice oh
If you lick deep into the ear
What would happen?
It's really a humiliating sound
After saying so many bad things about other
people, isn't that what senpai was like too?
You're not a voice for men
No, because senpai is a faggot,
so he wants others to hear it
because they want me to feel it too, they
want to be tilted, so they call it that
That's not going to work for me
I'm not a faggot either, I
just want you to cum faster
even if you try to
seduce me it won't work
senpai just wants to make Ojinjin get
an erection and then biubiu cum~
Come on, want to cum?
It's not good for your health to hold
back, although you have to hold back
Counting down while jerking
off more intensely
If I can't hold
back and cum at 0
Then it's okay to think
that senpai is a faggot
Then we'll start counting down
Ready~
5~
It feels good to have your
erect nipples licked too
Speaking of faggots, is it true that anything is
good as long as you're being played with by a boy?
Okay 4~
even if you make dumb noises...
It's impossible for a
virgin to hold back anyway
Next... [11:19.13]
[11:19.13] next...
getting licked back and forth deep in
the ear, is it getting weaker again?
I can't help it if I want
to come soon, can I?
I want to get to 0 quickly
and then biubiu ah~
Don't worry ~ only
2 seconds left!
I'll be ready to cum soon
I can't help it, I'm
going to cum by my hand
Come on, only 1 second left!
If you don't want to admit you're
gay, you have to hold back
Can you hold back from being jerked off so
aggressively? [14:19.77] Try it if you can!
senpai~
Well, I'm sure it
won't work anyway
If you can hold back even if you're being
jerked off violently, perform one, senpai~
Well, I can't anyway
0! 0! It's 0, senpai!
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on!
Just cum, cum in front of
me, cum in front of me
Come on, cum!
Come on, biubiubiu!
Senpai~ Ah~ I'm cumming as a man
It's true that
senpai is a faggot
Nothing can be said about me
So, even if you apologize
several times, it's useless
I won't forgive you, come to my
room when you get back to the dorm
If you don't come, it will be my
turn to say that senpai is a faggot
It's a date!