風花雪月汉化组译制，更多众筹作品与音声汉化相关加接待企鹅1-
594349181或群1011027379，转载请注明，谢谢配合
I've kept my promise
well, senpai
I'm glad you came to my room
Senpai, my room is very
girly and cute, isn't it?
The pink curtains and the
cute doll on the bed
Sweet smells good?
It's exactly like a girl's room
I'm just kidding... I don't think
you've ever been in a girl's room...
But, although you may understand
I'm not a girl
but not a faggot either
because I haven't
forgiven my seniors yet
Can I be punished for that?
It has nothing to do with
senpai's thoughts or arrangements
If I say punish, I'll
punish, that's all.
Come on, can you take
your top half off?
And then just, lie on
your back on the bed
I'm going to start
Mmmmmm~ I'm so
submissive as a dog
Yes, I'll keep you for that
So, first of all,
put the nipple...
and caress them
with your fingers
It's no problem, it won't hurt
Senpai will be happy
Here, touch it
You don't have to stop breathing
Slowly inhale and
exhale as you...
feeling the subtle
pleasure around my nipples
Yes, that's right, senpai~
Let me rub your nipples
together and get comfortable
I know...
Senpai's nipples are
particularly sensitive
So, I'll forgive you if you
use your nipples today
It's easy for all
of them, right?
Come on, it's only been a while
and already the nipples
are getting hard
It looks like it's
getting hot too
"Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha" and his
breathing has gotten messy
So sensual
Don't be afraid at all, senpai
No need to resist
Just accept the pleasure
that comes out of your body
The nipples are getting
hotter and hotter
The exhalation has
become chaotic
But even so
It's good that senpai's body is
becoming more and more sensitive
Enjoy the pleasure
with your fingertips
But then, senpai
Senpai knows that... The walls of
this dormitory are very thin, right?
If you scream too loudly,
other people will hear you
Watch out!
Senpai is a faggot if it's okay to expose the thing
that will become comfortable by playing with nipples
That's a different story
but... [06:42.78] almost want to taste
something different too, don't you?
Tired of being rubbed by
fingers all the time?
In that case, this...
How about this?
Putting saliva on the nipples
I'll give you a
squeeze this time
Senpai's nipples are
so wet from my saliva
So wet and nasty, befitting
of a perverted senpai
hurry up and grab the nipple
and start pinching it
Come on, squeeze it, squeeze it
Senpai's hard nipples
They look like they're
happy to be pinched
It's slightly more painful than rubbing
it with your fingertips, right?
Isn't that comfortable too?
I understand, senpai... it's very
comfortable to be pinched, isn't it?
I'm getting more and more excited,
and Ojinjin is getting hard too
But I'm not going
to touch Ojinjin
Please ask the perverted seniors
to cum with their nipples
Say, senpai, didn't I tell you
that the walls are very thin?
If it's that loud,
it'll be heard
Or will it be heard instead?
In that case, it's okay to
scream as much as you want
Give your humiliating
pant to the others
Come on, isn't it nice
to pinch your nipples?
More panting and panting
Scream louder
Yeah, yeah, that's right, senpai
It's great that you can
scream as much as you want
Do you want to go now?
Obviously Ojinjin didn't get touched, just
the nipples are becoming want to go ah
It's okay oh, go for it
obviously only the nipples are being
played with and Eugene gets hard and cums
After all, he's a senior, so it's better to have
your nipples twisted when you're there, right?
Twist it like this,
pinch it, pinch it
Come on, it's more comfortable
if it hurts a little bit, right?
Even if you let go of the nipple,
it's still hot and sensual
make the nipples wet with saliva
The hot sensation is
also very enjoyable
Senpai is really weird
You're not in a position to
say that about me, are you?
Eh? What? [12:40.71] It's okay to be
treated like an idiot by me... want to go?
If you want to be forgiven
by me, what do you do?
Senpai is really weird
but it doesn't matter it's
almost time for the appointment
Let's do a nipple orgasm
I'll forgive you
Go on, do it!
scream like a girl, get your
nipples played with and come
Go on, go on, go on, go on
biubiubiu~
Didn't that do it
Orgasm with nipples.
Did it happen?
I can't help it, I'll forgive
you for badmouthing me
But, I've got something to do
later, so that's enough for today
It's okay to sleep
in my bed like this
Good night~ senpai~