風花雪月汉化组译制，更多众筹作品与音声汉化相关加接待企鹅1-
594349181或群1011027379，转载请注明，谢谢配合
不妙要去了 要去了 要去了 射出 在里面射出
Cum! Fill Yukie with your cum!
Thank you~ My asshole
is already full!
And that's the end of your time
Next person ~ are you ready?
Senpai? [01:05.70]
[01:05.70] Senpai?
I've been seen!
Were you surprised?
To meet in such a strange place
Senpai come here too, right?
Standing there will make
the others suspicious
Come in quickly
Ah, I'm sorry, everyone, but I'm
in the middle of something.
but I just thought of
something interesting
Can I show you guys first?
Watch my asshole
get big and loose
That's it, there's a few things
I want to say to my seniors
Actually, I usually do it
in the toilet at this time
This was also after playing
with the former nipples before
in the toilet and having gay sex
Yeah, just like senpai said
I'm gay and I'm
having sex with men
although I don't know
why senpai would know
There's no need to hide it now
Come on, take a look, senpai
My ass is filled with your cum!
I had sex with several people
before senpai came to the bathroom
To be honest, I'm too
comfortable to remember
I honestly want you to
come in right now too
Stick an erect Ojinjin in...
although so far it's only been
with guys in the same grade
Only seniors are special
Please stick Ojinjin in
a cum-filled asshole
But relatively
don't tell anyone about this
Even if you're in the same grade,
you've done it with more than 50 people
I'm not going to be able to handle it
if we increase the number of people
Please keep it a secret
And there's one more
important thing
Actually, first timers don't
have the right to insert
you can only watch
yourself jerk off
There was a queue
to do it with me
but because senpai was a virgin
It's true that she's a virgin
In that case, it's special
Everyone ~ listen to me
Can we give the seniors priority
for virginity graduation?
I'm sorry it's taken so long, but
it's hard to be hard, isn't it?
Thank you, everyone is so gentle...
[05:18.44] I love it!
I'll let you have a
good time afterwards
So it's a long overdue
virginity graduation after all
Watch carefully, everyone!
It's okay to jerk off
to your own Ojinjin
So, senpai, thank you for
waiting, it's been a long time.
It's the virginity
graduation ceremony
Yukie's pussy is a mess
from other people's semen
It's easy to penetrate
I'll break it open
for good penetration
Come on, get it in
Senpai's Ojinjinjin
is inside my pussy!
It mixed with the cum that just
came out and made a dirty sound
Isn't that exciting?
Senpai~ Don't worry so much, just
swing your waist as much as you want
Virginity is just like
a monkey moving hard
Yeah, that's good
Just move your waist well and
rub your pussy with Ojinjin
Senpai's Eugene is
unexpectedly comfortable
It hit a very comfortable spot
and the sound couldn't stop
Virgin Ojinjin is so good
It's so comfortable~
What does my pussy feel like?
Senpai~
Isn't it comfortable? I'll suck on
senpai's ojin-jin and not let go
Of course it will be
comfortable, right?
Nah senpai look around you
Watching our lovemaking,
Ojinjin got a hard-on
And some people are jerking off
How about that? Is it
exciting to be watched?
Ojinjin is getting hard again... [09:57.20]
[09:57.20] I'm getting so hard inside
Wait, what's wrong? It's so
intense all of a sudden, senpai
Are you going to cum already?
Yes, I'm tired too.
Please cum in my pussy, senpai
Come on, come on, come on, come on...
[11:04.77] It's nice, isn't it?
Come on, shoot, shoot~
I'm going to go too...
[11:39.77] Go!
Senpai's hot semen
is pouring inside!
Senpai, congratulations on
your virginity graduation
Have more sex with
me in the future too