seniors What are you doing?
Senpai's room always
feels a little fishy
Did you think about me and
masturbate after that?
Senpai, I don't think you've had
any sex except for that day
I was very comfortable
too, and...
It's really exciting
to be watched
Eugene got a hard-on right away
But that's not what
this is about today
Senpai~ Please lend me money~
10,000 yen will be fine
Nah, it's okay, right?
10,000 is a bargain to
graduate with my virginity
Eh? What's it for?
I need some money for a date
with my girlfriend soon
Huh? I've got a girlfriend.
No, it's not good to not have
a girlfriend at this age
Senpai~ Don't you
have a girlfriend?
I'm sorry~ I wouldn't have graduated
with my virginity if I had
By the way, I graduated as a
virgin with my girlfriend
Faggot senpai~ Not
happy about it?
I have a cute girlfriend even if I'm
being penetrated by a man's meat stick
Really, don't be silent, senpai
You're not... Are you jealous?
Or are you just excited about
a faggot with a girlfriend?
Does the loser Ojinjin still
want to stick it in me?
Well, as long as you're
willing to pay me
And let you violate
as much as you want
Come on, take off your
clothes and throw them away
And then let me move myself
Just lie on your back, senpai
Ah, but can you jerk off Ojinjin
first and let him stand for a while?
Slowly, swallow Ojinjin
I'm sure we'll have to
untie it after all~
Otherwise it's
completely inaccessible
Finally, they're all in
How's that?
The asshole of a man
with a girlfriend
It's pretty attractive for
a loser Ojinjin, isn't it?
I want to get the money and enjoy
a date with my girlfriend soon
Let me get comfortable and move
I'm pretty good at
riding the seat
although when I do it with my
girlfriend it's from the bottom
The feeling of the pie shaking,
that's very exciting just to watch
My girlfriend is two years younger than
me and has been dating for six months
It's obviously a boys' school, want
to know how you met it, right?
That... posted a female
selfie on SNS again
There was a girl who said
"I want to DM for sex"
I had sex with her so many
times that I fell in love
A girl's pussy is
very comfortable
The bliss of a condomless
stroke is very unpleasant
But the ex of the queer jitterbug
Ojinjin also came out on the man me
Can you understand
that feeling too?
wrapped in the warmth of my body
The feeling of Eugene's pussy
wrapping around him and contracting
It's overwhelming, isn't it?
Well, after all, I've said
"like" a lot to my girlfriend
And I want to do it for
as long as possible...
with a senior who doesn't like it and doesn't
really want to be paid for it either
I really want it to end soon
hurry up and cum, faggot
jiggle m Ojinjin-san~
but... you're not satisfied until
you play with your nipples?
because it's very exciting and
the nipples are already erect
It's getting very lickable
Just by licking the nipples,
Ojinjin gets harder or something
How much do you
really like nipples
Come on, I'll move
my waist well too
Come on come on out
Make a humiliating
sound and come
Eh, you want to ask
me about that?
I'm still pretty comfortable too
It's not bad at all
but today I'm planning to make more
comfortable love with my girlfriend
I'm not going to cum now
Seniors just cum alone
Let's get moving!
Let's shoot! [10:17.42] Shoot!
Faggoty jerky losers
won't stand for it!
Shoot it, shoot it
Come on, cum!
I'm cumming!
but I don't have time
to pull out Ojinjin
Even if you make that
lonely face - no
I don't like senpai
or anything either
The only real affectionate
sex is with my girlfriend
Of course, it's the same
with other students too
That's just a sexual
thing to deal with
After all, it's good to get rid of
each other's sexual desires, right?
So, senpai, I'm
borrowing the money
There's a late-night fuck
party in the toilet tonight
I'll be waiting for you byebye~