Prologue.
Welcome home, mister... ♪
Good work, sir... ♪
...... what?　Are you dressed like this ......?
This is the formal dress of one who welcomes a husband...
How do you like it?　I'm ...... wearing a naked apron...
Is it a pretty ......?
...... yes... Thank you...
So ...... sir?　How would you like it?
Dinner?　Bath?　Or ...... phew...
Nn...... ♪ chu...... chu, rero...... nnchu, nnchu...... chu, chu Choo, choo, choo......♪
Hah......♪
Ah......♪ Master's kisses...... feel too good...... I feel so disgusting... ....
The front of my apron bulges out, flabby and ...... embarrassing, I'm ......♪
...... phew...
But your husband says that's ...... cute too ......♪ Thank you ......♪
Sir ......♪
The Master ...... chose me as his companion ....... He has promised me a future ......♪
He made me, a man's daughter, his ...... bride. ......♪
Such a husband, I love ......♪
Amu......♪ Nnnn, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn. Â ......♪
Hah ......♪
So ......♪
I'll serve you a lot, ...... and I'll serve you a lot. ...... Please hold me today, Master. ......♪
Please give me your hard cock in my ass cunt ......♪ Master, please give me your hard cock ......♪
I'm already getting ...... cock ...... excited too ......♪
So ...... sir... ♪
Please love me ...... a lot♪