Mmm... this way, mister...
Yes, sir... just lie down on the bed, sir...
You can leave your clothes on too... I'll fold them later...
I'm more interested in serving the Master now...
Okay, I'm going to take off my ...... clothes.
I can't wait to see your master's cock .........
N......sho, nsho......♪
ah......♪
Master's ...... cock...... is already hard...... ♪ It's so stiff, so big, so nice... ♪
You're expecting me to serve you, aren't you? ...... ♪ I'm so happy... ♪ Hmm... ♪
Well, I'll serve you in a man's pussy ...... ass cunt right now... ♪
What ......?　Do you want to see my ...... penis, too ......?
It's such a ...... shame, it is ....... But ...... if your husband says so, .......
Aprons ...... are lifted up, sir. ......
Nn...... ♪
Oh my God, I'm so embarrassed, I'm so embarrassed. ...... Sir,......... my little cock,...... is so tiny,...... it's growing,...... and it's going,...... ping,...... ping,...... ping,...... ping,...... ping! .......
Just seeing your husband's penis ...... not only makes my ass cunt excited, but also my penis ....... It's like this: .......
No...... so much, don't look at my penis, mister......♪ I'm so embarrassed ...... because you can see that I'm so excited. I'm ......♪
It's all over... Oh, my God... ......... Let me serve you quickly with my ass-cunt... .........
I'll fuck you with all my pussy. ...... you don't have to move. ......♪ I'll fuck you with my ass cunt as hard as I can ......♪ as your wife. I will fuck you with my ass-cunt......♪
I'm going to take Master's hard cock......♪ I'm going to hold it in my hand and put it in my ass-cunt......♪
What ......?　Oh, ...... ♪ Oh, don't worry, sir. ...... ♪
My ass-cunt already belongs to Master ......♪ I want to serve Master's cock as soon as possible, my ass-cunt is so debauched ......♪ So... ...I'm ready to be fucked anytime I want. .........
So ...... mister don't worry about anything, penis, just feel good ......♪
Now I'm going to ...... put it in. ......♪ Keep it like this, cowgirl. ......♪
Mmm......♪
Huh......... hah... ah......... mmm... ah... ah.........
......♪
I feel like I've already ...... been penetrated by half of my body ......... ♪ Master's cock ...... is too big... ♪ ...♪
You're so excited about my ass cunt ......♪ I'm so happy ......♪
Sir ...... ♪ I love you ...... ♪
Mmm......
Mmm...... mmm, mmm ...... mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm ......
P, hah......♪
Pff ......♪ I'm going to pussy you a lot, mister ......♪
Please make me feel good, penis, in a man girl's eh pussy. ......♪
Mmm......... ah......... ah, ah, ah, ah... ah......... mmm... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ................................
Mister ......... ♪ Oh, man, my man cock is hard... ...... ♪ Oh, man, my man cock is big... ...... ♪ Oh, my man cock is big... ♪ ...so much... ♪ Oh, come on, come on, come on... ♪ Oh, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on... ♪ Oh, yeah... ........
Fuaaa......... haaaa... mmmm... ahhh... ......... ♪
Sir, oh, my God, ....... My, my cunt ....... How do you like my ass cunt? .......
Does your cock feel good ......?　Am I doing my ...... pussy right ......? Am I serving ...... your husband's penis properly......?
Nn.........
Haa......♪
Master ......... Your manhood feels so good ......... You can feel it with his gentle kisses .........
Then ......... I'll do my best to make your pussy even more ......... I'll make your ass cunt tight and ......... I'll make your cock feel so good, Master. I'm going to make your cock feel so good ....... My asshole is ...... a dirty cunt for Master's cock only. ......
Mmm......... ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah......... mmm, ha, ha, ha, ha, ah.........
Hah, ah....... Pussy, too hard. ....... My apron is ripped open and I can't ....... You can see my cock again. ...... I'm going along with the pistons of your ass-cunt, ....... I can see a lot of my cock quivering ....... It's embarrassing. ......
Sir, oh ....... Please don't look at me too much. ......
Oh, ....... Your penis is so cute. ....... Sir, ....... Please don't say that. .......
If you say such a thing, ...... I'll be so happy ....... It makes me want to serve you more and more. ......
Mmm....... Haaaaahhh ....... Oh, oh, your cock is amazing, your cock, it's so hard......... Huhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh.
No, no... ......... I have to serve Master's cock... ......... I'm enjoying ass cunt, ass sex... ...Â...Â Master's cock feels too good... .........
I want to serve you properly, but ....... I always end up ruining my pussy. ...... I want more and more cock ...... and I want to take it in my ass-cunt .......
Master ....... I'm sorry for being a bad wife. ...... I'm sorry I'm the wife of an erotic man's daughter. ......
Haa......♪
Sir, you are .........
Sir, you can be a ...... eh wife, can't you? ......♪
Master ah....... I'm so happy ......... I love you... I love you, Master...
I like your penis... I like your penis, Master... I like your penis... I like your penis fuck... I like your ass cunt fuck... ......
Mister, I'll fuck you more ......... I'll fuck you more... I want a man cock... I want a man cock... I want a man cock... I want a man cock .........
Mmm......, ah, ah, ah, ah......, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah......, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah......, ah, ah, ah, ah... ass cunt... ...ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah ......... ♪
Oh .........Â My cock, it's jiggling .........Â A lot of ......, jiggling in my ass cunt...
I'm so happy for you, sir. ...... ♪
Yes, of course. ......... inside... inside, please... inside, please... inside, please... inside, please... inside, please... inside, please... inside, please... inside, please... inside, please... inside, please... inside, please... inside, please... inside, please.
I want hot cock milk... I want hot, thick, master's cock milk... ......... I want to drink a lot of it in my ass-cunt... .........
So ...... mister.........
Finally, ......, I'm going to fuck you hard ......, I'm going to fuck your manhood hard ......, I'm going to fuck you in the ass-cunt a lot ......, and I'm going to milk your cock a lot ......, a lot. Please milk my cock. .........
......... ♪ Cunt, cunt, cunt ...... ♪
Yes, ......... ♪ Mister ......, come in ......... ♪
Yes, piüsss, piüsss, doo piüsss, doo piüsss, doo piüsss, doo piüsss, doo piüsss, doo piüsss ......
Huh, ah....... Hah, ah ......... Hah, ah .........
Penis ...... thumping ...... inside cunt ......... ♪ Milk, lots of milk... ♪ ...Hot, cock, so much milk......, so much milk......, so much milk......, so much milk......, so much milk......, so much milk......, I'm about to make a baby... ... ♪
And ...... I also ...... came, I came, I came ....... My ass pussy ...... and my cock .......
I'm going to .......
Chuuu...... chuuu...... chuuu, chuuu....... N, chuuuuu...... chuuuuu...... chuuu.......
Ha, ah.......
Sir, ...... sorry, please. I felt so good, my penis, I came. ...... sir, my milk, it got on me. ......
...... eh?　Huh. ....... Already. 'I'm glad I made you feel better', what a ....... Your husband is a little too kind. ...... I wanted to serve the Master. ......
But ....... Thank you, Master. ......
Such a kind husband, I love him. ......♪
Hmmm... ...... ♪ Master... ♪ Please let me serve you again tomorrow, a lot... ...... ♪
I am the Master's wife... ♪