Welcome back. Sir,Â
Good day, good day, good day... ♪
What?　Today's outfit?　...... already. I don't wear a naked apron every day. ...... ♪ I was quite embarrassed ...... when Master saw me in my sluttiness... ♪
But ...... sir?　As soon as you get home, you can have your cock nuked ...... every day...
Hmmm... ...... ♪ Can I serve your cock today, too?　Sir... ♪
...... yes ♪
Today, yes. ...... If you do it the same way every day, you will get bored. ......
...... Hmm... Well, come here, mister...
Yes, sir... Sit down here on the sofa...
So ...... I'll leave you, too, neighbour. ...... ♪
Hmmm... ......... Sir... ......... Today's service is... .........
...... hooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
Hhhhhh, nnnnnn, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn .......
Hah......♪
Huh ......♪ Master liked to tickle your ears, as I recall, didn't he?
How about an ear licking hand job, ...... where you lick your Master's cock while he licks your ears?
...... Yes♪
So, ...... first of all, I'm going to take your husband's penis out of the ......♪
Nn...... sho, nn.......
Ah......♪ Hmm......♪ Master's cock...... is already growing so tight and big... ...Â He's very well dressed and ...... always has a nice cock...
Now, hold this cock, squeezing it tight ......... ♪
Up and down, shh, shh, shh ......♪
Keep going, keep going, keep going, keep going, keep going, keep going, keep going, keep going, keep going. ......♪
Chun, rero, rero, chu, chu, chu, chu, chu, chu, chu, chu, chu, chu, chu, chu ......♪
Hah ......♪
Whenever I lick his ear, his body shivers and his cock feels so good.... ... ♪
You're so cute, mister. ...... ♪ Feel your cock more and more... ...... ♪
Chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug ......♪
Hah ......♪
Penis, does it feel good?　Sir ......♪ My ear licking hand job makes your cock feel good ......♪
Hmmm ......♪ I'm a man's daughter, so I have a good point ......♪ In case you're wondering, I have the same thing on me ......♪ Where your dick feels good. I know exactly what it feels like. ......♪
For example,...... if you crunch your finger on the turtle of your dick to tease it,...... it makes you squeal,...... ♪ and if you poke your finger on the back muscle,...... ♪ it makes you squeal,...... ♪ and if you poke your finger on the back muscle,...... ♪ it makes you squeal. When you run your fingers along the back muscles or scratch the neck of your penis with your finger, it makes you feel a little bit ......
I know all about what feels good about your husband's cock. ......♪
So, lick his ears while you stroke his cock a lot ......♪
Nnnngggg, nngg, nngg, nngg, nngg, nngg, nngg, nngg, nngg, nngg, nngg, nngg, nngg, nngg, nngg, nngg, nngg, nngg .......
Haa......♪
...... ♪ Oh, my man, he's so jumpy ...... ♪ And there's so much clear ooze ...... ♪ coming out of the tip of his cock ...... ♪ and it's just dripping ...... ♪ ...... ♪ And there's a lot of clear ooze coming out of the tip of his penis. ...... ♪
When your penis has risen to this level, you can squeeze it with your hand and rub it ......♪
Mmm......♪ Mister, I can't help but sit up and feel it......♪ Does your cock feel good......♪?　Hmmm...
It's okay, penis, feel it a lot. ......♪
Jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz......
Mmm, hah......♪
Master's face, it's so melty. ......♪ His manhood, it looks so nice. ......♪
I'm still the Master's wife. ......♪ I'm learning how to make him feel good. ......♪
By the way, ...... master?　Don't you miss your left ear when you only blame your right ear ......?
I'll serve you there, too. ......♪
If you'll excuse me for a moment, ...... ♪ nsho ...... nsho ...... nsho ...... ♪
Hmm ......♪ Now excuse me from here ......♪
You're going to have to re-grip your dick, squeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee! ......
Now, the left ear ......♪
Aaaammmm ......♪
Nnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnn Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â ...... nchu, chuppah, chuppah, chuppah, chuppah, chuppah, chuppah, chuppah, chuppah......
Hah ......♪
Hmmm ......♪ Master is feeling very much in this ear too ......♪ Both ears are very easy to feel and ...... cute! ......♪
Please make your cock feel better and better. ......♪
Phew......♪
Oh, ...... ♪ My man parts are getting more and more jittery ...... ♪ Hmm, ...... ♪ Are you getting more and more cock milk from your balls? Is your penis getting milk from your balls? ......
I think my balls are getting hotter under my penis. ......♪ I can feel the milk simmering inside. ......♪
Please make lots of penis milk and let it out ...... lots of penis milk, testicles. ......♪
Amu......♪
Mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm... ...jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz, jizz. Sizzle, sizzle, sizzle, sizzle, sizzle, sizzle, sizzle, sizzle, sizzle, sizzle, sizzle, sizzle, sizzle, sizzle, sizzle, sizzle, sizzle...
Haa......♪
Oh ......♪ My manhood, it's shaking ......♪ Master's breathing, he's breathing hard ......♪
Mister, your manhood is about to come. ......... hot, sloppy cock milk, you're going to make me squeal. .........
Yes, of course, sir... I want a lot of cock milk... I want a lot of cock milk... I want a lot of cock milk... I want a lot of cock milk... I want a lot of cock milk in my hand...
I'm going to do a lot of hand movements and ear flicking...
Cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock, cock. Nnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnn. ......
Yes ......♪ Go ahead, mister ......♪
Yes, piüss, piüss, do piüss, do piüss, do piüss, do piüss, do piüss, do piüss, do piüss, do piüss, do piüss, do piüss, do piüss, do piüss, do piüss, do piüss, do piüss, do piüss, do piüss, do piüss ......♪
... ♪
It was so much, so ...... sticky, so thick ......... ......... ......... ......... ......... I can see that he felt my manhood a lot.
I'm so happy for you, mister. ......♪
But ....... It's a waste of penis milk ...... that you've gone to the trouble of pipping me, sir. ......
Can I have this milk ......?　Fufu ......♪ Please let me sip it all ......♪
Amu...... n-churr, churr, churr, n-churr, n-churr, n-churr, n-churr .......
Kok ...... Kok, Kok ...... Kok.
Kok...... nn.
Haa......♪
I got it, sir. ......♪
It was very thick and delicious ...... wonderful penis milk ......♪ Hmmm ......♪
Good work, sir... ♪
How was my service to you today?
...... Yes... I'm glad you're satisfied...
I also ...... enjoyed ...... seeing so many cute things about my ...... husband...
I'll do it again anytime you want... Master...