Welcome back, sir... ♪
Today is Friday, so ...... you're off tomorrow, aren't you?
Yes, sir... Thank you for a good week, sir...
We can spend some time together today... ♪
What?　Oh, yes... I put on the naked apron again... Master seemed to like this outfit a lot. .........
......Yes... I'm ...... glad you think I'm pretty...
...... pfffft... Eeeeeeeeeeee...
Squeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee!
Dear all...
I love you. ...... I love you...
I love you ...... ♪
N......Chu, chu, chu ......rero, nchu ......chu, chu, chu, chu u, nchu ......♪
Hah ......♪
Huh ......♪ Mister, I love you ......♪
......a♪
I feel ...... a very hard touch on my belly... ♪
Sir,......... did the kiss turn you on,......?
Hmmm ......♪ Naughty master ......♪
But ...... eh, I'm the same way ......♪
When I wear a naked apron,...... Master loves me a lot,...... so I imagine that, and I can't think of anything but eecchi... ...♪
Sir, oh, ...... ♪
Amu...... mmmm, relllllll, mmmm, relllll, mmmm, mmmm, mmmm, mmmm, mmmm, mmmm, mmmm, mmmm, mmmm, mmmm, mmmm, mmmm, mmmm, mmmm......♪
Hah ......♪
Please hold me ......, mister ♪
I can't think of anything else but ...... my cock... ...... my eejit cunt is so tingling... ...... I want a cock now... I'm so hungry ......♪
So ...... mister ...... ♪
...... yes ♪ Then to bed ...... ♪
What do you want to ...... do today?
...... sir, are you going to move?
Yes ...... ♪ I'm so happy ♪ Then please poke my ass cunt a lot ...... ♪ Mister ♪
Mmm......Chuck, lilo, chuck, chuck, lilo, lilo, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn, nnnn, chuck, nnnn, chuck, nnnn, nnnn......♪
Hah ......♪
...... Ahh... ♪ Oh, Master, his cock, he took it out of his clothes ...... ♪
It's amazing......♪ It's already tickling......♪ Big, cool, nice cock......♪ I love it! ......♪
Yes ......♪ Come anytime, mister ......♪ My ass cunt is already melting ......♪
Mmm...... ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.........
Oh, ......... my dick, it's coming in... ......... in my ass... in my cunt... .........
Ha, ha, ha, ah......... ♪ Oh, ......, did you get it all in, ......?　Hmph,...... Master's cock is too big,...... ♪ I think my tummy is all filled up,...... ♪
Yes, ...... ♪ It's okay, ...... ♪ You can move anytime ...... ♪ It's not enough to be put in... ...Â ...Â ...Â ...Â ...Â ...Â ...Â ...Â ...Â ...Â ...Â ...I want more and more cock in my ass cunt.......
...I want more and more of your cock in my ass-cunt... ......♪ ......... Â™" The cock is penetrating deep into the girl's cunt. ......... Â™" Oh, ah, ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ...... ♪
Nn......ah, nn...... ♪ Apron, don't roll it up, please ...... ♪ My cock... ...I can see it... ......... my little, big, boy's penis... .........
But ...... Master says my penis is cute and he likes it too ......♪ He says it's very exciting ......♪　So ...... I don't mind if he sees me ......... ......... and wanks my growing cock ......... and my cock... and my cock... Please make me more excited. ......♪
Ah......... haaaaaa......... mmmm... hmmm... ahhh... .........
Every time Master ......... pokes his cock, ......... my cock shudders and quivers again, ......... very, very, very dirty... It's ....... But ...... it feels so good. ......
The feeling of ass-cunt feels so good ......, I can feel it in my cock too... ......... it feels so good... ......... ahhh... Ohhhh... .........
Sir ......... Sir, sir... Oh, sir... .........
Nn......, chu......♪ chu, chu, chu......♪ nn, nn, chu, chu, chu, chu, chu, chu Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â ......
Haa......♪
Master ah......... I like, I like, I like Master's cock... I like to pussy with Master... I like to have Master poke my ass pussy... I like to have Master poke my ass pussy... I like it... .........
I love cock... I love cock... I love cock... ......... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... .........
Master ah......... Master ah......... made me his wife ah......... a man's daughter, me... ah......... ...Â...Â He married me and told me he loved me.........
Not long ago I was ...... anxious ....... I'm a man's daughter, so ...... I wondered if I would be a good wife ....... I wondered if it would be okay for me to be by my wonderful husband's side. ......
But ......, Master always ...... always always loves me a lot ....... He makes my cock feel good by my service,......... He says I'm pretty,......... He says I'm lovely,......... He says he loves me,.........
So I don't have ...... anxiety anymore......... I can feel how he feels a lot......... He feels the same way. I already know that he feels the same......... .........
So, Master, please give me a penis ......... ......... more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more.
I belong to Master ......... I don't belong to anyone else ......... I'm devoted to Master... I love only Master... I don't care what he does to me. ...... ♪
I'll listen to any kind of naughty wish if it's from ...... the Master. ......♪
So, mister, please give me a man cock... man cock, man cock... man cock, man cock... poke me all over my ass cheeks with your man cock... ......... tell me that you love me... tell me that you love me... man cock... ♪ Oh, give me a man-po, man-po, man-po ...... ♪
Mmm.........mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm...mmm....mmm...
Haa......♪
Oh ......... my man cock ......... it's getting hard... ......... I can feel it throbbing inside my ass-cunt... .........
Oh, master... ......... You're about to come... ......... Your manhood feels so good... .........
Yes, ......... Yes, of course, sir... ......... When you do it, make sure you do it inside... ......... In the ass-cunt, in the ass-cunt, in the ass-cunt... Please put your cock milk inside me. ......... ♪ Don't put it outside me. ......... ♪
I want to feel all of Master's stuff inside ....... ......... I want to feel the warmth of his cock milk in my ass cunt. .........
So ......, please give it to me inside... man-pussy milk... man-pussy cum... man-pussy cum... please give it all to me inside your ass-cunt... ......
♪ Oh, man, so much ass ...... ♪
♪
......... ♪ Yes, come in, mister... ...... ♪
...... Oh, ......... ♪ Oh, man, man, man, man... ♪ Oh, man, man... ♪ Oh, man, man... ♪ Oh, man, man, man... ♪ Oh, man, man, man... ♪ ......... he's pouring... ......... into my tummy...
Inside my ass cunt, inside ...... hot ...... ♪ I love the way my husband ...... loves me ...... It's warm, it's ......♪
And ...... I, too, my body got hot and ...... ♪ man-cubicle, I came ...... ♪ man-cubicle, I came ...... ♪ man-cubicle, I got milk from my man-cubicle, I got milk, I got milk from my man-cubicle, I got milk from my man-cubicle. ......♪ I got so much milk on my belly ......♪ I think I've never had so much ......♪ before! ......♪
You made me feel good too, didn't you, ......♪ Mister ......♪
Mmm......♪
Chuu...... chuu, chuu...... chuu, chuu...... chuu, chuu...... chuu Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â ......
Hah......♪
If I get served in my pussy like this, ...... baby, I might be able to do it. ......♪
...... phew... ♪
Sir ......♪ Thank you ......♪ for loving me so much ......♪
...... Ha! ♪ It felt so good ...... ♪
Well then, ...... sir?　After a break, let's have dinner... I've prepared a delicious supper...
So ...... when you're full, you can take a bath together ......
And then we'll do eh, eh, eh again...
I had Master move me around a lot and tell me how much he loves me. ......
Next time, I'm going to move... I'm going to make your cock feel so good in my ass cunt...
I won't let you sleep tonight, Master...
Because I'm ...... Master's wife... ♪