Extra.
Sir,Â Welcome home...
How shall I serve your cock today? Do you have any requests?
Um, ...... would you like me to masturbate with you ......?
Eh, eh!　Well, are you going to masturbate with me again, ......?
...... Mou. Master pervert. Of all the things to do, masturbation is ....... Really, it's so embarrassing. ...... ♪
But ...... if your husband is happy with it, ...... I can't help it... ♪
Then I'll whisper, "cock-sucking," ...... and you can match that pace, Master.
Hmmm. Come and masturbate with me, ......♪
Penis, shiko, shiko. Penis, shiko, shiko.
Penis, shiko, shiko. Penis, shiko, shiko, shiko.
Penis, shimmy, shimmy. Penis, shimmy, shimmy.
Penis, squish. Penis, sucking.
Penis, squish. Penis, squish.
Penis, squishy. Penis, squishy.
Penis, squishy. Penis, sucking.
Penis, squishy. Penis, sissy.
Penis, squish. Penis, sucking.
Penis, penis, tickle. Penis, penis, tickle.
Dick-squeezing. Penis-squeezing.
Penis-stuffing. Penis-squeezing.
Dick-squeezing. Dick ticking.
Dick-squeezing. Penis-squeezing.
Penis-stuffing. Penis-sticking.
......... Yes, sir, sir... ......... I'm cumming. .........
Ah......, hah, hah, hah......♪
Penis, I came, I came, I came ....... The thought of masturbating with my husband, with my husband, I got ...... excited, I got ...... excited.
I've cum a lot, I've cum so much. ......
Ugh, embarrassing, it is. ......
How did he ...... feel, sir?　Did you feel good, penis, ......?　My penis, did you have a wank ......?
Ah......♪
...... Yes... ...... ♪ Good... ♪
If you don't mind me saying this, ...... you can always request it again. Sir,Â Â Â Â Â Â
...... every day, because it's embarrassing, but not every day.