風花雪月汉化组翻译制，更多众筹作品与音声汉化相关加接待企鹅821731317或通知群773800845，转载请注明，谢谢配合
Thank you for coming to the shop
You are the guest who made the reservation, right?
I've been waiting for you for a long time
Come on, this way please
Please sit here
So before we start
I will have a brief psychological consultation
if you have any requests
please feel free to ask me
The set menu you ordered this time
It's the nipple development package, isn't it?
There are many other options
If you have a request, you can just ask
as there are customers of all interests coming to the shop
So don't be shy!
"Today I want to feel pleasure only with my nipples"
the sensation?
Mmmmmm
So that's it
although you tried to touch your nipples yourself
but you didn't get any pleasure
Are you trying to become able to masturbate with your nipples?
Or do you want to be like a girl
do you want to get pleasure from having your nipples played with?
like that?
Mmmmmm
Ah...so
mmmmmm
Mmm...hmm
So that's how it is
You and your girlfriend are not physically compatible
not satisfying her
and you're worried about that
If I could feel the pleasure like a girl
you could also satisfy your girlfriend
You think so
If you're trying to experience what it's like to be a girl
wouldn't it be a little bit better if the other person was male?
If you think it's better to be male
We also have male staff on this side
What do you plan to do?
Well~
So how about this?
You pretend to be a girl
and then do it with me
Yeah, put on girl's clothes and makeup
And become a girl completely
What do you think?
Lace?
Will it turn out like this?
Do you hate it when I do h things?
If you don't find it annoying
Do you want to try it?
because you're smaller in stature
and more neutral looking
I think it would suit you very well
It's quite comfortable to dress up as a girl and do it
It's not weird at all
There are quite a few of these customers
because I like to do h things to cute girls
so I want you to do that
Nah, how about that?
It's okay
I'm gonna make you nice and cozy
! Really? So happy!
because there's the additional cost of renting clothes and makeup
It's going to cost a little bit more, that's okay, right?
Thank you
Then please proceed to the dressing room
This way, please
It's okay
It will definitely suit you