風花雪月汉化组翻译制，更多众筹作品与音声汉化相关加接待企鹅821731317或通知群773800845，转载请注明，谢谢配合
Please sit on the chair over here
Are you a little bit nervous?
After all, it's your first time doing makeup
It's okay, please relax
So here we go
Let's start with the lotion
Your skin looks great
Do you usually take care of it?
Obviously not
I'm jealous that your skin is still so good
What kind of makeup would you like to try?
Something more flamboyant, or something more lovely
If it's you
It would be more of a cute type
Okay, then I'll give you a cute makeup
So then I'll start applying the foundation
Spread it with your fingers
so that it fits into the skin
Is your heart beating faster?
It's okay
Because you're already a good-looking person
It's going to be perfect for you
I'm going to start applying it to the corners of my eyes
Please close your eyes
You can open your eyes now
How about that?
Did you just put on a base makeup
It's a completely different look
It's a strange feeling?
So now it's time to start the eye makeup
Let's use this light pink eyeshadow
(Note: the heroine doesn't use honorifics after this sentence)
because you're supposed to look like a girl
so with a little bit of makeup
and you'll look cute
Well, that feels good
It's nice to look good with makeup, isn't it?
Next up is... this
This is called an eyelash curler
Use this to curl your eyelashes
and your eyes will look big
Well, that's pretty much it
So then with the eyeliner
with a little bit of emphasis on the eyeliner
and don't move it around
Yeah, there's a lot more
Eye makeup can change a person's impression to a great extent
You have to do it properly
What's wrong?
because my face is too close to yours
So it's starting to get tense?
Did your heart start to beat faster?
I'm going to do lots and lots of h things to you next
So relax now
That's nice
because you have very angular eyes
we do a slight drooping eyeliner at the corner of the eye
Let's make it even cuter
Oops~
And the other side too...
Well, that's cute
Next, brush your lashes slightly with mascara
Ugh?
You say I look happy?
Because ~ you're getting cuter and cuter, so my emotions are getting high too
Your eyes are getting really cute
And then a little bit of eyebrow pencil
Ugh? What's going on?
Yeah, makeup is really hard
But it's nice to make people cuter and cuter like this
Well, it's perfect!
Your eyes are so cute
So next is blush
What are you shy about?
It's okay, it's perfect for you
You look very shy
You look like a girl too
Aren't you getting into it a little bit too?
That's fine
Let's get even cuter
Which lipstick do you use?
Let's use this one with a slight orange tint
It feels great
And finally, let's put on the wig
I think you're more suited to long hair
Here, turn your head a little bit towards me
Oops...
Well, it's really cute
Nah, do you want to see it?
Look at yourself in the mirror
How does it look?
Doesn't it feel like you?
You're the cute girl in the mirror
How's that? Are you happy?
Isn't that a bit strange?
So let's get dressed
First of all... start with the underwear
Is that par for the course
Wouldn't you rather?
Not unwillingly?
You wear this next set of underwear
And this camisole
What's wrong with you?
Are you shy about being looked at by me?
In that case, you can use the fitting room here
Let me see it when you're done
Can you put on a bra properly by yourself?
How about that? Is it over?
Can I open it?
Ah, it's really ~ lovely
It really suits you
Are you happy?
Nah, are you happy?
What kind of clothes do you want to wear?
I've got everything
Do you want a student uniform?
Do you want a suit-style student uniform or a sailor uniform?
Suit style?
Hold on a second
Suit uniforms...suit uniforms...
Okay, put it on
Are you happy you can wear the uniform?
It suits you!
It really looks like a girl
And it doesn't look out of place on the street
Ahh, it's really cute!
A little more perfume
How about that?
Now your body is smelling sweet and fragrant
That's right...
Let's come up with a name
since it's gotten so cute
We have to come up with a name
What kind of name do you want?
Can I help you with that?
Hmmm ~ Tele...
Can I call you Xiao Yao?
I'm happy that you like that name
So, we're going out next
You put on these shoes
Just think about it there's only the living room dressing room and the fitting room
There are other places to go if you want to start conditioning
Let's go for a walk together
Do you feel shy about going out like this?
Absolutely no one will notice, don't worry!
Okay?
Let's hold hands and go out for a walk