風花雪月汉化组翻译制，更多众筹作品与音声汉化相关加接待企鹅821731317或通知群773800845，转载请注明，谢谢配合
What's wrong with you? Are you nervous?
If you keep looking down, you'll be suspicious instead
You have to walk with your head up
Eh? It's not weird at all.
Two girls walking holding hands or something
Look at those two people in front of you
also two girls holding hands
There's no one watching them, is there?
So we were both holding hands
and there won't be any problems
Just hold it a little tighter
(laughs) Xiao Yao, what kind of girls do you like?
Yeah, I like cute girls.
You like the same type of girls as you do now
Because ~
I can tell by the look on your face when you see yourself with makeup on
Even you think it's cute, don't you?
Don't be shy
It's really cute after all
As a woman, I'm a little jealous
Can I take your hand, Xiao Yao?
Can you?
What's wrong?
A little shy?
That's cute~
How far is it to your destination, you ask?
Well, a few minutes away, right?
What's wrong?
Do you want to be done with the h thing soon?
Your heartbeat is coming from the arm we're holding
Can you feel my heartbeat?
When I think of all the things I could do to you
and it's getting exciting
you're so shy
you really look more like a girl
How about that?
Are you getting to the point where you don't care what people think?
Because you look like a girl no matter what
You could be a little more confident
You'll be more comfortable if you're completely a girl
What's wrong?
You asked if you couldn't get into the hotel if you wore a uniform.
We're not going to a hotel
It's an apartment building that we've rented
Don't worry about it
By the way, can I stop by the shop?
Yeah, it's a bookstore
Is it this way again?
Found it, found it
Do you know this comic?
It's a manga about love between girls based on the theme of lilies
You asked me if it's a h book.
although it's not 18 forbidden
Here, take a look
It does have a bit of an erotic scene to it
like kissing, or hugging each other, or touching each other
Or even this scene
Putting your hand under your skirt and touching
The content is kinda h, right?
Nah, pick the next thing you want me to reproduce from this comic
What do you want?
Which one would it be? Which one would it be?
So that's what you like
Held from behind
And whispering in your ear
while being licked in the ear and having her breasts fondled
You want me to do things like that
So that's what happened
Nah, it doesn't matter if it's a little bit quieter
Can I please try this?
"Please do this to me"
Hurry up
It's okay oh
Is there anything else you want me to do?
Nipples... what do you want me to do with your nipples?
Because you want to get comfortable with your nipples, right?
You want to be played with hard by me
And finally become as sensual as a girl, right?
Say "please play with my nipples" and beg me
Hurry up
You can do it
I'll make you feel better
Even if you tell me to stop in the middle
I'll keep going until you get weird, so be aware of that
So let's go
You're pretty m?
You're into angst play, right?
Heart racing from anticipation
It's the flat around the corner oh
You can see a beautiful night view from the 30th floor of the penthouse
Nah, Xiao Yao
Let me kiss you, right?
Come on, come over here