風花雪月汉化组翻译制，更多众筹作品与音声汉化相关加接待企鹅821731317或通知群773800845，转载请注明，谢谢配合
Come this way
Look, the night view is beautiful, isn't it?
I just kissed you in the lift, sorry about that
You're really cute
You really do look like a girl
What's wrong with you?
Are you shy about staring at me?
Um...
Hmmm~
It's really cute
I'll do lots of nice things for you
Can you be just my little Yao today?
Really?
I'm so happy!
Is it shy to walk down the street dressed as a girl?
You look like a girl when you're shy too
When you're gazing at me like this
I can't hold back my feelings anymore
Your head is filled with thoughts of wanting to be done to me
You want to make erotic moans like a girl while you enjoy the pleasure
want to be comfortable ~ want to be anxiously played ~ want to be bullied ~
Nipples want to be played with to their heart's content
Rubbing or twisting with fingertips
Pinching ~ licking ~ sucking ~
And then orgasm with just the nipples
You want to feel the "nipple orgasm", right?
Nah, you promise me one thing
You're not allowed to have an orgasm with a stick today
but I might touch it a little bit
I'm not going to make you cum by rubbing against it
Let's forget about the male pleasure
Let's remember the female pleasure
Got it?
And your answer?
It's important what you say next
I want you to remember
If you want to be comfortable like a girl
you can't just go for the pleasure
You have to focus on receiving pleasure
Focus your attention on receiving pleasure and superimposing it
and you'll naturally taste stronger pleasure
Got it?
Although once you taste it once, you can never go back
That's okay, right?
Let's engrave female pleasure into your body
Look to my side
Let me hold you tight
Can you hold me tight too?
How's my body?
Is it soft?
Your body is very soft
Sweet has a very nice smell
How do I smell?
We both smell like each other
A sweet erotic aroma spreads around
Just take a deep breath in here
and your brain will feel dizzy from the sweet smell
and it'll want to do it ~ can't hold back from wanting to do it
Do you want me to touch your boobs?
But not yet
It wouldn't be comfortable to start touching all of a sudden
You have to start with a gentle hug and whispering in your ear
Or make you anxious
and your shame and desire will slowly overflow
Just being touched on the shoulder like that
and you get a giddy feeling, don't you?
And then slowly
putting my hands on your back from the top down...
and your legs will go limp
so that you don't fall down
If you hold your waist tightly
A paralyzing feeling of pleasure will crawl through your body
Hold me tighter
It's obviously just a hug
Why is my heart beating so fast?
Is this the first time you've felt like this?
That's a unique feeling for girls
Putting my leg between your legs
I rub my thigh against your inner thigh
what's wrong with you?
your legs are trembling
Are you comfortable?
Answer me!
It's comfortable, isn't it?
It's just being held gently that makes it comfortable
Look into my eyes
Let's kiss, shall we?
You can't stand up anymore?
Let's go to bed then
you sit here and lean on me
do you want me to hold you from behind and do it for you?
You want it to be like the cartoon you just did, right?
How would you like to be done?
Want to be whispered in your ear, right?
Clearly nothing has been done
Just whispering in your ear can make your body tremble
Do you want me to touch you?
Little Yao...
You're so h
phew~ (laughs)
You're making a really cute sound
How about over here?
Phew~
Are your ears comfortable?
Let me lick it for you
Then you can beg me with "please lick my ears"
I'm not going to do it for you
You want to get comfortable with your nipples today, right?
but do you want me to lick your ears too?
Then just this once
You've shown me a lot of you in heat
And your ears can do it for you too
if you rub your thumb near the palm of the hand you're holding
A numbing sensation will gradually overlap, right?
Did you get a shock?
If you use the palm of your hand, it'll look like this too
What would it look like if I touched your boobs with this technique?
What are you going to do?
maybe just touch the nipples and you'll come
So it's like wrapping two hands around the outside of the suit and uniform
and start fondling your breasts
Gentle downward pressure
or rub them like a gentle squeeze
the other side of the breast you try it yourself
Yeah, just try it like I did
although the thrill is weak
but it will give you that overall light feeling that your chest remembers
and you'll want more pleasure
phew~
You can't give too much stimulation all at once
Focusing on receiving the soft pleasure
A girl should build up the pleasure little by little and then reach the peak
you clench your legs together and try rubbing your inner thighs
That's great, twist your waist a little bit too
Take a deep breath like I did and try to exhale a sweet breath
Awesome, the expressions are so erotic it's getting cute
this hand that is touching you every time it rubs against your nipple
there's a slight rush of pleasure
What's wrong with you?
with a dumbfounded look on his face
Did it become slightly more comfortable?
And the ears are turning red
Are you shy?
I'm going to unbutton my suit
One by one, slowly
If you do it one by one you'll get your heart racing
than making you anxious like you just did
unbuttoning you like that would give you more of a weird feeling
Just make a girl anxious like you just did and the desire will get higher and higher
I'm going to take off your uniform
I'm going to touch you on top of your shirt like I just did
stroking it up and down
or shaking it like a circle
rubbing it gently
and the other side like I do
Try playing with it yourself
Gently press it up
or rub it gently
if the slightest touch of the tip causes the body to tremble slightly
Next, stroke the chest with the index finger like a line
How about that?
When you run your finger over the nipple you get an electric current of pleasure through your body
The fingers are stroking the nipples
Look~ Look~
You're getting even more comfortable than you were just now
already making h moaning sounds
Come on, try stroking it with your fingers like I did
Relax your body
slowly, as if letting yourself get anxious
feeling slightly less
Do you want me to touch you more? Do you want to be toyed with?
Want nipples rubbed? What the hell is that?
You remember what I just said, right?
you can't stroke in the spirit of your desire or go for pleasure
You have to focus your attention on receiving pleasure and being immersed in it
If you can keep this up you'll become more comfortable
At the end of the day
The orgasm-like pleasure will continue
Slowly release your moans of pleasure
Yes~ "Ah, ah, ah~"
How cute is it that you're feeling it?
Look, I'm making you anxious with my fingers
every time I touch my fingers to your nipples unintentionally
the sweet pleasure spreads throughout your body
Yui...
Nah, Yao-chan, answer me
It's more comfortable when you're called by your name and touched at the same time
Xiao Yao, Xiao Yao... so cute
Even my heart's beating faster when I see how shy you are
You can feel my heart beating from the back, right?
You have to be like me
And then let out more h's exhale