风花雪月汉化组译制，更多众筹作品与音声汉化相关加接待企鹅821731317或通知群773800845，转载请注明，谢谢配合
You have to take your shirt off now!
Don't you want to? Are you shy?
You're reacting like a girl, it's cute
You're starting to behave naturally like a girl
I'm going to unbutton your shirt one by one
And the body temperature is rising
You look really cute when you're holding back shyly
If you're shy, you'll get more comfortable
Become more shy, right?
Look, the buttons are all unbuttoned
You can see the lovely camisole now
It's time to take off the shirt
The camisole really suits you, it's so cute
The shoulders are slim and the skin is slim
It really looks like a girl
What's wrong with you?
Are you satisfied just by being touched on the shoulder?
Your skin is really sensitive
Run your fingers around your belly button
How about that?
Isn't it a little better to be stroked through your clothes than directly?
Because of the unique touch, it feels like it's going to get weird
What would it be like to touch your nipples through your vest?
Wanna try it? Do you want me to do that?
Then wrap my fingers around your back
What's wrong with you?
Did just the touch of my fingers on your back turn you on today?
And it makes an "ahhhhh" sound
It's sounding like a girl too
Yes, let me hear more of your lovely voice
unhook the bra and take off the straps too
Take off the bra with the camisole on
Huh?
Even through a snug fitting tank top
I can see that your nipples are slightly raised
It's just a little bit of touching and it's like this
Do you want me to touch you so much?
I'll rub it for you from above
How about that?
Isn't it nice to rub your palms against the top of your vest?
It's just a light rubbing
and it feels like it's going to get weird
Drawing circles with your palms
up and down .... Stroke it from side to side
You don't have to hold back the sound oh
Yes, make a sweet exhale
"Ah...ah...ah..."
as if she's pouting
To make a lovely, lustful exhalation
you palm yourself on the other side of your breast
Yeah, touch it like I did
It's even more comfortable than it was just being touched
You're gradually becoming able to make lovely noises
Let me hear more and more and more
want me to rub your nipples with my fingers?
then you take a spill, "Please rub your fingers against my nipples"
What's it going to be?
It's nice to rub it with your palm like this
That should do it for now, right?
If you can be cute and pampered
It's not like I can't do it for you
but until then it's all palms
You like to be made anxious like that right?
You're getting all misty and your expressions are getting very nasty
It's nice to be touched in such an anxious way, isn't it?
Every time I'm stroked, sweet pleasure comes through my nipples
Your nipples are getting hard and they look like they want me to touch them
I can't stop feeling good
Come on~ "Please rub your nipples more with your fingers".
Then I'm going to touch you
With the index fingers of my hands
rubbing around the nipple like a circle
Rubbing around...
My fingertips are getting closer to your nipples
Your heart is beating faster with anticipation
stroking your slightly puckered nipples with your fingertips
Rubbing ~
The sound you can't help but make ~
Rubbing...
Make more and more lovely noises
The pleasure will increase with the moans
because little Yao is a cute girl
Try "ahhhhhhhhhhhhh"
Next, stroke it lengthwise with your fingers
The nipples are getting hard from the pleasure
and then rubbing the nipple horizontally
playing with her like drawing circles
the slippery feel of the fitted vest is really comfortable
It's nice to be stimulated by a slight pleasure like this all the time, isn't it?
Let your body remember the pleasure of the nipples even more
Put your fingertips against your nipples like this
and then gently press and twist it as if pushing it
Is that comfortable?
come on ~ twist your thighs and rub your inner thighs
You can also wiggle your waist lasciviously
hardened nipples being played with by me
Wiggling and twisting...
twisting it like this
or rubbing it which is more comfortable?
The right nipple that's being twisted
or the left nipple being rubbed
then place your palm on the side of your breast that you feel comfortable with
Yeah, just put it on
and then gently place your palm on the nipple and start drawing circles
like a dragonfly gently turning
How about that?
It feels good to have your nipples gently stroked, doesn't it?
Your breath is getting more breathy
Your nipples are getting harder from the pleasure
you take your hand up a little and rub it gently again
and you'll get a soft pleasure
I'll do the other side of the chest for you too
You want to experience soft pleasure all the time like this, right?
Try to breathe deeply at times like this
Ha-ha-ha
Sweet breaths like this
That's fine, keep doing that
You're sounding more and more like a girl with your senses
Next, rub the area around the nipple in a circular motion with the finger of your middle finger
I'll do this side of the breast for you
You'll have to do the other side yourself
You have to tease slowly
Rub your fingers a little closer to your nipples
So let's try rubbing your nipples once
rubbing...
What about the sound of the h? It's okay.
Try making a sound every time you touch your nipple
Rub...
Try rubbing your nipples slowly up and down and side to side
Rub your fingertips gently as if you were making yourself anxious
You can do it!
The nipples that you touch and the nipples that I touch feel completely different, don't they?
It's nice to feel different pleasure on both sides at the same time, isn't it?
Make your voice a little bit more shrill, make a moan
That's awesome
It sounds exactly like a girl is panting
The brain gets weirder and weirder when you make a sensual sound
Come on ~ try panting louder
I'll pinch the nipple like this when you're not looking
What about the "no~" sound?
That's super cute!
I'll watch you next
Try playing with it yourself with your hands
Here you go, try it
left and right with different touches to the left and right
stroking the protruding nipples through the vest or rubbing them
or you can occasionally pinch it
How about that? Is it comfortable?
It's comfortable, isn't it?
You're getting to the point where you can feel it with your nipples
Are you happy? How's that?
You're really happy, aren't you?
You're masturbating right now, Yao-chan
Like a girl, masturbating
Yeah, nipple masturbation
Isn't it nice to masturbate with your nipples?
Just a gentle touch can become so comfortable
The pleasure can go on as long as you want
It's not like boy's masturbation where you just come and it's over
Once you remember the girl's pleasure, you can't go back to it
There's no stopping your fingertips
will keep playing with your nipples
Make more h noises, play with it
gentle as if to make you anxious
playing with your own fingers
How about that?
Are you starting to understand how to enjoy the pleasure of the nipple?
That's great.
So let's get even more comfortable