风花雪月汉化组译制，更多众筹作品与音声汉化相关加接待企鹅821731317或通知群773800845，转载请注明，谢谢配合
Next I will use my fingers to play directly with oh
You put your right hand in the sleeve of your vest
Where are your nipples?
The fingers that are searching for your nipples are slowly brushing your skin
It's exciting, isn't it?
Is it a little bit more up?
Or is it to the right?
or left?
Is it around here?
(laughs) Well...
Is this the areola here?
Is this the place?
Use your fingertips to put your nipples...
across ~ (laughs)
You shuddered a little bit
So let's do it again
Crossing...
I press my fingertips gently on your nipples
Your nipples are pressed flat
Really, you stopped playing with your own nipples
You have to play with it from the top of your vest like I did
Press it or flick it to make it more comfortable
Yeah, yeah, yeah... try that again
Next, play with it like you're twirling it with your fingertips
You can, just twirl it like this
You can pant in a more lustful voice
You can play with it differently with a different finger
It's going to feel different
Let's try it with the middle finger this time
It's like you're going to come just from being rubbed
But you can't think about orgasm
You have to concentrate on the pleasure
Isn't that great?
A girl can feel so much with just her nipples
Yao is a horny girl
Yeah, girls...
is a girl who likes it best when her nipples are played with h
puts her hands inside her vest
Try touching your nipples directly
Try turning it with your fingertips
Turn, turn...
I'll rub it from the top of the vest
twisting and rubbing on the other side
Which side do you think is more comfortable?
your own twisting nipples or the nipples that I'm rubbing against?
Which side is comfortable?
And you're such a greedy man?
Then let's continue on both sides
making noises as we rub our legs together
and then wiggling more
Let me see you more h
Let's try it with the other hand
your own hand rubbing against the top of the vest
I'll play with the other side directly
What's wrong with you?
You're drooling a little bit.
You've become a prisoner of nipple pleasure
I'll take your vest off and you put your hands in the air
Try lying on your back
Your nipples are getting red and raised
Do you want me to do more?
How about that? What's your response?
Well, I'll do what I just did
and play with both your nipples at the same time
Turning your nipples with my fingertips
or rubbing it like a circle
Yes, you can... panting in a lovely, crying voice
Your hardening nipples are being twisted and flicked by me
pampering me while enjoying the pleasure
Please I say "more, more"
Come on ~ tell me about it
If there's something you want me to do, you can tell me too
What would you like me to do?
Do you want me to press your nipples with my fingertips?
Just pander to me in a more lovely voice
What's wrong with you?
holding the vest off so tightly
Do you want me to play harder?
Then I'll wrap my vest around my fingers and play with the nipples
That's awesome
Do you feel like you're going to come before you even lick it?
Do you like being rubbed like that?
Or do you like the feel of a girl's underwear?
Does the smoothness of the touch make you want to go crazy
It's about to get weird already
It's like rubbing through the cloth like this that makes you want to stop
You look exactly like a girl
You've turned into a female in heat
pinch your nipple gently with your thumb and forefinger and twist it
How about that?
It can get so comfortable even without jerking off there
It's nice, isn't it?
The girl's pleasure will go on forever
You let out such a gasp
Are you completely turned into a girl already?
Maybe there's no going back
But you can't go back, right?
After all, it's so comfortable
Let's make more noise and revel in the pleasure
Different sounds depending on the technique
It'll be more comfortable
If you rub your palms together
Make a sweet sound of "Ah...ah...no~"
When it feels good to be rubbed
"Ah, ah, ahhhhh~" sound
You can do it!
Get more comfortable while looking into my eyes
If you rub your nipples gently with your fingertips
And you'll get a "huh? ～
A lovely, sensual sound of "Ah?
But my movements make more sounds together
Twist twist twist...
with more lustful, lovely sounds, get more sensual
You're getting very slutty
And as a bonus, I'll lick your ears
That was a very lewd sound
One more time
You're making sounds like a female in heat
It's already sounding like a girl
That's for sure
because your body is already feeling like a girl's body
You can, oh, turn your whole body and mind into a girl
Enjoy the pleasure, enjoy the orgasm
If you lick your ears like this
You'll want me to lick your nipples, right?
Imagine that
How comfortable would it be if the ears I was licking were nipples?
Let me fill in the other ear
In the meantime
play with your nipples a little harder
become more sensual with your nipples
Body trembling
and made an "ahhhhhhhhhhhhh" sound
Keep moaning~
It's just the two of us anyway, so we can make more noise!
Let me hear more of your lovely voice
You have a great voice
It could get more comfortable
Would it be weird to keep going like that?
It's okay even if it gets weird
I'm the one who wants you to be weird, that's why you're weird
Yao, look over here
Put your right index finger to me
That's a lovely finger
Let me lick it for you
Look at your own fingers
It's got a lot of my saliva on it
Put this finger of yours against your right nipple
Yes ~ put your saliva covered finger gently on top of your nipple
Turn it slowly as if you were drawing circles
It's slippery from saliva
It would feel very comfortable
It's like the nipples are melting with saliva
Sweet and deep pleasure coming through
To become more comfortable, try moving it yourself
Your left nipple is also being played with anxiously by me
How about that? Is your brain about to melt with pleasure?
Nah~ you hold out your left index finger
Next you suck and lick your own finger
Come on ~ try it
Be a little nastier
It's really h... it's sick...
and then licking my own fingers while doing so
as you imagine yourself now
while becoming more sensual
Try putting a well-salivated finger against your left nipple
just as you did with your right nipple
Try it quickly
Nah~ which side of the nipple do you feel more comfortable with?
The left side with your own saliva on it
or the right side with my saliva on it
Nah, which side is it?
Is either side comfortable?
Come and lick my finger
You can lick it with the tip of your tongue or you can suck on it
playing with your nipples with two fingers
and licking my fingers
Your panting is unstoppable
completely absorbed in the pleasure
Your saliva is delicious
the way you're panting as you play with your nipples
Exactly like a horny girl
It's really, really cute