风花雪月汉化组翻译制，更多众筹作品与音声汉化相关加接待企鹅821731317或通知群773800845，转载请注明，谢谢配合
Nah, look ahead
There's a big TV
Look, you're reflected on the TV
Did you know that there's a camera next to the TV?
You're being filmed right now
But I won't record it, don't worry
Look at the way you look in the picture now
A cute girl in a student uniform
making erotic noises as she plays with her nipples
enjoying the pleasure
That's what you look like now
You look like a girl who's masturbating, no matter how you look at it
Masturbating with her nipples while watching herself on TV
You have to do what I tell you to do
How about that?
Isn't it nice to masturbate while watching your own H?
Who is the girl with the h printed on the screen?
Yeah, you're Xiao Yao oh
You've turned into such a h girl
There's no way to turn back into a boy anymore
Rather, you don't want to go back either, do you?
Move your fingers in order to make yourself comfortable
Make more lustful noises
Wiggle your fingers and play with the nipples
Let me stick your saliva on it
Your nipples are sticky from the saliva
Rub it harder with your fingers
Let me lick your ear again
Watching your own h's reflected on the TV
Getting more sensual, panting, writhing ~
Nah~ you pinch your nipples hard and try it out
The intense pleasure runs through your brain
Is it going already?
Not yet oh
Relax your fingers a little bit if you're about to go
Rub your finger gently against it
And if that's not enough
just squeeze it with your fingers or scrape it with your fingertips
You can also press it in
like this to overlap the pleasure
And you can have an orgasm with your nipples
Like a little bit of overlapping pleasure
Play with your nipples while you're aware of that
Yes, you can, your voice is getting even more h-erotic than it was just now
and even shaking your waist involuntarily
rubbing her legs
It looks like a girl who is masturbating with her nipples anyhow
like a girl, let out more panting