风花雪月汉化组翻译制，更多众筹作品与音声汉化相关加接待企鹅821731317或通知群773800845，转载请注明，谢谢配合
Nah, what do you want me to do next?
What do you want me to do next?
Do you want me to lick your nipples?
I've been playing with it since just now and I can't stand it anymore
You pouted and said "Please lick my nipples"
Make it cuter!
And again, say, "Please lick my nipples."
What to do?
I'll only lick it if you make it stand up a little bit more
Nah, can you make it a little more erect?
What's your answer to that?
Well, I'll play with your left nipple
and then you go on and play with the right one
To become more comfortable, play with it
Your own fingers and my fingers
Which side is more comfortable?
Do you like mine better?
But your own playful nipples have gotten bigger
Do you really like my fingers better?
You want me to make you more comfortable, right?
You try the way you want me to touch you with your own fingers
Ugh~~ you like being done that way
I'll do it like you do
My nipples have gotten a little bit bigger
You can use more of the touch that you want me to use
You want me to lick you, don't you?
Then you'd have to make your nipples bigger
Nah, try looking me in the eye while you're pouting
Repeat "please lick my nipples"
Got it?
Then I'll dab a little bit of saliva for you before I lick
When you move your finger, it makes a watery sound from the saliva
Are you about to come?
You can't come before you've licked
If you want to be licked, you have to keep repeating the pussy
Your nipples are getting very erect
So, I'm almost ready to lick them for you
You have to watch me lick it
My mouth is getting closer to your nipples
The tip of my tongue is about to touch your nipple when it stops
You beg me one last time
and say "please lick my nipples"
I'll lick you good
You hold on to the sheets tightly
Is it that comfortable?
Anyway, there's no one else, so you can make more noise
I'll lick the other nipple for you too
One side being licked, the other side being played with and squeezed lightly
It's about to get weird
Could be, it's getting even weirder
twisting and turning the nipple with the tip of your tongue
Your nipples look delicious, let me suck on them
Your nipples are delicious~
Try to moan with the sound of my sucking
Your sensitivity will increase!
Your panting has gotten weird
Does it feel good to be licked and fondled like this?
It's so comfortable when your body is writhing~
Does it feel like you're going to come? Is that what it's like?
You sound like you're about to come
Look, it's going, it's coming~
But, no orgasms yet
How can I make you come so easily?
I'd have to make you feel so comfortable that you'd become weirdly pleasurable first
Do you want to get weird?
You want to be weird, right?
I just need to lick your nipples again
and you'll feel the same orgasmic pleasure that you just felt
The pleasure will last forever
How about that? Is it comfortable? Is it about to get weird?
What does it look like if you bite the nipple lightly?
make this sound like a cry
so comfortable that it's about to get weird, right?
I'll bite it again
Make more and more slutty noises
What will you become if this intense pleasure keeps going on?
Are you scared?
Scared but want me to do more, right?
Squeeze your right nipple firmly with your thumb and forefinger
pinch ~
your body jerked a little bit
How about the left nipple?
Pinch it ~
which side of the nipple is more comfortable?
Pinch it
so good, so good
and when you squeeze it, you're panting loudly
really
I won't stop until you answer
pinch...
Is that the right side?
pinch the...
or does it say left?
pinch
if both sides are pinched at the same time
what would it look like?
Are you scared?
Does it feel like something's about to pop out?
But you don't want me to stop either, do you?
What do you do when you want me to do more?
Yes~ you have to pamper me
while looking at me and saying "please squeeze my nipples harder"
That's a good boy.
So
I'm going on~ oh
Squeeze -~
That's awesome
while stiffening up and making so much noise
Did you go a little bit?
Is it a white head?
Look between your legs
If it were normal, you'd probably just shoot white fluid and be done with it
but not today
Did you experience a non-ejaculatory orgasm? (female orgasm)
Yeah, that's a girl orgasm
And you know what?
That's what a girl's orgasm feels like
The inside of your head and your body starts to twitch
The head is turning white, right?
It's your first female orgasm
Female orgasms can last many times
The more times you go, the more pleasure you get
just rubbing the nipple gently with your palm again like this
and you'll feel a very strong pleasure, right?
It makes such a lovely sound
when pinched and then gently rubbed
It's going to be nice, isn't it?
Rubbing...
Try to use sweet sounds like "Ahh~! Ahhhh!" in a sweet sounding pant
rubbing...
You're already so wet you can see it through your underwear
Look at that, so much prostate fluid
No
because you're a girl so it's love fluid
Look at your love juices on my fingers
It's already flowing out so much
What a slut~
You lick up the love juices on my fingers
I won't help you continue if you don't lick it
Lick it... lick it...
What a straightforward boy
Is your own love juice good?
It turned out to be very tasty
I rub my love juice covered fingers on your nipples
and then turn it again
Your nipples are even more perky than they were just now
Your nipples have gotten so big that you can hold them with two fingers
It's really like a girl's nipple
hold your nipple with your index and middle finger and twist it
Is that comfortable?
So it's very comfortable
And your voice is becoming more and more h, and it's becoming more and more strange
Twisting and twisting
Wiggle wiggle wiggle ~...
The love juices are dripping onto the bed
More can come out
Hold your right nipple with your own fingers and try it like I did
How about that? It's great, isn't it?
Is there no stopping the pleasure?
It feels like it could go on forever
That's the pleasure of a girl's nipple
wrapped in soft pleasure
Very deep, deep, deep pleasure
Do you want to go? You'd love to go, wouldn't you?
But you can't focus on the orgasm
Focus on the pleasure that you're feeling right now
It's nice to have your nipples played with
Focusing on your nipples being played with by saliva and love juice covered fingers
I'll keep licking them for you, get more into the pleasure
while matching my tongue
while making sweet "ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh" sounds
Focus on the sound of being licked
Make more panting sounds
of being licked slowly
Make "ahh... ahh... ahh..." noises
When being licked intensely and quickly
Make intense moans of "ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh"
You can, oh, focus more on the pleasure
When you're being sucked strongly
You have to make a loud "ahhhhhhhhhhhhh" sound
You're so cute, you look so comfortable
More lewd panting and crying
Licking her tongue over the nipple caught in her fingers
Does it feel like it's going to twitch again?
Make more noise with the sound of being licked and the pleasure
You see, it's almost time to go for another female orgasm, yo?
What will it look like if you have an orgasm?
Put your fingers against your nipples
rubbing it or twisting it
or pinching and pulling it
Try playing with it in any way you like
Make even more lustful noises
Something's coming that you can't even contain yourself
It's gonna be oh, it's gonna be
What about the orgasm that's going to come
making an "ahhhhhhhhh" sound
It's not working, it's not working, it's not working...
can get weird oh
Got it?
while trembling at the waist and writhing
already at the limit, can't hold it back
there's no need to hold back
Just give yourself up to the pleasure
Look, it's coming, it's coming
It's already starting to tremble
It's going, it's going
Going to climax, going to go go go go...
Going for it --- ~
Your body pops up and starts to twitch
And the sound of the orgasm doesn't stop
just getting licked on the nipples after the orgasm
and it's like another orgasm is about to happen
your underwear is getting wet
How about a girl's orgasm?
It's awesome isn't it?
You can still go on
look~ it feels like it's going to get weird being licked on the head again
You don't have to be aware of the orgasm thing
Just give your body over to the pleasure and just sink into it and let out a gasp
Just pant in time with my movements
Your body is trembling violently again
You don't need to focus on it your body is already trembling involuntarily
unconsciously having a female orgasm
Did you orgasm again?
You can't stop it anymore, continuous female orgasm
and you play with your nipples in response to your desire
you don't have to hold back because you can come a million times
I'll play with your nipples with my fingers while I lick your ears
Take in the pleasure and let your mind go blank
If you're about to go you're going to pant lustfully
Something's coming
Your body starts to tremble
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming~
It's awesome, I can't stop panting
The love juices won't stop either
The bed is already getting wet
Have you caught the knack of the female orgasm?
You should be able to orgasm even without my command, right?
I'll be playing with your nipples
You just do what you want
countless and countless orgasms
Your nipples are so sweet and delicious
rubbing it like this, making it engorge and turn red
It looks like it wants someone to play with it even harder
The room echoes with your panting
Did you come again?
It's trembling
become more lustful, more sensual