风花雪月汉化组译制，更多众筹作品与音声汉化相关加接待企鹅821731317或通知群773800845，转载请注明，谢谢配合
obviously a girl but like a boy here
What is this?
Is it a meat stick?
You're a girl
How can you have something like that?
It's your honey pea (clitoris)
Yes, the honey pea
That's what's on the inside of your labia
for you to focus on it
Here's your honey pea
Put your hand on it
If you rub it like a nipple
What would it look like?
even though I said no playing with the meat stick today
but if it's a honeydew
can be special for you to play with
You imagine a girl being comfortable playing with her honey pea
Xiao Yao
Do you want me to help you?
What's your answer?
Then I will help you well
I'm rubbing your pea from the top of your panties
I'm trembling at the slightest touch
I'll rub it up and down
I'll rub my nipples up and down with my fingers as well
It's nice to have your nipples and beans played with at the same time, isn't it?
Being played with horizontally
You try doing that to your nipples too
The love juices are leaking out, the panties are getting wet
If you press your finger against your pea
and it makes a plopping sound of water
The love juices flow more and more in pleasure
As soon as more love juices flow out, you'll get more comfortable
Ouch, your body is spasming
Is that another orgasm?
How many times has this happened?
You've had more orgasms than you can count
There's no way to go back to being a boy
But you didn't intend to go back in the first place, did you?
because you could be so cute and comfortable
But the fingers playing with their nipples won't stop
Panting unstoppable as I play with my honey pea
because there's no point in going back
both physically and mentally into a girl
And that would make it... more comfortable.
By the way, I've got a great thing to try.
This, do you know what it is?
A bra?
It does, it looks very similar on the outside
It's made of silicone
The part that's pressed against the nipple...
It rotates like this.
Isn't that great?
A tongue-like part in the centre of the rotation
How does this work, right?
You should know
put this on and if you flip the switch
and it will rotate and stimulate the nipples
So the nipples will be licked while it's rotating
Nah, do you want to put this on?
Wouldn't you love to try it?
So in order to be able to spin more easily
put a drop of lubricant on your nipples
Then I'm going to put it on your boobs, yo
because it's silicone to fit on your boobs
Don't worry about it falling off
How does it fit?
It's lightweight, so it doesn't feel out of place, right?
Let's turn the switch on and try it
How about that?
Isn't it more comfortable than you thought it would be?
It's like being licked by a real person
You see, how about that? How's that?
Is it nice to have both nipples licked at the same time?
It looks very comfortable
Do you like it?
There's a lot of patterns in the licking method, it's going to get more comfortable
again it makes a very h sound
I'm just watching from the sidelines
It's like it's being licked gently, it's very comfortable, isn't it?
That's fine.
It's okay.
Make a sound with its movements
Don't hold back if you want to come
Your body is starting to tremble
Did you come a little bit?
You try spreading your legs a little bit
I've tied your ankles to the foot of the bed with rope
Really~ Don't run away!
I won't hurt you
How about that?
Isn't it nice to be tied up so tight you can't move?
If the freedom of the body is taken away
the body becomes more sensitive
Try holding out your right hand
Tie your wrist up and tie it to the bed
What's wrong with you? Are you excited from being tied up?
Do you like being tied up?
because you sounded even weirder than you did just now
I can tell
Let's use the blindfold next
How about that?
It gets more exciting when you're deprived of your vision
In this situation
just whispering in your ear makes you tremble
because you don't know what's going to be done
Heartbeat racing with anticipation
It's going to get even weirder if you keep licking your ears
Even if you're about to come the toy won't stop
if both nipples are being licked and fondled at the same time
Are you having an orgasm?
You can have countless ejaculation-free orgasms
You put your left hand out
Do you want to be tied?
but this side won't be tied
You put your ring finger out
and you put your ring finger on your honey pea
You match the frequency of the toy
try playing with your ring finger on your honey pea
Move it gently in small movements and play with it as if you were rotating it
great oh your voice is very h
because the ring finger doesn't usually get used much
It's like a sense of being played with by someone else, right?
It's like a girl playing gently with your honeydew, isn't it?
already not working again?
It won't stop until I'm satisfied
Let me see more of your slutty self
To become even more promiscuous
or this state will go on forever
Are you going to come again?
You can, you're going to get even hornier
and then turn others on with your h-ness
Is that okay?
It's not enough to feel like that
Keep exposing your feminine instincts
Show your nasty ways
with the action of the toy
And your fingers get more and more intense
Your fingers are covered in love juices as you play with the honey pea
You have to lick all the love juice off your finger
Your tongue is so h, lick it more
Keep stimulating your nectar with your fingers
It's gonna get weird if you keep going like this?
So it's not working?
No, I just want to see you get weird
I'll always be watching you
So be weird
As soon as I'm satisfied, I'll stop the toy for you
And I'll untie the rope for you
And then, I'll make you more comfortable
Just imagine
being tied up and blindfolded and having your nipples sucked by a toy
and then playing with her own honeydew
Lascivious panting girl
This is you
I'll tie your left hand too
and put the jigger against your honey pea
Struggle more, let out more gasps
You're really responding to it
Do you like being done that?
To keep it from falling off
I used my underwear to hold the jumper in place
all tied up and then played with nipples and honeydew by the toy
It's like being ganged up on for a prank
You imagine yourself being bullied by several girls at the same time
Do you like the right nipple?
Or how about the left ear?
Or is it more comfortable in the right ear?
It's definitely the left nipple, isn't it?
Your honeydew is standing up like that
The toy plays with your nipples nonchalantly
It's like you're going to come with just a little bit of stimulation
I can't stop~ I can't stop the continuous orgasm~
But I can't get enough of that alone!
Struggling and panting, frantic and crying
Has it gotten weird?
I won't stop until you're weird
I'll take the blindfold off for you
because of the pleasure you're turning into an aheyan, it's really erotic
it gets weirder, weirder right
Is it going to be no good already? Is it going to go?
Is it going to come?
Here we go again, right?
It feels like it's going to go ~ it's going to go ~
It's already going to be no good
There's no way to hold back anymore
It's going, it's going oh
Going for it, going for the female orgasm
Going, going, going...!
It's crying out in comfort
I'm having a great orgasm
I'll untie you and take the toy away
the nipples are getting so red and erect
They're turning into girls' nipples
How about that? Is it comfortable?
It's really nice