风花雪月汉化组译制，更多众筹作品与音声汉化相关加接待企鹅821731317或通知群773800845，转载请注明，谢谢配合
Although it's almost time to end
Do you want to do more?
It'll get weirder if you keep doing it?
But actually you'd like me to
do one more, right?
If you promise me...
to be my pet
and I can do more for you
Do you want to be my female pet?
What are you going to do?
Yes ~ become my female pet and then let me do whatever I want
The rest is entirely my private time
so there's no cost of extension
but if you don't want to be my pet
I won't continue to do it for you
You've completely remembered the pleasure of the female
There must be a lot of things you want me to do for you, right?
wanting me to do it for you, are you?
You want to be weird because I do what I want?
Nah, want to try to be my female pet?
In that case, you'll have to say it
"Please let me be your magnetic pet"
One more time
And one more "please" at the end
Yes, you'll be my female pet next
Become more comfortable with me
Let's get even more comfortable with this next, shall we?
I'm going to put lubricant all over you
You look so erotic with all that lube
playing with your nipples with a lubricated finger
How about that?
Doesn't it feel a little different than it did just now?
It makes a watery sound when you play with it
It feels like it's going to get weird when it makes a sound
Try making a pant that's close to a cry
Didn't you turn into my female pet?
If you don't pant more I'm going to stop
pinch your nipples with your index and ring fingers
That looks comfortable~
Listen listen listen listen~
Every time you squeeze it, it makes a gurgling sound of water
What's wrong with you? Did you come again?
You're becoming orgasmic with just that little bit of stimulation
You can keep coming with your nipples
As soon as you pinch your nipples you'll have an orgasm, right?
It's like when you pinch your nipples you have a continuous orgasm
How about twisting your nipples while being pinched in this state?
It makes a very strange sound
How about that? How's that? Do you like having your nipples pinched?
If you suck on your nipples in this state
What would become of you?
It's going on oh
the body jerks into this
you'll keep coming for as long as I'm sucking on it
You'll feel better if you make a sound when you come
It's okay to say, "Ahhhh, I'm going to come!"
Make a moan of pleasure
Let's show more aheyan moans~
There's no way to stop the orgasm
Play with your nipples with your own hands and have a continuous orgasm
Get more sensual
Come on! Go for it!
Have a continuous orgasm!
You're my ejaculation-free orgasm pet, right?
Come on, answer me
What are you to me?
you're my female ejaculation-free orgasm pet
I'll make you more
so keep saying "I'm your non-ejaculatory pet"
Let me lick your other nipple
Playing with your own honeydew
there's no stopping the orgasm, there's no stopping the panting
I told you that it becomes more comfortable to make a sound when you come
But there's another way to make it more comfortable
That's .... Hold back the sound!
No matter how comfortable it is, you have to hold back the moans
And hold back your voice when you come
Even though you can't help but make a sound when your nipples are being played with
but you have to hold back
No, your voice is leaking out a little bit
Even if it's comfortable, you have to hold back your voice
Your gesture of holding back and struggling
Let me continue to admire
The look on your face as you endure and come
So erotic that you can't stop
Your voice is coming out again
I'll stop if you don't hold back
There's nothing I can do about you
I'm going to take your panties off and lift your waist up a little bit
because the love juices are getting wet
Look at that, it's slutty, isn't it?
You panties, take it in your mouth!
No saying no, take it in your mouth!
You've got your nectar so big and dripping with such love juices
You're really a pervert then
I'll lick your ears
you're playing with your nipples and honeydew at the same time yourself
by me licking my ear while pulling hard on my own nipples
Trying to make a sound but can't
If I don't make a sound, the pleasure will just keep building up
It's bad, isn't it?
If you don't make a sound all the time you feel like you're going to go crazy
Your body trembles and
as if you're about to spring up
The sounds that you've been holding back so far seem to be about to be released
Whenever I suck on your nipples
you have to squeeze the other nipple hard with your fingers
Got it?
Going for it ~ it feels like it's going for it's going for it...
It's not working anymore, going going going going...
no matter how comfortable the orgasm is you must hold back the sound
going going going going going...~
Go on, go on! ...! No ejaculation orgasm it!
oops oops
you're having an orgasm
you came because you were so comfortable and you even had an orgasm
I took my panties off
Both of you ~ get more comfortable with me
put lubricant on my breasts and hold each other tightly
Let's get the two nipples overlapping
Your body is very soft and comfortable to hold
Come and hold me a little tighter~
Can you feel the nipples and nipples touching each other?
just by moving slowly the two nipples will rub against each other
It's very comfortable, isn't it?
And it makes my nipples feel good too
That's great!
And rub it a little bit more
You can stop holding back your voice and just let it out
Make more lustful noises in my ears
I'll hold you tightly and rub you up and down
You can keep on coming and crying out
And make more and more raunchy noises in my ears
Put your nectar against my crotch
It's like a nipple
Let's rub our honeydew together
the two pressed tightly together between their strands
and there's a pleasure that grows
moving slowly like nipples .... Letting them rub against each other
moving while making the lubricant make a watery sound
the honey beans rubbing against each other
That's great~
More~ Let me feel it too
move your body a little bit more, move your waist a little bit
It's like putting your love juices on my body
while clinging together and moaning~
while making more lustful watery noises~
The pleasure of the two gradually melting and becoming one
with the sound of my feeling
And you cry out for pleasure
Can your pleasure continue to rise?
Because you're a slutty girl
And it's going to get even more sensual, right?
with both nipples...
About to come? Can't hold back anymore?
Already?
Feeling like it's going to get weird?
It can be oh, get weird
Let's get even weirder
I feel like I'm going too
Yoru, I'll make you come
so you have to make me come too
Nah~ make me come~
And more, and more...
More panting
Let me see your dirty face
Pleasure building up all over
It's almost overflowing
I can't stop panting and spitting and sweating and loving...~
Your body can't quite take it
It's at its limit, isn't it?
You have to release all the pleasure that has accumulated in your body at once
Got it?
I'm on the verge of orgasm, and there's no stopping the flow of love juices
There's no stopping the panting
And so the crying goes on and on
the two nipples, the pleasure fused together
Be one with me, my voice is your voice
Just hearing the panting that echoes in my head makes me feel like I'm going to go
You have to release all your love juices when you come
Spit it all out
I'm going, I feel like I'm going...~
nipples rubbing against
I'm going to get weird from the pleasure of my nipples...~
All because the nipple pleasure is reaching its limit ~
It's going, it's going, it's going...!
Going together, going together...!
Ko Yao, Ko Yao!
Going to go going to go going to go, going to go--!
Ko Yao ~ Ko Yao ~ are you okay?
It's okay to hold me like this
Do you get comfortable with nipples?
How's the pleasure for girls?
You're really super cute when you're slutty
It's very erotic
It's totally girly
Nah~ do you want to stay a girl like that?
Or do you want to be a boy again?
What about wanting to stay a girl
What about the girlfriend thing and all that doesn't matter anymore?
because you can get so cute and comfortable too
After all, you're my female pet
Do you want to know more about girly pleasure now?
today you've remembered the pleasure of nipples
next time it'll be that hole's turn...
I'll teach you well
Or should I start now?