风花雪月汉化组译制，更多众筹作品与音声汉化相关加接待企鹅821731317或通知群773800845，转载请注明，谢谢配合
After all, there's not much energy left today, it doesn't look good
Next time you do it
I'll spoil you even more
Right, let's keep it girly and go home today
Specially, I'll give you that uniform
It's okay
After all, you're not thinking of going back to being a boy, are you?
So, you can stay a girl for the rest of your life
Yao-jao, turn this way
Can you make a promise with me that you'll come back next time?
Then I'll give you a reward
Then one last reward for you
This one ~ the camera by the TV
Even though I said I didn't record it but I did
from the time you entered the room and then all the way through
I'm sorry~ I'm sorry~
You don't have to worry
I'm not going to sell these videos or upload them to video sites
Pull the SD card out
Well, this is a gift for you
It's got a lot of your h expressions and gestures on it
Until we meet again
I'd love it if you could watch this video and get even more h
It's nice to masturbate while watching your h self
So let's use this to get comfortable before we meet again
So, let's go back together
It's been a really good day