I'm going to be your
exclusive pet from today
First year cheerleader
Rei Kuroimi
Although I think you know
me from the same class too
but why would you choose
me, who is not popular?
Aren't there lots of other cute
girls in the cheerleading section?
or do you think people like me
don't put up much of a fight
so that you can order me
around as you please?
No. It's okay, right?
Because that's the rule of
the cheerleading section
And I'm just going to do it
You know that too, don't you?
Our school cheerleading
section's service sex system
The first one is the
girls cheerleaders
have to go and be the exclusive pet
of the male students near game day
giving him sexual support
Secondly, it is to satisfy the
male student who is the subject
to motivate him daily with oral
sex, handjobs, intercourse, etc.
Third become a female cheerleader
who specializes in pets
cannot disobey the male
student who is their owner
which means that
you are my master
I am your exclusive pet
Before the game is over
Whatever you order me
to do, I must obey
Does that sound like a joke?
If I had known about this system
of service from the beginning
I wouldn't have joined the cheerleading
section even if I had died...
Ah, you said you didn't know...?
Are you pretending
to be confused?
So, is it okay to do nothing?
I've got a pretty good
looking face, don't I?
No need to play dumb I know the
rumors from the boys, right?
wanting to do horny things with Rei
Kuroimi and messing up her poker face
and then you get really mad at
the boys for making wisecracks
and acted out in class... [03:00.53] [03:00.53]
[03:00.54] I know all about that too, right?
Although I didn't ask you to do
this, I don't have to thank you...
And then what? Do you want to do it?
Or not?
Please don't worry, since I'm
in the cheerleading section
I don't have the right
to choose not to do it
Assuming that you really don't know
anything about it given the miraculous odds
even if it's just to get me to
support you before the game
that's none of my business
What's wrong?
Undressing is just a necessary step in the service
of the cheerleading section, you don't have to care
See, how about that? This is the
kind of nasty bikini you like...
This mini bikini that's
not even close to nude...
Did you underestimate the intelligence
network of the cheerleading section?
On the day you chose me
We even found out your favorite
side dish for masturbation, right?
Well, then, if you'll
excuse me, master...
What's wrong with you?
I'm just kneeling to you
It's like a ritual of swearing
allegiance to your master
It's just a classmate in a dirty
bikini in an after-school classroom
just kneeling down to you
Master, let me kneel and
pledge my allegiance to you
From this day forward, first year
cheerleader Rei Kuroimi is your sex pet
In accordance with the service system, for one
week prior to the start of the competition
I will obey your
orders absolutely
Please take care of yourself
Then allow me to offer my master the
kiss of the oath of absolute loyalty
So, are you excited?
Got myself turned on by having a girl
in my class wear such a kinky outfit
What an incorrigible pervert
Master, anything that your
rod can imagine is erotic
can be done with my
body, Rei Kuroimi?
So, for the next week
Please be gentle with me and take
good care of me, okay? Master...