And a hard day of practice
Did you notice that you were
being watched all the time?
The sight of the other
students is not good, is it?
Because it's common knowledge that
I'm going to be owned by you.
that I'm going to have sex with that
poker-faced, sweatshirt-wearing girl
You're very excited about having me
all to yourself, aren't you, master?
Pervert...
Come, please sit over there
This is the sex support room under
the name of the cheerleading section
Well, it's like a single
room in a couple's hotel
What's wrong with it?
Ah, that too
You like the nasty
bikini best, don't you?
You see? How about that?
The girl who was just
wearing a tracksuit
actually wore such an erotic
swimming costume underneath
Perverted owners get a kick
out of that, don't they?
It stinks...it smells like sweat
You can't even take a shower when you're
actually going to have sex with a woman?
You're not a monkey. I wish you'd
take care of your hygiene.
No, it would be rude to
say that to a monkey
You already have a
hard-on, don't you?
Is that right? After all, you have a woman
in front of you who can do whatever you want
in a sexy swimming costume
No matter how many arrogant
and capricious things I say
I will become a woman who will obey
you as soon as my master commands
Do you want to do it with me?
First experience...
Eh, you're asking me
if I want to do it?
Well, that's certainly...
Not even if I die, master?
I can't even imagine giving my
virginity to a pervert like my master
But master, if you have
ordered it, I cannot disobey
What are you hesitating about?
Well, order me to do it
If I don't satisfy you, I'm going
to get yelled at by my counselor
Suddenly you're kissing me
If you want to do it, then say
it honestly from the start
And then what?
And ask me what I'm
going to do...
Is it really okay to do nothing?
Is that alone enough? Kissing...
Come on...
That was quite an awkward kiss
Are you satisfied?
So...
I'm going to start by using my
hand on my master's rod, huh?
Jerking off...
Does it feel good?
Because the first month of cheerleading,
they made me practice all the time
like this, jerking off
and jerking off...
A way to stimulate a boy's
weaknesses one way or another...
Jerking off, jerking
off, jerking off...
It's twitching
Do you like the feeling of being held by
my finger ring around the coronary sulcus?
Rubbing and rubbing the
coronal sulcus like this...
Scratching gently
with your nails...
and sometimes adjusting the pace...
[07:52.27] Rubbing and rubbing and rubbing...
rubbing and rubbing with
the palm of my hand...
jerking my hand around while
squeezing my balls too...
rubbing and rubbing,
squeezing and squeezing...
Is it going to get weird being rubbed
on both sides at the same time?
Do you like all of this?
Although I was going to completely bully
you once I found my master's weakness
to make you cry out
from the pleasure
But if you're weak
all over, it's easy
The front end is getting
sticky from the patience juice
It stinks...
Master, does the smell of my
patience juice excite you?
A sticky rod made of
prostate fluid...
Do you think if you don't cum you'll
be able to keep doing this to me?
And you've been doing
it since a while ago
and you've been peeking at
my boobs since a while ago?
Pervert...
I've said it a few times,
but I'm a cheerleader
As long as the owner
is close to game day
you can cum all you want on me
and rub my tits all you want
Come on, you can rub
my boobs, right?
Come on, please. You're welcome.
No, it won't hurt
But I feel sick, master
Breathing heavily, rubbing
with great hunger...
do you want to rub my
breasts that badly?
If you like my boobs that much
Then I'll give you a titty with
Rei Kuroimi's 91cm G-cup breasts
The rod is reacting
You want to use those tits
to get your own eugenia
want to thrust hard into
my cleavage and deform it
while shrugging my hips and doing
uncharacteristic pistoning
while letting me
do your titties?
Did the tits of your silent and
aloof classmate turn you on?
How does it feel to have
your rod between my breasts?
Master's rod is very hot
It's about to burn my boobs
Now put my saliva on the rod...
This is Rei Kuroimi's
special saliva lube
It's sticky and nasty, isn't it?
So please allow Rei Kuroimi
to have breast sex
to serve her master's rod
to the best of her ability
It tastes so heavy...
The rod comes up near my face
Even with ordinary breathing, I
could smell it coming this way
What about it, master?
Did you feel your rod
with the boobies?
That's an
uncharacteristic moan...
no matter how comfortable
my titties are
and no matter how much
you want to let it out
Please don't make that
girly sound, okay?
My saliva mixed with my
master's patience juice
It's sticky and disgusting...
Well, how long are you
going to let me do this?
Can you cum faster?
If I keep this up, senpai's fishy
meat smell is going to be on my boobs
Come on, come on out!
There's nothing I
can do about you
because if you keep doing this, it doesn't
seem to be enough to make you cum
so please let me suck your tits
I'm going to enjoy
my master's rod
Clearly still just
licking the glans
and already there's
such a strong reaction
all the way to the
back of the throat...
taking the arrogant woman's
titty hole aeroplane cup
Does it feel comfortable
to violate like a toy?
It's like using a girl's
mouth as a pussy for sex...
It's so bad...
No one likes the owner except the
cheerleader's sex pets, right?
What a pervert...
What's wrong?
I didn't say I didn't
like it either
Come on, you can invade the depths
of my arrogant throat all you want
What an intense piston thrust...
It's so bad...
Are you going to cum?
It's okay...
Please impregnate the depths of my
arrogant throat with my master's cum...
Master's cum pours into
my mouth full of...
I fired up...
Master's cum is
sticking to his throat
That's disgusting...
Are you happy to make me drink
something so disgusting?
That's really bad, master
there's still a bit
left in the urethra
I'll squeeze it all out
for you with my hands
Jerk off...
like you oh master...
Those words just
now were all lies
I love you
Even though I can't be honest
and say a lot of bad things
but I actually like you the most
Master, please forgive
your arrogant sexual pet
I love you the most master!
How can this be serious, dummy~
Come on, let's get the
rest of the cum out!
Jerk off, jerk off, jerk off...
swoosh swoosh swoosh ~
my hands are sticky
from my master's cum
It's so hot...
The taste... it's awful...
How about that, master?
Was my handjob and titty
blowjob comfortable?
So, that's the end
of the service
Can you put your trousers
on and get out of here now?
I still have to clean up a room that
someone has recklessly left full of semen
Okay, so I'll see you tomorrow