Hard day for you too, master
What's wrong?
Ah, you're being in the
club room in a nasty bikini
waiting for you, right?
Don't worry, the cheerleading
section is allowed by the school
Which means that
me and the master
are allowed to do anything
in this club room
And then, at the end of the
club, the sweat-soaked master
want to do something with
me in a nasty bikini?
Huh?
No, I didn't even think about the
harmless-looking virgin host
would actually make an order for
me to lick his hindquarters
for a female student to
lick her own rear end
You're a hopeless
pervert, master
Well, as a sex pet, I can't
disobey my master's orders either
So, please take your hot,
wet, unbathed bottom
and come to my face
Master's hindquarters
come to me...
sweat and the smell of the
hindquarters mixed together
There's a dizzyingly
androgynous scent...
So, I'm here to clean up
my master's posterior
How does it feel to be licked and
serviced by your beloved pussy?
It smells bad but
it tastes good too
No, I don't hate that, do I?
Not only the outside but also the
inside of the hindquarters...
Yes, I'll lick all over
After all, I'm now a butt
wash for my master's rear end
You don't have to worry about it, it's one of
the requirements of the cheerleading section
I can also be the master's
potty if I'm ordered to do so
I can drink your pee
if you tell me to
and I'll do what
you tell me to do
The rod is hard and erect again
Are you excited imagining
treating me like a pisser?
That's disgusting...
I can't help you, I'll just lick my rear
end and jerk my rod at the same time
Master's pussy is so
wet with my saliva
I'll help you lick your
rear end deeper too
And of course, I'll jerk
my rod at the same time
The taste of the hindquarters is
getting stronger and stronger
is seriously trying to seduce the female and is
determined to make the other guy just smell his rear end
male scent that makes her pussy
wet and her womb tingle...
Master how does it feel to have your rear
end licked by a nasty girl cheerleader?
Don't retract your waist
That's an order from the master
Let me be your butt wash...
The perverted rod that gets turned on by
licking the hindquarters also wants...
jerking off and jerking off...
Master's balls too...
this side's balls too...
Does it feel good to
have your balls licked?
That's gross...
Right, squeeze,
squeeze, squeeze...
It feels good to be
squeezed by my hand too
I'll give you a massage
so you can cum more
Squeeze and squeeze
and squeeze...
The hindquarters are quivering
and it looks so lonely
if you squeeze your balls and
lick your pussy at the same time
the balls will clench up
It's very comfortable no matter
where you're being stimulated
What a pervert...
that no ordinary man could
ever get his girlfriend to do
rubbing her balls like
this and jerking her rod
plus licking your rear end.
[12:59.48] It's the best, isn't it?
Are you about to cum?
Your humiliating girl-like moans are getting
louder and louder, aren't they? [13:29.38] Master?
Gotta hand it to a master
who's so unlikeable...
You see, this...
It's the underwear
I just took off
Do I usually wear such
erotic underwear, you ask?
The sense of immorality in the
midst of a boring school life...
although I'm only wearing this erotic thong
with very little fabric to turn you on
but maybe I'm just as
perverted as my master
take this hot wet panty
I just took off...
as a muzzle for the master?
Perfect for a pervy owner
Please be wrapped in my
feminine scent and suffocate
Well, I'm now going to be lovely for
the master who has become lovely
back to doing rear end
licking and hand jobs
The hindquarters are
completely relaxed too
Master...
You can't get enough of that hindquarters licking
and handjob while you're choking, can you?
Come on, please
take a deep breath
Enjoy my feminine panties
You're about to cum, aren't you?
is panty choking Play's rear end
licking hand job that comfortable?
this is so not nice...please
just cum like that
jerking off...
Come on, please let all of
your master's cum into my hand
so much cum again...
Wow, my hands are getting sticky...
[18:21.38] That sucks...
What's with that
look on your face?
Does it mean...
I see, perverted master
what about handling the
master's semen like this
It's the same disgusting semen
that always sticks to your throat
What about it, master?
You can lick your
rear end on command
and give you the thong you
just took off as a gag
What's the verdict on the faithful sex pet that
drinks all of its owner's fishy semen into its belly?
What an incorrigible pervert
So master, I'll take care of the packing...
[20:18.53] See you tomorrow