Excuse me...
So, master, what do you intend to do
when you bring a girl into your room?
Well, the rules apply even outside
of school when it comes to sex pets.
So even if you give me an
order now, I have to obey
So master, what kind of Play
do you want to use today?
Lovers Play...?
Are you trying to make
me who's not a lover
whispering "like" while doing
horny things with you?
What a pathetic pervert
You know, even with that
Play, I wouldn't like you.
And even then it's okay?
I get it. So...
Master, I like you best
Master, I like it, I
like it, I like it best
Like it most of all
Master, it's just me
and Master today.
Anything you want to do, Master.
because...
Rei Kuroimi is the
master's lover
Is that satisfying?
What a pervert...
What is it, master?
I'm just sitting
next to you, huh?
The shy master will be
nervous about the distance
It's only natural, right?
If it's not a real girlfriend
wouldn't be this close to
you in a boy's room, in bed
It's clearly the owner who says
he wants to play Lovers Play
but he's getting all red-faced
because he's getting so close to me
It's so humiliating
I'm so close to my favourite girlfriend
and I can't do anything about it
Are you sexually impotent?
Master, you can only do this kind
of kissing with your girlfriend?
Sex pets are clearly the
owner's sex handling cups...
only exists as a sexual
gratification for the owner
This kiss that only
brings lips together
It's the kind of kiss that
makes girls swoon, master
How does it feel, master?
kissing a girl in uniform on the
bed in her room after school
It's a boy's dream
It's the kind of thing that normal
boys would never be able to do
You've been ogling me since
a while ago, haven't you?
My 91cm G-cup breasts...
bulging from a uniform different
from the usual erotic lingerie
And what's next?
Do you want to take
my uniform off?
How about that, master?
I think it looks plain and innocent
with white underwear on top and bottom
I don't really like the ones that
are too much of a showstopper
As a girlfriend's underwear,
that's a high score, right?
And then let's do the
tongue out kiss...
Come on, open your
mouth please, master
It's awkward... [07:44.92]
Is it a lack of confidence?
intertwine your
tongues properly...
My deep kisses are making
your body melt, aren't they?
The look on your master's face just
now was a very uncharacteristic look
The rod is erect again...
It's okay, I'll just do the tongue
kiss with you while I'm at it
while I jerk your dick
because now I'm
your girlfriend...
I like you, master
Come on, stick your
tongue out a little more
Come on, I'll come
and suck your tongue
Master likes kissing a lot
I like to kiss
with my master too
I'm really kissing you
like I'm your girlfriend
That's not nice...
but you're still kind of handsome
when you're kissing hard, aren't you?
Please don't get carried away
You see, girls love to kiss
So kiss more often to
satisfy your lover
What a clumsy kiss that totally
reveals your inexperience
Well, it wasn't bad at all
Did you say my panties were wet?
this it's just sweat
please don't get me wrong
Do you want to touch my pussy?
A wet pussy that's been made to mix sweat
and love juices by my master's tongue...
Yes, come on, please
Isn't that hot?
No, it's not the kiss with the
master that's turning me on...
Come on... more touching
That's right...
there's the clitoris...
It's the weak spot that girls always
tease when they masturbate...
Yes, that's the clitoris...
Please don't fiddle
with it all the time...
So intense... what
are you doing...
Ken must be a virgin, right?
I didn't know that the cheerleading
section had such rules and...
men like virgins, so before
offering them up as sex pets
you don't have to do pussy practice...
[15:56.96] That's what the counselor said...
So that's too intense...
kissing...?
Wait, stop for a
second...stop...I'm going...
Going, going, going...
I told you to stop
and you still forced me to come...
[17:18.25] That's so bad
You just flipped
my switch too...
I said master
Are you going to try to do the same thing
with me that you do with real lovers?
So that's why...
I'm asking if you want Rei
Kuroimi's virginity oh?
Sexual desire is
really like a monkey
No, that's a bit rude
to say about monkeys
Yes, master
I'm going to change my
clothes a little bit
If you look at me,
I'll kill you, master