Okay, you can watch
it now, master
How about this? It's the
master's favorite dirty bikini
From now on, you're going to be with a female
classmate who wears this kind of erotic clothing
and have sex for the first time
Are you excited?
My pussy is also in heat
from the teasing I just did
completely ready to receive
my master's rod at any time
So, the hymen I've
been guarding...
that I've been
protecting for 16 years
The pussy that I've
guarded for 16 years...
I'm going to give it to you now!
You can just lie there
I'll ride up and move myself
Okay, so...
Are we going to start?
Your rod and my
pussy are kissing
It's so hot it's
going to burn...
and then I'm going to
slowly lower my back
Your rod is opening up my
tight pussy and thrusting in
All the way in...
It didn't hurt as much
as I thought it would
I don't know if it's because yours is smaller
or because I'm a perverted masochist...
It's okay, master
I've been studying in the cheerleading section
to learn about boys' dreams too, haven't I?
Taking a girl's virginity
during her first experience
And then to have her waist
twisted to her heart's content
while the tip of the rod presses
and rubs against the womb
while pressing against it and cumming
internally boys love that don't they?
It's okay... [04:08.75] to cum internally
into my womb with your thick semen
The rod is getting
bigger inside...
Is it the imagination of cumming
in my pussy that's turning me on?
Deep in my womb, I'm being
pumped in and out...
Looks like you want
to get me pregnant...
Do you want to keep playing
Lovers Play with me?
Yes, although I don't actually
want to have your baby
but if it's an order
then there's no way out
Please let my womb
carry your little baby
Suddenly thrusting so hard...
Do you like playing
Lovers Play that much...
So, I'll be your lover
next time, right?
love it love it... master's
rod feels so good so good...
Come and kiss...
My pussy is getting excited
again after being kissed
and the sensitivity went up and
it became more comfortable
It's so comfortable even though
it's being thrust so hard...
I might be a perverted
female masochist too...
The depths of your stomach are
being pushed up from below...
This is so bad...
I'm sorry, I don't have the grace
to let out a lovely moan...
No grinding of the
womb like that...
Wait, wait, wait, wait...
too much pressure...
going for it... no...
no hitting my depths...
Here we go...here we
go...here we go...
Master It's so bad...
Why? I've been there...
[09:18.92] It's a lie...
No, I'm going... I
just had an orgasm...
It feels good... [09:31.71] I'm
about to come again... [09:38.55]
I'm sorry... I apologize
for teasing you...
I'm really, really sorry
for teasing the master
I apologize... [09:54.04] I apologize... [09:54.04] I
apologize... [09:54.04] I apologize... [09:54.04] I apologize.
It's going to get weird...
Going...
Are you about to cum? You can...
Please cum in my pussy and make
me pregnant with your child
there goes there goes
there...swoosh swoosh swoosh~
My womb is full of
my master's cum...
If I've been internally ejaculated with such
thick semen, I might actually get pregnant
Your cum is spilling
out of your pussy
The afterglow of your orgasm...
You'll be responsible for me
if I get sexually dependent
Well, even though I acted
a bit flustered earlier
but that was just my
performance, right?
Isn't that par for the course?
A woman who makes that kind of scream
just from her womb being hit...
Well, never mind, I'm not going to
continue discussing this with you either
Anyway, master
The day after tomorrow is the official
race day so tomorrow is the last time?
Please think about what
you want me to do, right?