Cheerleaders are given emergency contraceptives
after they've been internally ejaculated.
Basically, they have to be taken within 72
hours, and the sooner the better, it seems.
but I'm going to be separated from my master
by tomorrow anyway, so I haven't taken it yet
Then the master's orders are that he doesn't want
me to take the emergency contraceptive pill...
and that's okay?
called me into the club room after school
and made me dress up as a cheerleader
I was wondering what you were
going to ask for...it was boring
Do you think I'd answer "yes, I
can" to something like that?
Master?
You said I would do it if it was an
order but what if it wasn't an order?
I don't know what
you're talking about
Ah, so that's it. You think
I'll be charmed by your charms?
It's a genius to be
that self-absorbed
Aren't you more talented at
self-indulgence than the clubs you're in?
Master, don't you
just give me orders?
Like yesterday let me treat you
like a lover and say like...
Do you hate that?
Please command me quickly
Say "become the sex pet
girlfriend that likes me best"
Come on, hurry up... command me
Yes, that's right, before
the game ends tomorrow
Rei Kuroimi is the girlfriend and sex
pet who loves her master the most
Master, what are
you going to do?
after school in the club room because
the competition starts tomorrow
So there won't be any more people coming,
will there? You can do anything, right?
I'm cosplaying the girlfriend of a female
cheerleader as requested by the owner, right?
Look, look, look... Go, go, go!
You can do all the things that
boys think you can do to me?
I'll do what my seniors want and not
take the emergency contraceptive pill
So please make sure you
get me pregnant today
Do you want to kiss
a little more?
Okay, I got it
Okay, come on, do your master's
favorite tongue twister...
Stretch out your tongue a little more...
[05:47.08] You want to be sucked by me, don't you?
Please sit on the
bench over there
Well, I'll be rude
and sit on yours
Would you find it heavy?
What's wrong?
Do you still get nervous now
that we're sitting face to face?
I'm doing what my master
tells me to do, huh?
I'm your girlfriend
if it's a girlfriend
Don't you usually want to have sex with
the person you like while kissing?
And you say "you don't have to
force it if you don't like it"...
What a bad idea!
I know I like kissing
do you feel my
pussy getting hot?
It seems to be in heat
again from kissing you
I can't help it... I'm
going to stick it in...
This time it's coming
in smoothly...
How does it feel, master?
and the cheerleader girlfriend
who is obsessed with the master
linked together with
opposite seats...
I can feel the pussy connect directly to
the owner without the condom in the way
How do you feel about the
slippery feeling inside my pussy?
The folds of my pussy wrap around and
take on the shape of my master's rod
Yeah, it's nice, isn't it?
You see, because it's rare to use the opposite
seat, you have to hold me tight, right?
Even when you're hugging a pervert
like you, it's reassuring
It's so nice to be hugged while
being thrust with a rod...
Here it comes...
Kissing... nah, kissing too...
My body is so weird... [13:08.11] I'm
not supposed to like you at all...
but my pussy is so happy
every time your rod is in it
I love it, Master... I
love it the most...
I obviously thought
I wasn't slutty
but as soon as the rod was
in me, my pussy loved it
I'm such a perverted masochist
Master, I thought you were a boobie,
but you like asses too, don't you?
Hold on to the important
ass of a girl
The hindquarters are
still not allowed
I'm told that one won't be unblocked until
after the cheerleader's second year...
Hey, hey, hey, really...
while being played
with in the ass
while being pumped by the
rod feels so good...
I'm a pervert who feels
things in my ass too
I'm so scared to keep feeling this good...
but it's so good...
I like it, I like
it, I like it best
Rei Kuroimi likes
her master the best
I want to marry my master
and have his babies
I will give all I have to my master
and I hope that he will accept me
Give my womb a final blow...
so powerful, so intense...
is seriously trying
to get me pregnant...
I can feel by female instinct that
this male wants to impregnate me...
My body is sunken by your rod
I can't resist your rod anymore
like it... like it... master...
like it...
please fill Rei Kuroimi's
pussy full of thick cum
master please let me give
birth to master's little baby
like you master... like like....
please let my womb be something
completely for the master
going going going going...
shoo shoo shoo~
It's coming out a lot, master
The cum is flowing
backwards out of his pussy
This is definitely going
to get you pregnant...
What about it, master? [19:19.09]
The ideal sweet sex for a boy...
I feel good too, I thought I was
really going to fall for your rod
Come kiss me...
Nah, I like you
If you do get pregnant, you'll be
responsible for me then, won't you?