Master, aren't you
trying very hard here?
No, I really mean it, don't I?
Although I always thought the master was a
monster with only sexual desire in his head
but I can't believe I'm making
a good effort to join the club
I'm a little bit...though
really only a little bit
but I'm also impressed with you
And then what, master?
How are you going to be responsible
for my enlarged belly?
Even while sucking breast
milk from my breasts
while saying some handsome
line about being responsible
It doesn't sound very
convincing either
Forget it, if you'll treat
me like a girlfriend
and not as a sexual pet,
then I'll forgive you
even while sucking breast
milk from your breasts
while saying some handsome line
about taking responsibility
It doesn't sound very
convincing either
Forget it, if you'll treat
me like a girlfriend
and not as a sexual pet,
then I'll forgive you
I'm not happy, even if
you say you like it
Then, as promised, let me be your
girlfriend from today onwards
to enjoy sweet pregnant
belly sex with you?
You've got a great
erection there
from seeing my belly
swell with my own semen
excited by it?
What an incorrigible pervert
but as of today my body
belongs to you too
so it doesn't matter
what you do to me
Whether it's these huge breasts
that are starting to produce milk
or a wet pussy that's in
heat after seeing your rod
You can play with it
as much as you like
Suddenly the kiss
is so intense...
you seem to have
built up a lot too
You can... [03:54.11] just build
up your monkey-like libido
Take it all out on me
And let me taste
more of your tongue
And your saliva too...
Nah, it's almost time to...
And ask what for...
You know that... [05:22.58] You're
a real bad-hearted pervert.
I get it. I'll just
say it myself, right?
Please put your
rod...in my pussy
You're the one who's making
this perverted request
but my pussy is twitching
with anticipation
It seems we're both half
as kinky as each other
The tip of your rod is
pressed against my pussy...
The tip of your rod
against my pussy...
That's great... because it's been a while
since I've done it so I'm taking my time...
so intense all of a sudden...
It feels so good to be
pumped by the rod...
It's okay, drink more
of my breast milk
It feels so good to be sucked on my boobs
and fucked by a rod at the same time...
So into the boobs,
like a little baby
That's great... it's getting
bigger in there again...
So excited to drink my breast milk again...
[08:46.54] So happy...
I love it... I love you...
That's not a lie,
I really like you
My pussy is completely
falling under your rod
I'm in love with
you inside and out
Do you... like me too?
I'm so happy... just hearing the
word "like" makes my pussy tense up
I'm probably a good woman too
Is it almost time to cum?
It's okay. [09:47.48]
Please take your thick cum
and pour it all over my
masochistic pregnant belly
I'm going too, going, going...
masochist pussy
is going to go...
while spurting breast milk...
You're coming with me...
Phew, phew, phew
I lost consciousness for a little while... [11:04.50] The
pleasure of your internal ejaculation was so intense...
That was awesome... your cum is
still coming out of my pussy...
It's overflowing... so much...
It's as thick and fishy as ever
What are you resting on?
If you want to be my boyfriend,
one shot is not enough, right?
Nah, master...