●Episode 01: Prologue My
lover is a man's daughter.
Going out is fun, but spending time alone
together in a room like this feels special.
See, closer.
It's a shame to be apart.
Outside, you seem to be worried about people's eyes on you, but here,
you can be so close that your breath touches each other... right?
Right, so...
Mmm... oh, your face is
right in front of me...
Haaah, haaah~♪
Sorry, sorry, I just
wanted to breathe on you.
But your breath is on me too.
It's kind of creepy.
Hey, let's keep our lips
touching each other.
So... you want to kiss
me, I invite you.
No? Mmm, choo-choo...
Mm-hmm, I knew you'd
say no, I asked.
Don't laugh at me anymore.
Chuff, chuff, chuff,
chuff, chuff, mmm, hah...
Do my lips feel that good?
I see, I'm so happy.
I've been taking care of my lips
in preparation for kissing you.
But... but... but... but...
Mmm, I gave you a surprise kiss.
Did I surprise you?
For my part, I also like these...
slightly chapped lips of yours.
It's like you're nervous about kissing me, and I
think that's cute and innocent, that kind of thing.
Mmm, chu, chu... hah...
your face is red.
When you make a face like that...
nnnnggg... ah, I want to go deep too.
Ohhhh, deep kisses with open mouth
and tongue licking each other...
No, would you think it would be more
erotic if I called it tongue licking?
Ahhh... hum, nah, nchu...
you're so hot in my mouth.
Give me more tongue. Ruh, nmmm, juh,
juhp... juh, juh, juh, juh, juh, juh, juh.
Ha... you are...
Hmm? Maybe you're not
even aware of it?
Just kissing you is making me a
little hard in the front of my pants.
It's really easy to figure
out what a dick is.
I'm excited now, I'm happy - I
don't hide it, I express it.
I especially love yours because
you respond so quickly.
I'm not comparing you to
anyone, so don't worry.
Of course, I'm only
thinking about this dick.
Come on, kiss me some more. Rebu, nnnnnnn....jeez, jeez,
joooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo...
When you react like this, I
can't wait to fuck you too.
You're not going to ask
me what - are you?
Well, even if you pretend you
don't know, I'll answer you.
Sex with you...