●Episode 02 Masturbation
Play Oh, by the way...
I was bragging about you, and then my friend
gave me something weird as a present.
I promised to show it to her and
ask her how she liked it...
Can I just put it out there?
I'm sure it's in my bag...
Hmmm, here you go...
Yeah, a masturbator.
The body's a bit big there too, but...
look, here.
The hole is too big
to use normally.
It would be effective enough to
make you feel better, though.
It's not just my arm, it's
going to go in your arm too.
Fist-fucking... is
that what it's called?
I wonder if it's a product for people
with that kind of taste... Eh?
Oh... you think of
great things, you.
I was wondering if we
could use it together.
I think it's possible...
That's very violent
and disgusting play.
Maybe my boyfriend is a pervert.
I don't know... I can't
speak for others either.
Just imagining it makes me tingle...
and I'm getting hot.
Your dick is bulging bigger than before, and if it gets
any bigger, it's going to be painful in your pants.
Shall we fuck you as
soon as possible?
Masturbatory sex of
your own devising.
Hmm, we're lucky we're men, because
we get to play like this...
Then I'll have to take it off...
Hey look.
It's gone like this.
Swollen and upturned...
I'm surprised at myself.
I'm going to undress you too...
Wow, wow.
Aren't you getting stiffer
and harder than usual?
Ha, you like it that much?
Masturbator.
To tell you the truth, this is my
first time using a masturbator.
I was just wondering
what it feels like.
Well, even if you're a cat person,
you're at least interested.
I didn't think my first time would
turn out like this, though.
But... it's going to be
a very good first time.
I'm going to drip some
lube at the entrance.
Nnk, blend it in... is this
how it's supposed to be?
It looks kind of erotic.
Well, it's a toy, but when I think about the fact that I'm going
to put it in here, it starts to look more and more erotic.
Now... before you...
My cock and your cock, side
by side, facing each other...
And then... like the tips
of my cock together, mmm.
Oh, the glans and the glans rub against each other,
mmm, hmm... oh, this just feels so good already.
Hmm, I'm tempted to treat you
like this, but I'll hold back...
Only after you put it in
the masturbator, right?
Then, let's... zu zu zu zu~♪
Ah, ah, hah... mmmm, hmmm...
it's going in...!
The sensation of my cock being
wrapped in something wet...
What's this, what's this... the feeling of
the mushy stuff inside hitting my pole...
Oh, oh... so this
is a masturbator.
Maybe it's because I'm with you and I've got my dick in
you, but it's not loose or anything like that at all.
It's rather tight, like it's squeezing
your whole dick, it's amazing.
Mmm, nnk...
Umm, yeah, I have to get it
in all the way to the base...
Haahahaha, nnghhh...
mmm, it's done...
Amazing, we're both inserting
ourselves into the same masturbator.
The entrance is spread all
the way wide with two dicks.
Hey... look at me.
Choo, choo... haha, nnnn... I wanted
to kiss you to mark the insertion.
Let's move it then.
Mmm, oooh... hold the masturbator
firmly and take your cock out and in.
Hah, hmm, hah... the more you handle it, the
more stimulation... the stronger it gets.
Ah, hah, hah... kuh, nkuh... hmm, hmm...
hah, hah... nmm.
In and out... ah, hah... nngh.
Nkk, hahahahah, nhuh... nhuh...
nhuh... nkk, hi, ah.
It feels so good to have
a cock in my hole...
Because... nnh, nnh, I've had people put their dicks in
me before, but I've never had to put my own dick in...
Oh, oh, thrusting feels so good.
Mmm, mmm...hah,
hah...fuck, ohhhh...!
And, nnnn, ahhh... and, and... and... and... and... and... and... and...
and... and... and... and... and... and... and... and... and... and... and...
Ahhh... the erotic voice sometimes mixed
in... you can hear it right next to you.
Pre-cum, throbbing... mmmm, I'm getting
all tangled up in your cock inside.
I'm also getting... pre-cum, throbbing...
from your cock.
Mmm, nkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkk-
kkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkk...
Ohhh, when it's wet...
it's even better...
Nn~~~, didn't you just... just...
just a second faster?
Golly, I was vigorously rubbing my goosebumps with
my goosebumps... maybe it was a little bit bad.
I've only just started and I thought
I'm going to get out already.
Oh, hahaha... nn, nn...
it's okay.
I can do it...I want
to move it harder.
Come on, here I go... mmm, hah, mmm...
mmm... mmm... mmm...
Hah, hah, nngh, nngh... hgh, nngh...
hmmm, hmmm, hmmm.
With a cocktail of lube and their pre-cum, yeah, it
feels good to piston while making giggling noises.
Handling a cock with
a hole is so good.
Fuck, ohhhh... ahhh... nnghhhh...
it's getting hard there too.
Oh, oh, my stomach
is tingling...
Kuha, hahaha... this feeling...
Oh, God... it's making semen and
it's building up at the base.
Your cock is also...
hah, mmmm, hmmm...
You're cumming up my
balls, aren't you?
Ahhh... mmm, you're so
close to my dick, ahh...
I know exactly what
state you're in.
If you ejaculate inside a masturbator,
the semen will get mixed in too.
And the moment of ejaculation, everything,
everything... haha, we taste each other's cock.
Until the inside of my masturbator is coated
with mucus, agh... ahhh, hah, nn~~~...
When I imagine it, my thrill
rises even higher...!
Yeah, yeah...! I'm going to shake
my hips as much as I can and come.
Hah, hah... nnghhhh! Hahah...
ah... ah, nkuh...!
Masturbator, if I do it this hard, it might break, but...[09:34.32]I
can't stop even though I know I'm going to break it.
I like it when the head of
the cock bumps inside, yo!
Oh, fuck... I'm coming, fuck...
～～～～!
Fu, fu, ahh... ahhh,
it's coming out.
Your semen is hitting my
glans and it's disgusting.
I'm getting ejaculated on
while I'm ejaculating.
Haaah, haaah... nnghhhhhh...
haaahhhh...
I'm cumming... with your semen...
oh, I can't finish cumming.
Hahaha... mmm...
Hahaha... you were amazing
handling my cock together.
I let out so much.
Mmm, kuuuuh... oh my god, it's dripping
out of the entrance of the masturbator.
Mixture of white
and clear mucus...
Masturbatory sex,
that was so good...
It was a present from a friend,
so let's use it together again...