●Episode 03 Sex with a man's daughter What's
next... Hmm? Do you want to put it in already?
Okay.
Actually, you know, I've
prepared myself for anal.
All I have to do is lightly wet it with
lube and it'll be a fuck hole in no time.
Hmm, would you pull it off?
Or... would you be excited? I'll turn
your ass around like I always do...
Untie this long, vertical
anus with your fingers.
Ah, ah... nnghhh, yeah... put some lotion on the entrance and then use your finger... [00:36.70]Oh,
oh, oh... [00:37.71]Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh... Haaah, nn, hhh... haaah, nnghhh, nnghhh...
Nyup nyup nyup nyup... ah, nnghhh, haaahhh, ah, good.... Oh,
haaaa... haaaa... hmmm... hmmm... ahhh... haaaaahhh, mmmm...
Kissing too...chooch...hah,
nnh, chup...chup...chup...
Anal, you're making
nasty noises.
Creepy... nnchu, chupuru, rn, chumu, ah...
hah... hah... churu.
Hyah, nchuah... puhhh. Haha, I found your prostate... [01:40]
Rheeru, mmmpu... ahhh, mmmm! Nkku, hauuu... nkku, huuuuu...
Mmm... ah, it's time to go.
Let's put it in.
Oh my god, I'm so
wet, it's okay.
Come on, come on, I'm
opening my own bum.
Yeah, put it right there, hah... oh,
fuck... it's spreading... kuuuuunnnnn...
Hahahahah, ah, hah... hahuhhh, kuhhhh...
hah, it's in.
It's hot and hard
and feels great.
I still love this cock...
my anus is happy.
Piston slowly at first.
I want you to get used to
the size of your cock.
After all, it's a tight
hole with one cock.
Mmmmmm... hahahaha, ah, ah... yeah, keep
going. Hah, hah... nngh, nngh... hah, hah.
Fuuu...uu...uu...nkku,
haaaa...ha~, nnhaaaa...ahh...
Nnghhh... hah... nnghhh... hah... nnghhh,
the protrusion of the calli neck is caught.
I'm gonna rock your ass too.
I'm going to rub your
nice tight entrance.
Mmm, cu... ah, ah, ah...
mmm, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Hmph, nh... hah...
hah, ah, mmm, hah...
Haaaaah, ahhhh... kuhhh,
hhhhh, nnnhhhhhh...
Huh... that's good.
When you're doing this... don't you feel the closeness
between your cock and your anus increasing?
You start to understand even the smallest changes
and movements, and it feels better and better.
No, when this happens it's not
anal anymore... it's ass pussy.
It's more flexible than before, undulating deeper and
stimulating your cock... it's really pussy, this.
Nnnn, cuhhhh, ohhh... I
want to fuck you harder.
More close to my back... just put
your weight on it, yeah, yeah...
I'm going to put it in deep and pump it.
Nnghhhh... ah, nnghhhh, hag... deep...
And when I turn around.
I can see your feeling
face this close to me...
I love you, mmm...
Like this, mmm, mmm, hah, hah...
Rub your skin together as hard as you can, ah, nnghhh, hah...
Kuhii, nnghhhhh~... haaaaahhh... oh my God, it feels so good.
I'm getting my dick deep in your ass cunt.
Haaah, nnhhh, kahaha... ahhh, kufu, nggu.
Hi, hah, kuh ah, anh...
hah, kuh ah, ah~!
Ahhh, nnhaaaa... I love having my
boyfriend's cock gorging me deep inside...
Kuhnnn, hahahahah,
kaahahahahah, hihi, mmm...
Hyahhh, oh God... if you even touch
my nipples together, hah, mmm.
My ass pussy is so tight... ohhh,
ngh, I can feel your thick cock.
Hee, nng... hahaha, nghhh, hhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh-
hhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh...
Hah, hhh, hhh, hhh... hhh, hhh... hhh...
hhh... hhh... hhh... ahh.
Nngh... hhhhhhhh, are
you going to come?
You can let it out while
I'm deep-throating you.
This ass pussy is ready for you to cum inside it... [06:09.46]Hahhhh... [06:09.46]You can cum inside it... [06:09.46]You can
cum inside it... [06:09.46]You can cum inside it. You're going to have to spit out all the semen you've got in your balls.
I'm gonna cum too, so join me! [Nggg, hah, hahuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu! Hahhhhh... ahhh, nnggg, hmmm, hyah, nnggg!
Aaagh, aaagh! Hug, nghhh, hmmm, hmmm, hmmm! I'm cumming... my cock's coming! I'm going to spit it out... cough, cough!
It's coming out...
ooooh... ～～～～!
Ha ha, ahhh, ahhh~... soooo... sooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo-
ooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo...!
I'm going to soak your
ass pussy with semen.
Haaaaahhh... that felt so good.
Ohhhh... ohhh, I'm getting a nice
white discharge from the entrance.
Too erotic...
Come on, let's kiss again...[07:15.97]Chup,
nnnk...[07:15.97]Chup, chup, chup.
Pfft, you know...
I've got something I
want to ask you for.
What would you think if I told you that I
wanted to do the opposite next time...?
Tachineco reversal.
I mean, you want to have sex
with the one I put my dick in.
I'm curious to see how good your anal feels
and what you look like when you feel it...
Hey, hey, hey...
take my virginity.
What, in exchange?
Yeah, sure, sure.
I can't say anything, but
I'll make it happen if I can.
I'll be happy if you're
comfortable with that.
Hmm? Hmmm...I see?
Well, I kind of know what newlywed play
is like, but what is master play like?
Is it like being a
maid or something?
Do they wear costumes?
You still like that
sort of thing...
Ehh, which, slave?
Master's masochistic slave...
The kind that will gladly shake her hips no matter what kind
of perverted play is demanded of her... that's what I mean.
This way, the newlywed play
doesn't seem out of the ordinary.
You're going to be a perfect girl and you're going to do
it in a setting where your dick doesn't exist... um, yeah.
From kissing her welcome home to lovemaking
sex for pregnancy... hahaha, hahaha...
My face is hot just
imagining it...
That sounds pretty
embarrassing, that.
I didn't know you had
a hobby like that...
But okay.
I'm not averse to pretend sex either, and I'll
do my best to live up to your expectations.
So don't forget your promise.
Hmmm, do you want me to
cut your fingers off?
Or shall we kiss
like we promised?
Hah, choo-choo... mmm, choo-choo...
hah, chup, mmm.
Hmm, I'm looking forward
to it, Tachineco reversal.