●Episode 06: Master play 01: Forced floor
masturbation Master, I'm here now.
Please do whatever you want.
I am your obedient slave.
I am happy to carry
out your commands.
... ha, yes. I'm going
to take off my clothes.
I will properly show you my
disgusting body, Master.
Mmm, hmm... ah, mmm...
Haa, nn... you mustn't hide it...
right, I understand.
So, um, what's next...
When you say yourself...
is it masturbation?
I understand, I will obey
the master's orders.
I will do it so that you
can see it properly...
What?
If you tell me not to use my
hands, how can I do that...
Yup, floor masturbation...
That was masturbation, rubbing
your dick on the floor.
Gosh... you're on your back on the
floor and you're swinging your hips...
Oh no, it's embarrassing
just to imagine it.
My legs are shaking.
But... ya, I'll do it.
If that's the master's orders.
My first floor masturbation,
please watch.
Huh, the position is like...
like this?
Nnk... hah, nn, I have to
touch my dick on the floor...
I have to lie down on the bed...
... mmm...
I can't believe I'm dressed so...
miserably like a frog in front of Master.
Ahhh, ha, yes... I'm so embarrassed
I'm getting a cock erection.
I can feel it getting bigger and bigger
between my body and the floor, ugh.
So, then... I'm going to move my hips...
nn, hhh! Cold... hard... hghhhh!
Huh, nngh... it's different
from the masturbation I know.
Your own body presses on my cock,
rubbing against the hard place...
Even a slight movement brings a
tingling, numbing stimulation...!
This is floor masturbation...
To be honest, I'm scared
of the stimulation...
But... you've ordered me to do it,
so I will. Please let me do it.
Nnkk, nn, hiii... hahahaha,
kufu, nnghhh, nnkkk.
Hahi, ahhh, kuh, nnghhh...
hah, nng, nghhh.
Ugh, every rubbing
is a great one.
How are you doing? Are you
a good floor masturbator?
Oh... thank you.
Please have a look a lot.
I'm still a poor hip heckler,
but I'll do my best.
Press your back muscles against the floor, back and forth... Haa,
nnkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkk... Hifu, ah, ahh... kuhhh, ahhhh...
Yes, that feels good...
I'm properly feeling it on the floor...
kuh, ahh, haagh...! My dick is hot...
Oh, oh... what should I do...
I'm rubbing it all
over the floorboards.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
ahhh, kuh-uh.
But it's good, it's so good...
This is the best
masturbation I've ever had.
If I do it harder,
I'll stain the floor.
I'm about to get pre-cum all
over it, but I can't stop.
Mmm...mmmm...I'm rather tingling, wondering what will happen
if I go too hard. Hgh, hah, hah... kuhi, hahn, kyafu!
Hahahaha, ahhh, gross, hahi! That cock is
soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
I'm going to love
floor masturbation.
How can I not love it when it feels so good... [04:56.68]Hug,
nnghhh! Ahh, ngh, hah, hah, huggy, nghhh, hah!
It's a habit... I'm getting hooked...
hahaha, hahguuuuuh, nn~~!
... heh? Aaah, no...
Even if you're pistoning hard against the floor, even if
it looks like you're having passionate sex... hahi, ahhhh.
The only one I adore is Master.
This is just masturbation...
aagh, nngh.
Hagu, ngguah, haagu, nnghi,
believe me, master...
Please give me
additional orders.
I will obey anything, I will
prove that I am obedient.
Yes... thrust your hips forward and press your
back muscles completely against the floor.
We have received your orders.
Then... then... then, gosh... hi, ugh...
ngh, ngh... kuhhhh!
What is this... haha, ugh...
pressed.
I'm in quicksand and
my dick is in pain.
But it's just as good...
ku, fuuuuuck.
Kuruhi but... aagh, hagh, nnghhh...
hmmm, hmmm...
Gosh... huff, huff, don't toot yet... you have to show off your hips heko heko. Hecco heko, heko
heko oh... hagyuu, kuhihi, aagghh! Huggy, nnggghhh, kuhhh... oh, hekoheko, hekoheko ohhh...
Ah, ahh... Kuhhh, hah, fug... nnghhh, nnghhh,
hahi, ahi... ha~h, nnghhh... kuhhh, hahhhhhh.
I'm so happy on the floor wet with my own
pre-cum. It's disgusting how slimy it is.
Oh, I can't stop my hips from getting hard. Oh, hoggy... kuhhh, haagh, kuruhi... cock, kuruhi...! Ho-oh... haguah, nng... hihi,
hiiiiiiiiiii... haaah, gimohiiiiii! Master... haagu, nggu... haa, hihi, se, semen... it's coming. I want to take it out.
I want to spit it
out from my cock.
Can I?
Nkk, kuhhh, hah... please
give me permission.
Slave cock is not allowed to ejaculate without
permission, so if you don't say yes...
I, I uuuhhh... kuhhh,
ahhhh, hah, nkuhooooooo!
Ghhhhh, hahhh... cock ohhh, I want to cum. Please allow me, please allow me... I'll do
anything...! Guhhh, nghhh... hi, guhhh... hagyuu, kohyuu... hoooooooooooooooooooo....
Ah...
Yes, yes...! Thank you.
I'm going to ejaculate... on the floor like this. I'm going to cum, I'm going to cum. I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming,
I'm coming. Cock, cramp... oh, it's coming, it's coming, oh, it's coming, oh, it's coming... kuhuuhuuhuuhuuhuuhuuhuuhu... ～～～～...!
Haahahah, ohhh... you're
cumming, ohhhh...
Semen is flying out of
my pressurised cock.
Ohhhh, huuuuhh... master, I like
floor masturbation ejaculation...
Kuuuh, nnkyuuh, hahaha... ggh, I'm going
blank, gghhhh, ahhh, fuggghhh...!
Hhah... ah... ah... hhooohh...
oooh...
Ha, yes... it's out.
I ejaculated between the floor
and my body... ah, hah.