●Episode 08: Master
play 03 Slave sex.
Hahahaha, nnh... Hahahaha, ah,
I got Master's feet dirty.
I'm sorry I splashed
slave semen on you.
Yes, I will responsibly
lick them clean.
Let me carefully lick and clean you
from the soles of your feet... mmm.
I'm sorry, my dear... leb,
njuuuuh, hahahaha, mmmm, ngguuh.
Haah, nnghhh...njuh, lebuh, juu,
juuurrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr...
Chumu, chupuah, rurrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr-
rrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr...hyaaa, bitter.
Nchu, neruh, hahm... chupu...
and it's thick and plupu.
It tastes like slave semen...
mmm, hah, nnk, jizz.
Mmm... chup, chup...
oh, Master's erection.
Um, please let me continue to
serve your cock, master's cock.
My mouth is full of the taste of my own slave semen, I
want you to let me override it with the taste of Master's.
I don't care how bitter it is.
Because if it's Master's,
it will taste good.
Say hello to your cock first.
Mmm, chup... haha, thank you for
allowing me to give you a blowjob.
Mmm, chu, chu, chupp...
hahaha... hah, mmm.
Oh, I smell so much cock...
mmm, chu, chu-puh, hah.
I'll be, nmm, chup...
hah, nmm, chup, chup.
Hahaha...then...I'm going to suck you to the back. Aam, nnjuh, jyuuru, ngguah, jyuupuah...
nnjuh, ngguah... hah, you're so big... you're so big... you're so big in my mouth.
Mmm, jubub, nghhh...
nmm, njub, njub, njub...
Kimo hiiiiiiru ka... jumuah,
gubu, neruju, juju, juju pururu.
Njuru, hahaha, jjubu...erubu,
njubu, njugu... nmm?
Puhhh, more like... ngumu, hiii...
fuguuuuu!
In your throat?
Hyah, nngghh... use it.
Gubu, gebu, nggu... gafu, nggu oh, I can't breathe...!
Habu, nggu, nggu, gubu, gubu, gubu... ngguuuuu!
Swell up... mah-kaa, gub-oh, oh, gub-oh...
gub-chug...
Gubu, gubu gubu... higi...
higuuuuu!
Muggghhh... ugh, ggggh...
ggggh... ugh...
Ngg, ggg... kehokehokehokehokehokehokehokehokehokehokehokehokehokehokehokehokehokehokehoke-
hokehokehokehokehokehokehokehokehokehokehokehoke... [03:06.59]Nggu, hahahaha... nggu, hmmm...
Oh... thank you for
Master's thick semen.
It's so thick and so much that it almost makes me swoon, and to
receive such an ejaculation... keho, kahaha... I am a happy slave.
Hahahaha... oh, my
cock, it's still hard.
I'm properly ready.
I've prepared lotion so that Master
can use it anytime he wants.
I'm going to stick my finger in.
See, see... nnnk, hahmmm, hmmm... you're
making a giggling sound, aren't you?
You are also useful as an
ass masturbation slave.
Please enjoy yourself with me.
Oh...! Now, please
excuse me on your knees.
I will accept myself into
your ass and shake my hips.
I'll make sure you can see everything...
agh, ugh, thick.
My entrance widens in the shape of
Master's...ohhh, haaaaahhh, ahhh...kuuuunnn...
Haaah, nnnk... ahh, I was
able to insert it firmly.
From here, move your hips
up and down, aagh, nngh...
I'm going to handle your cock.
Hhh, hhh... kuh, ahh, ahh, mmm,
hhhhh, hah... hah... hah...
Nkk, nkk, nkk, haaahhh, hhhhhhh...
hahgh... hahgh... hahgh.
Hahhh... can you even see
the folds being rolled up?
Every time you pull it out and in and
out... hmmm, hmmm, hmmm... ahhh...
It's being rolled up and
pushed in, nnghhh, nghhh.
It's completely turned into erotic folds,
my asshole... Hagh, hmmm, look at it.
Hah, uh...? Oh, my cock...
it's erect again...
Kuha, ahhh, hmm, hah,
hmm, hmm, hmm...
Aagh, it's because your ass feels
so good, I think, ugh, ahh.
I'm so happy now that I have Master's cock and I'm serving
pistons, so... agh, nnkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkk... ahhhhh!
Kuhhhh... hahahaha, hmmm...
ohhh, I'm sorry.
I've stopped moving.
The prostate gurgling hit me and
it felt so good... nnghhh, hah.
Ts, I'll continue. Hagh, nghhh, ohh... ahhh, hyagh, nghhh, hhhhhh. Hah...
hiagh ah ah ah, nngh, nngh. Oh, oh no... it's coming, it's coming... hahuuuu!
I won't ejaculate first alone, I'll hold back...I'll hold back, but...! [07:07.79] I won't
ejaculate first by myself...I'll hold back, but...! Hagyu, nng... ah, huahhh... kuhhhhhhhhh~.
Ha, hahi... ah, hah... that was... meh, meh... meh... meh...
meh... meh... meh... meh... meh... meh... meh... meh... meh...
I came like a woman
without ejaculation.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry...!
Agyu, nggu...ho, ho oh,
the thrusting is amazing.
You're holding my dirty body like this, and you're masturbating me to the fullest. I'm so happy... and... ah,
ah, kuhn, ohh, ohh... ah, ah! Kahii, oh, ohh... ha, guh... nnggghhh, haaaaah. I have to do it to you too...!
Nggoo, oh, ohh... hugh, nnh, nhoooh,
kimohi, kimohi, lesuuuuu...!
Ho, nnggh... hgh, ahhh...
hyah, nnggh, hahaha...!
Shugo, oh, ngggh, hhh...
cgh, hgh, ahhg, nghhh!
I'm gonna come so hard...
but it's so good.
Hagyuu, oh, ohg, use it deep inside,
serve me... aagyuu, nggu, hagu!
Ngg, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah... ah... ah... ah!
My, my master... my
cock is swollen.
Are you going to
ejaculate on me?
Come on, come on... dump
your cock in my arse-cunt.
Higu, nghhh, ohhh... bum bum bum bum bum bum bum
bum... bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum.
I'm going to make you come... gf,
oh, oh, oh, ngg, hmmm... hahi!
Higuah, ahhh... kuhn, nnghhhh...
haaaaahhh, hi!
Semen come, semen bless you...
give it to me... hmmmmm...!
Fuuuuuu... hah, hah...
hahii, ahhh.
It's coming in my
stomach, it's coming.
Me too...Hig, ugh,
I'm coming again.
I shouldn't cum on Master's belly too...
ahh, mmm, ahh, hah, hahi.
Yes, yes...
Please punish me.
Please discipline your wicked perverted
masochistic slave, Master...
You're quite the
sadist, aren't you?
The way you looked down at me,
you were just like a master.
I was being tortured so much it hurt,
but I really felt it too and I came.
But this is the end of the
newlywed play and the master play.
Now it's finally my turn.
Of course anal, but there are
other plays I'd like to try.
I can't wait for it now.
I know you're looking
forward to it too... mmm...