●Episode 09 Tachineko Reversal 01: Footjob & Chick Stomping Haamu, nunchu... hmmm...
nmmm... chu-chu, chu-puru, nuru-chu... nnn~? Of course she's in a good mood.
Today is the day when you can
ask me any naughty request.
Don't worry, I'll never
do anything painful.
I like you, so I want to try different
sex and see different reactions.
I want you to trust me there.
You didn't suggest playing with
me with that in mind, did you?
You look so troubled...
so cute...
Will you take off your
trousers and sit down first?
Not next to me, in front of me...
on the floor, not on the bed...
Hmm, you have a cold bum.
I understand.
Keep your legs wide open.
Kneel up on your knees... yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah... it's called an M-shape spread.
Ha, very erotic...
It feels fresh to look down.
And... you can see so much
better in this position.
My still docile cock and my tight
asshole are all in my view.
Could you guess what
I'm going to do?
You played with me first, so I can
guess what you're going to do.
Let me handle your
dick with my foot.
That felt so good.
I was also excited by the sight of you
moving your legs while looking at me hotly.
So... let me be in the
opposite position this time.
Here, rub your feet...
rub your cock...
Nn, hah, hah... nn, cu... hmm...
hah, mmm... like this...
Nnhaaah... hah, semi-erect cock soft and ticklish. Ahh, nngh, hah, hah, hah, hah...
nngh, hah... nngh, hah... Kuhuh, hahuh, nnghhh... hah, nkuhuh... hah... hah...
I don't know, am I
as good as you?
Trace the back muscles with
your feet, mmm... hah, mmm...
I stroke the tip with
my foot on the ground.
This felt good.
Hey, does the master feel...
ah...
Oh, hah... nhuh, hah, nhuh...
hah, nhuh, nhuh, nhuh.
Nkuh... hmmm, hmmm...
hah, hmmm, hah.
I'm glad you're feeling
properly comfortable...
You're going to have a hard-on
before you know it, Kimi.
I'm glad you're doing so well.
Hahahaha... nnh... nnh... nnh... nnh...
nnh... nnh... nnh... nnh... nnh.
Every time you jerked off as my foot played around
with you, your hardness and size increased.
You're really honest, you cock.
For you, it's like... hah, mmm,
I don't know, it's a problem.
You look so embarrassed and you're
trying so hard to hold back your voice.
Hah, mmm... so~le, I'll
keep stroking you.
Nn, hah... nn, nn, nn... the tip,
it's getting more resilient.
Nn, ah... hah... nnk, hah, hah... nnh... nnh... nnh...
nnh... nnh... nnh... nnh... nnh... nnh... nnh...
Ahh, nnnk... nnnk, nnnk... hah, nnnk...
how about here?
Oh, I like that
reaction, I love it.
Haah, ahh... nnnk, nnnk... hah, I
want to make your legs even harder.
...phew, yes.
You even stepped on me with
your big feet, didn't you?
It was a mixture of pain and feeling
so good, I almost went blank.
That feeling...I thought I'd let
you have a taste of it too.
I'm gonna...
squeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee...
Yeah, yeah... nnnkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkk-
kkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkk...[05:18.06]I'm going to give you a taste.
Giggle, nnggg, hah, nmmm...
hh, guh... nghhh.
Hyah, ahhh... wetting...
You're starting to come
out ahead of time.
When you step on my cock, you'll hear a nasty
sound coming from the soles of your feet.
See, see... how can
you not hear it?
Haaaah, good sound.
There's no way to hide the fact
that you're feeling my feet now...
Hhh, mmm, that... that... that I'll step on it more...
[06:09.93]Kuhhh, hah, hah... nghhh, hah... nghhh, nghhh!
Mmm, it bounced so
much under my feet.
Kuhaaaah, hah, nn... hey, if you don't
have to~... are you going to come?
Heh, I'm about to ejaculate uncontrollably
when you step on my dick with your foot...
Dawg, I'm not going to stop you.
If you're going to ejaculate, you're
going to do it with my foot, right?
Don't ejaculate anywhere else.
Hmm, Master made me do that too.
Haaaah... remembering that time
makes me even more excited.
The cool master who was stepping on my cock, and the cute you who was
feeling it with tears in your eyes when I stepped on your cock...
I can see them overlapping
and my roots are tingling.
And then... [07:19.63]I'm going to
put all this pressure on your legs.
If you keep shaking me finely like this...
what do you think will happen?
The semen comes up from
deep inside your cock.
See, see, I won't stop!
Mmm, mmm, hahahaha, mmm, hahahaha...
kuh, hahahaha...
Oh, ahhh, nnnk, nnnk... hah, I'm
going to keep going until you cum.
Hah, hah, nnk... hh, nnk...
hah... hi, nnk.
The base is swelling more and more. You
can't get enough of my cock, can you?
It feels so good to have a thick
one coming up, doesn't it?
So I'm going to do more, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm,
mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm...
See, see, see, see...
nnnk, haaaaahhh, nnghhh!
Haah, nnnkkk... ah, you've
reached your limit, haven't you?
One more blow and I'll jump out.
Even if I resist saying "no~",
oh, nnghhhh, hahig, hahig...
Balls pumping not at all mature...
make you cum like I want you to...
I'm going to tommy you
while staring at you.
Spurt your semen out with my foot...
that's it, that's it, that's it...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh... hot...
I can feel your cock
quivering under my feet.
Every time you move, it spurts out semen...
haha, that's so erotic.
You got a footjob
too, didn't you?
You said you couldn't do it.
You even pushed your cock into the soles
of my feet yourself towards the end.
Hmm, I'm not making fun of you.
Mmm, chubby... the most disgusting
and wonderful boyfriend.
Can I ask you for
your next request...