●Episode 10: Tachineko reversal
02: Nipple attack & ear licking.
Here... give me your hand. You're
losing your strength, aren't you?
Next time I'm going to hold you
while I do it, so don't worry.
I'll hold you.
You're bigger than me, but if you stretch
your arms out, I can squeeze you like this.
Your back is a little sweaty...
[00:24.48]Smell your neck.
You felt me until
I was like this.
Haaaaah...kun-kun, I'm so happy.
Of course I don't just hug you.
There are many things
I still want to do.
Haaaaahhhhhh...
Haha, good response.
I just blew on it.
I want to see a better reaction, so...
I'm going to lick your ears.
Nnellllll, jhmm, jhmm, jhmm,
jhmm, jhmm, jhmm, jhmm, jhmm.
Licking your ears...
how do you like it?
It's a different feeling than
getting your dick licked, isn't it?
Ju... nnnnjum, jum, jum, jum,
jum, jum, jum, jum, jum, jum.
Njumu, njumu, njumu, njumu, njumu, njumu,
njumu, njumu, njumu, njumu, njumu, njumu.
Nnju, nnju, nnju, nnju, nnju, nnju,
nnju, nnju, nnju, nnju, nnjp, nnjp.
Jumu, njumu, njumu, nareruu,
chumu, jumu, jujuu.
Mmm, hah... I could keep licking your ears like
this, but there's something else I want to do.
I'll leave it at that.
Next time...I'd like to
play with this part of you.
Rustle my nipples...
You know that even men
can feel good, right?
And that's a female nipple that's
hitting your back right now.
Let's make yours matching too.
Here, hmm, first of all, prepare
to feel it with your nipples.
I'm not going to make you
hard all of a sudden.
No direct touching yet.
I'm going to use the palm of my hand
and stroke it through your shirt.
Really gently,
without any force.
Slide your hand
from top to bottom.
Now from bottom to top.
Rustling... rustling - I still don't
distinguish between nipple and areola.
Slowly, slowly, slowly over the
whole breast... rustling, stroking.
Nudge, nudge, nudge...
hmm, ticklish?
Don't worry, that's just
the way it is at first.
Mmmmm...
Don't resist, you don't even
need to say that you can't.
Just concentrate on my
voice and my nipples.
Nnh, hah... rustle,
rustle, rustle.
Both breasts, stroke them gently...
warm them up.
See, your chest has
gradually warmed up.
And your nipples are starting to show up on
your shirt a little bit more than before.
I'm starting to realise
that it's here.
Then...I don't want to touch
them...[04:42.21]Mmmmmm...
I dare you to ignore my nipples,
which are starting to get pointed.
This time around... rub and twirl your
fingertips to explore the shape of the areola.
Kuru-kuru... kuru-kuru.
Kuru-kuru, kuru-kuru...
kuru-kuru.
Kuru-kuru-kuru... a little bit closer
to the nipple... but don't touch it.
Huh? I'm a bit
disappointed, aren't I?
Did you think, 'Please, ohhhh... please fuck my
nipples too with the force you're using now'?
...ah, don't make erotic noises?
Duh. I'll say on your behalf what
you're too embarrassed to say.
Just listen to me.
Kuru-kuru-kuru-kuru,
nipple-ring-kuru-kuru.
"I want to be nippled, I want to be nippled, I want to be
nippled, I want to be nippled, I want to be nippled....
I want to be fucked so much...
Look, tsun tsun, tsun tsun...
Tsk tsk tsk, kunyu
kunyu kunyu...
The pointiness of your nipples
is getting bigger than before.
You've been waiting
to be played with.
Mmm, Kunikunyu, Kunikunyu...
twang, twang, Kunikunyu.
"Feels good, feels good..."
Kunikunyuukunyuu~.
But oh, there's more to come.
Sensitive nipples... don't you
want to be touched directly?
So~let me slip my fingers inside
your shirt... wow, plump...
You can lightly press your fingernails
against it and crunch, crunch, crunch...
Click, click, click... nngh, hah... nngh, hah...
nngh, hah... nngh... nngh... nngh... nngh...
I was soooo scared all over.
Then continue crunching, crunching...
hahf, crunching... hahf, crunching...
Crunch, crunch...nk, harder,
crunch, crunch, crunch.
I'm going to scratch your
nipples more and more.
Where they're about to become female
nipples, I force them to blossom.
I can't wait for the thrill to spread from my
chest... See, even my hips are swaying on their own.
"Mmm, hahaha... ohhh, nipples are so good... crunch
me more... please tease my female nipples..."
Hmm, maybe one day you'll feel better
just hearing my voice, crunch, crunch~.
When that happens... I'll whisper it
to you secretly in public places.
I'll make you impatient
without touching you...
Hmm, did you imagine that?
My heart is amazing, I can feel
it in my hands, it's racing.
But now that we're
alone, no rushing...
Here we go.
Crunchy, crunchy, crunchy.
Crunchy, nipple crunchy...
crunchy, crunchy...
I'm going to push you harder
and harder to stimulate you.
I'm going to make sure that the
pleasure spreads to your cock...
Crunch, crunch, crunch, crunch...
kary...
Hahaha, when are you going to get a hard-on... you're
going to get a nipple cumming and you're going to cum?
You're really talented.
Then I'm going to pinch your nipples,
which are now completely sexualised.
I'm going to lightly claw them, squeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee-
eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee!
Stimulation that might have been a bit
painful at first... you're happy.
"I can feel your nipples
creeping up my cock."
"Oh, I'm cumming... I'm cumming
from the nipple squeezing..."
Nnnnnn, hah, squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak,
squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak.
Your hips are rocking, that's good...
kurikku, kurikku kurikku.
"Ahhhhh... I'm cumming, I'm cumming
when they play with my nipples."
S~leeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee-
eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee.
I spewed so much!
Wow, I never thought I'd
actually cum on my first nipple.
I'm going to keep pinching your
nipples so you can finish it.
Kuri kuri kuri, kyu
kyu kyu, kyu kyu~.
Yes, I came good.
Come on, let me see your face...
hmmm, you're making me squint...
Are you sleepy, pretty...
Choo, choo... hah, nnnnnn... hah, nnnn...
but I won't let you sleep.
We've still got the
show to go on.
You've been hitting me in the
ass since a while ago, right?
My cock is getting stiff even
though I didn't touch it.
Nngh, haaaa...[11:08.54]Don't make my ass squirm
anymore...[11:08.54][11:08.54][11:08.54][11:08.54][11:08.54]I'm gonna get you...
You're reacting so naughty, I
can't afford to be too naughty.
Hey, I can't wait to
fuck your ass with this.
Of course you won't
say no, will you?
Nngh, hah... chum, chum...
but I won't tell you...