●Episode 12 Epilogue I love you.
Your ass tightens up and moves like
it's trying to drink up all the semen.
I thought it was going to
suck my consciousness away.
Hmm, I'm not exaggerating.
It's all true...
I was going to enjoy the look on your face when you were feeling
it, but... you got carried away and moaned all over the place.
I slammed my hips into you without any
restraint... and it's hard on your ass, isn't it?
I'm sorry, I'm not
used to being tapped.
... are you okay?
Yeah, good then.
Hmm, thanks.
You've been with me for a lot
of the sex I want to do.
I know it's in the name of getting back what you
asked for, but it's still a nice thing to do.
Choo, mmm... hah, choo, choo...
mmm... I love you.
So - I'm begging you.
Will you let me do it again,
just once in a while?
Tachineco reversal sex...
Because you seem to have a
talent for nipples and anal.
I want to make you
feel even better.
I want to make you learn
how to be a mesmeriser.
I think she'll show me the cutest
and she'll moan with a nice voice.
I can't stop imagining that.
Of course, next time, I won't ask you
to do me a favour one way or the other.
I'm going to do you
a favour first.
And if you're willing to give me your anal... I'll
do my best to give you any kind of kinky play.
Both the newlywed play and the master play were
extremely embarrassing... but they felt just as good.
You know what else you
want to do, don't you?
...and well, now we've both given each other plenty and we're
both moderately tired, so let's just hang out together.
Haha... I, you know, I like this
kind of relaxing time after sex.
I like the time... when we hold each other and slowly savour each other's
sleepy, sweaty smells. Hahmmm, nnchu, chu... haaaa... nnkk, chu, chu...
Chupu... hahf, nn... like... nnp, chu...
hmm, I love you, my boyfriend...
Finish.