1. waking up to
masturbation appreciation
Art thou...art thou awake?
Did you get scared
Please don't stare
at me too much
I think you made a
very loud noise
My body is always
restless in the morning
Today my body is even more
restless and hot...ah
As I told you last night
My private parts are very greedy
I don't know if it's because of you that you
don't put your finger in it and stroke it...
I'd be so hot all over my body
Even now my body craves the
pleasure of last night
so that the spider silk that
binds you is spewing out...
I have shown thee a
disgraceful side of me
I can't stop my fingers
Do you ask if demons
can masturbate too?
How can there be any creature in
this world that is not in heat
It's all your fault
It was thou who gave me
the ultimate pleasure...
Last night was really too...uhhh
Don't look. Don't
look at me like that.
It's...hot...so hot
I can't stop my fingers,
it's so uncomfortable
Don't look at me again
It's so good, I can't think
Did you do something
while I was sleeping?
No, my brain can't think at all
I need to be more violent~
I'm coming, I'm
coming, I'm coming!
Here we go, here we go!
I told you not to look...
Why are you still staring at me? If the
answer is not to my liking, I will eat you!
And thou sayest that thou canst
not take thy eyes off me at all?
That is to say... you
are fascinated by me...
As long as thou art not despising
or pitying me...all is well...