2. Little girl posing
for sexual intercourse
Thou...take responsibility and try
to deal with my private parts
Try to soothe my private parts
A single orgasm is not
enough to satisfy it
I want... I want you
It's not enough,
it's not enough!
You wait first
See, I've sealed
the spider's legs
It will be easier to have
intercourse in human form
It's called the art of transformation, but
this pose is a little more constrained
Can you... hold me
tighter than this?
Okay, then I won't go
into what just happened
But that said, now it seems as if
your body has grown a little bigger
Now thou lookest very sturdy
Seeing my body, thou
seemest ready here too
What an honest man
May I ride on thy body?
I will mount thee
and twist my waist
With this body I
will not spew silk
nor will I crush
thee with my weight
I'm going to penetrate.
How is it? [03:12.99] How does it
feel to have sex with a human girl?
This body looks very young
People might not even
think I'm a grown woman
I'm going to continue
to lower my waist
In...here it comes
When my body shrinks, it's
more like I'm pampering you
I'm a little shy
It seems to you as if you
were violating a little girl
Does it excite thee more?
May I begin to wriggle?
I can't help it, I'm writhing!
Good...big~
That's it, that's
what I'm longing for
And...since I'm in human form
and since I am now
in human form,
my privates have become tighter
My private parts are
tighter, aren't they?
You do this...
every day to me...
give your body to me every day
For my sake...live
Just exist for me...live for me!
Let me bind thee
Even without the spider's thread, I
will deprive thee of thy freedom
I will not allow thee to
die so easily...never!
Thou art my own
Something that
belongs only to me
Come on, I'm going
to pump even harder
This... is great... the human form...
is so comfortable
The first time I made love in
human form was so comfortable~
The privates are so small that
they can easily penetrate deep
Move your waist for me
Move it...
Make thee mine own
here it comes
here we go, here we go
That's a nice look
happy?
Keep on living
You only have to be with me
to make your presence known
Come on, thou too, pump thy loins,
I want to be pounded by thy cock
I'm so happy, so comfortable...
So...so good!
Even if you are denied by your own
kind, I will prove your worth
so hard~ so firm~
I want to trust you
with everything
So good~
Look, these are your
favorite breasts!
Enjoy the swaying of my breasts,
which do not fit my smaller body
And look upon my breasts...
and my...expression
Look at my face as a little girl who is intoxicated
with the pleasure of being violated by you
That's a great look.
Harder, harder!
There you go, that's big!
I'm going!
Are you going to cum too?
Yes, come on, come on!
In this position, perhaps
I can get pregnant
Come on, make me pregnant
Make me pregnant
Go...go, go, go, go
Here we go, here we go,
here we go, here we go