3. Peace and tranquillity in a little girl's
gesture to accompany sleeping intercourse
It's raining
Let's kiss... I want to kiss...
Why are you suddenly
touching my head...
Isn't it nice to kiss sweetly?
Let's keep kissing, shall we?
It's nice
I love it!
I want to invade your body... your mind...
your whole being
And not to pull out
I want to continue to
feel your warmth... okay?
I can't spit out the spider...
Can you help me?
Nay, thy body is trembling
Is it a little cold?
Nay, is it sobbing
So, thou wishest to
exist for my sake
Good boy, good boy, I'll
take everything you have
Oh yes, thou art already mine
So I will not allow
you to die so easily
I'll give thee more peace of
mind with my little girl's pose
Or is the spider woman's form
more sexually arousing to thee?
You don't want to be bound by
spider silk again, do you?
Ah, it's so good, your
cock is still so hard
I can feel your warmth
deep inside my body
It is so comfortable
Yes, why should I only
be attracted to you?
To me, man is a savage
and lowly creature
But... perhaps even if thou
hadst seen my true face
you approached me without fear
I was perhaps struck by your
begging and helpless posture
and the desire to protect
I was a little puppy at the time
To be honest, I
wanted to eat you too
but...your attitude
of wanting to die
made me hesitate...
perhaps out of pity for thee...
Or perhaps I was overwhelmed
by your magnificent body
I'm quite taken with thee too
Do you still wish
to be eaten by me?
I'll eat you too, hehehe
Thou art an inscrutable creature
though humans are the most
intelligent of all creatures
but only humans
would take the initiative
to end their own lives
and even more so in this kingdom
I'm told they have a wide range of
suicidal techniques such as harakiri
driven by the idea of "shame"?
Is there anything more precious in
this world than to end one's own life?
is there anything more painful in this
world than to end one's precious life?
I cannot, after
all, understand...
but I am also interested
in this foolishness
Maybe it's because I don't understand
it that I want to understand it more
In the end, I can't understand
the cause of your pain
How unfathomable
It is because thou art determined
to die against common sense
That makes me want to
know thee more deeply
Good boy!
From now on I will be with you
Nah, that's good
My body is so hot
I am to blame for
my sexual desire
so my body is
particularly honest
my waist tends to start
to twist unconsciously
I'm sorry I'm so
lustful and lustful
Just keep this
position like this
I want you to stay inside
me for a while longer
I'm so relieved~
It's so warm
What are your plans
for the future?
Will you continue to live in
this ruin with me like this?
Well, then I will visit
your home together
but... rest for a while
It's so warm~
You ejaculated so
much last night
but your penis is still intact
What a good boy... good boy...
Take me into your
arms, that's it!
You can rub my breasts
as much as you like
Good~ caress my breasts gently
Yes, that's right, that's good
You're so skilled at this
Closer to me
Let's hold it... it's
so comfortable...
My breasts are so
soft, aren't they?
Our nipples are so firm that
they're touching your body
Do you like that?
What an honest boy...