4. Blowing into private parts
Is this the...flat you live in?
There doesn't seem
to be anyone there
It's almost time to go back
to your old form, isn't it?
It feels a bit small
If you eat the neighbours... you'll
have a two-bedroom apartment...
Hmm? What's wrong?
If you want me to stay
in peace, treat me well
I don't think you're that
good, I won't eat you...
Come and make me feel good, and
I'll let you go if you do well
Come on, come here
Lean your head towards the part where
the human and spider parts meet
No, don't lick
Just bring your
face closer to it
Your breath...is hitting
a sensitive spot
Ahh...it's so good
That's it, the feeling of the
tip of your nose touching
Yes, there it is...
It's so nice here...
Don't ever stick
your tongue out.
It's tickling me
Can you see...see me
yearning for the male
teased...it's all rising up
I'm sure I'd be shy
if someone saw me
But you're already my family...
I want you to know me
better and trust me more
To show you the nasty side of
me...that no one has ever seen before
It's so comfortable...
I do like to be
licked down there...
But being teased like this...
I like it too...
The feeling of touching
but not touching...
I can't help it...
Hold this position...and breathe...
that's it, yeah
It's so good...
That's great
What? It's not like I want to be spied
on...I want to expose myself to people
I'm not the kind of
person who's not shy...
Ah no, to be honest, I'm still
shy about showing it to you too
I'm shy but the pleasure
outweighs the shame
It's really nice to be blown on a
sensitive spot...with a slight gasp
I'm too sensitive there...
I get a slight flush even
when I touch it myself
If I get licked...I'm sure I'll cum
all over the house with spider silk
I can barely hold it in with a
little bit of a blowjob like this...
Your body heat makes me feel
at ease...so comfortable
Of course it tickles...and
I'm embarrassed to do it
Even for you...I'd be shy
But even so...doing this with
you...I'm happy as can be
I'm willing to show it to you
because it's you, you know
A human being who has recovered a
life and thrown himself at my feet
Poor, sweet, fragile
human beings
without my shelter
would have died...
It is because of you...that
I am comfortable
Bring your face a
little closer...
It's a cramped and plain
room, but it's nice
I don't need anything
extra...you're here...
as long as you're here
I want to hold you but it's
hard to do so in this position
At least let's interlock
our fingers...
It's so warm
It's so nice to blow
long and hard like this
Just a little more...
so nice
It's my turn...
You like that, don't you?
It's blowing back~
Ah no...
I've already said
it's sensitive...
I can't help you!
Let's do more
I love it...I love it...being
blown long and hard like that
Good boy~ Good boy~
What a good boy~
Blow some more...
The sun...is setting
It's going to be night soon
People are sleeping
and we're alive
Shall we go out
and see the moon?
What are you so nervous about?
It's a long night
Let's do this until morning
That'll be fine
It's so nice
I may be smelling very lustful
to entice the male scent
very... very nasty
smells and noises
my body still remembers what it was like to have
sex with you...I'm looking forward to it...
but because of this...please
bear with me for now
How lovely...good boy~ good boy~