5. Wild sex in the
hills under the moon
Hey sex
Keep up, we'll be
at the top soon
Come on, come on, come on
You're already panting
at this level.
A man can't keep up with me in my girlish
state... [00:38.97]I'm usually too lazy
The wind at night is so pleasant
Do you want to rest your feet?
[00:45.29]Look, there's a place to rest.
There are chairs too,
sit down and rest
Then I'll have to
sit on your knee...
Give me a hug
Come on, give me a hug
How many times do you want me to say it
when I say I want you to hug me, you idiot?
That's very reassuring
What's wrong? It's
too dark to see?
You're just saying that, but you're
already touching your breasts
I only said you could hug me, but I didn't
give you permission to touch my breasts
Don't apologize all the time
If you want to apologize, don't
touch them in the first place
Your hands are so hot
your breath on my ear is so nice
Ears...one more time...
breasts too...can touch...
Do you like it better in
its current girlish form?
I'm comfortable leaning on you... [04:25.21]I'm
comfortable committing myself to you
Touch more...breasts...put
your hands under your clothes
Yes...that's it...
Can I turn to your side
We are the ones who
dwell in the night
I can see your
face so clearly oh
A look of lust that makes
me want to bully you
Look...you're hitting
me down there
You've got a hard-on already.
Can't stand the
mountain top anymore?
My waist isn't moving...it's
your fault...you made me...
I'm going to get wet... [07:17.00]
I'm going to take my panties off
You just...do what you like
There you go, let's do it
I'm going to...sink my waist
So big...
It's so warm inside...so hot
want to move already?
If you're in too much of a hurry,
the transformation will be undone
You don't want to be
crushed by me either
Come on in
Coming in...
back inside me now
Come on, move, I
want you to move
I want to be fucked by you
Soak me with your venom
So hard...deep down being...
so small...so big down there...
being attacked...so majestic...
before in your flat
you were staring at my bottom
and blowing up, right?
You've been holding back, haven't you?
[10:05.14] So have I...
been holding back...
Just blowing makes
me so happy...
I want to dwell on this
feeling for a while longer...
I've been...wanting
you to come in here
Sure enough...crossing
paths with you...the best!
Stick your tongue
out and suck me...
So happy...suck me a
little longer...so good...
look...these are your favorite
breasts...touch them...
That's right...when they move,
they rock around, right?
I see you look like you
want to touch them...
It's a little bit smaller
this way, but it still shakes
You can grab it too, right?
It's also big enough
to hold your bottom
It's so comfortable...so...so
comfortable
Wait...slow down...
going...going to go
inside me...is it
that comfortable
I told you not to apologize
I love that you're so intent on
craving me...on violating me
You're so desperate for me,
you make me feel so good
That's right, isn't it?
I'm embarrassed to be
affirmed by you so bluntly...
I can't believe I'm able to take you, who
is invulnerable to all kinds of drugs
Is it because I'm beautiful?
Did you call me "cute"?
How can you talk to your
master like that, you bastard?
Are you teasing me?
Are you? Do you really
think I'm cute?
Not just to make fun of me...
That...don't stop at the waist
Don't just touch
your boobs...move!
That's it...
Uterus...being pushed
up one by one...
So deep...so comfortable...
What did you just...say?
That's what you just said...
that
that's what...say it again...
cute...
Say it again...
What's wrong...my chest is so
warm...it's so uncomfortable
Say it again...say it again
I like you...I think
you're cute too...
your expressions, your very
existence, are so cute
You look so tempting,
but you can't eat
It's hard for me to eat...
I want to be with you more,
to stay with you more
I want to hear you
say I'm lovely
Come on, say it
I'm so happy...
Please give me...your warmth
So good...I want it so bad
wanting your...hot cum
like impregnating a
teenager...cum inside me...yes
Stupid...who wants
to have your baby
Don't be so self-absorbed...
cum out...cum out...come on
Going for it...going for it...
Going for it...
so hot~