6. Sleeping peacefully on
the hill under the moon
Is it all coming out?
So, that's enough
What a shy face
You want to sleep on my
chest without any worries?
It's the first time I've ever taken on the form
of a demon while being plugged in like this
Wrapping you tightly
with spider silk
so that you can't pull
it out again for a while
Come on, your body will get cold too
if you're in the mountains like this
I'll hold you...
[01:49.07]lean over
What? You're still shy about being
pinned by your breasts now?
Your ears are turning
red...I'll take it!
Come on, you can put
your face on it too
You can be as
pampered as you like
The long beard is sticking
to my breasts, it tickles
I'll have to shave it
off when I get back
Is it warm?
Me too...it's warm
Your dick and body are like
covered in gooey semen
It's both annoying...and
blissful at the same time
It's a beautiful night
to see the moon
I didn't notice it at all
All I can think about is you
I'm twisting my waist a little
I'll give you a break
When you want to move, you
can move as much as you want
It's so nice
To be honest...as a demon I...
I don't know what to do when I'm
making out with a human like this...
being told "I like
you" or something
It's pretty weird when
you think about it
Do I have a crush on you?
I don't know
I don't really want to admit it
Like other monsters, I
have contempt for humans
I think humans are a
bunch of lowlifes
Even now I still think so
So, you and I are not equals
If you admit that you
and I are equal...
it would feel like an acknowledgement
of the human way of being
Hey, don't bite the nipple
Am I overthinking this?
You have a lot of nerve to
tell your master what to do
Hug~
I'll squeeze you to
death with my breasts
Wrap you in happiness and
send you to that world
Hold~
So warm
You, breathe well
What if I really die
That's why I said
it's okay, dummy
You're a real pain in the ass
I don't hate him or anything
I've said before that feeling
your breath makes me feel at ease
You can hold me tight too
It's not as important
as reassuring you
By the way, I'll lick your ears
If you like my breasts...
Suck or lick...whatever you like
Ah, I almost let you fall off
when I relaxed a little bit
Okay, okay, okay... so you don't
fall off while you're in a daze
I've wrapped you in spider silk
so that you won't escape tonight
I'll never let you leave me
Can you feel it?
tickling you
because you look like
you have weak ears
I'm sleepy but I still want
to do something to you
And I want to touch it again
The human body is fragile
and grows old quickly
and the thoughts of the
heart can easily change
Isn't it better not to
have a relationship
Even then I want
it, I must have it
I want to be warm now too I want
you to hold me by your own will
Want you to live
so that I can be happy
Then I'll be happy
You and the world...are
not quite the same
I'm just a part of
this world as a demon
In the 200 years
that I've been alive
I have asked myself many
times if I am happy
but the answer has
always been no
When it comes to happiness, it only
exists in connection with the world
or rather...with other people
I think though...you being
human...that's annoying
but I now...also
feel that I'm happy
I want to be touched
on my back too
back...yes...with my fingers
It's itchy...but I like it
being stroked on the back
like this...I like it so much
Let's sleep together
And then...it's nice to have the
same morning with you again...