peichisan personal handiwork
Welcome, little brother~
This shop, a custom shop that will follow the customer's
preferences and provide the appropriate world view
This time, my brother
has a reservation.
The appointment is.
Heh heh~ I guess there's
nothing wrong with that
To cater to your taste, I'll
try to cosplay this time too
Hmph~ How about
that, does it fit?
Let me play with you
today instead of [Alice]
I'll charm you
So. I'll explain the details of the shop to
you next, so let's get started right away
The purpose of your brother's visit to
this shop is, of course, [to ejaculate]
It's completely different
from a person masturbating
but a comfortable masturbation
under the instructions of a girl
It's like that, right?
It's okay, don't worry~
I'll give you what you want
But I won't let
you cum so easily
Because, that's not fun
So, I'll get my brother
to play along with me
It's a very simple
game, don't worry
So, I'll explain the
rules to you later
Having said that, I'm not thinking
of anything particularly difficult
I'll just make my brother anxious and
increase the desire to ejaculate
But if you keep listening like this, your brain
might break down comfortably, so be careful~
The script was already decided when I
was asked to help with masturbation
I'll just have to go for it!
So, it's getting late,
let's get started!
No matter how many times I reach the edge of
ejaculation, I will not be allowed to ejaculate
I'll give you a taste
that you can't wait for
So please pay attention and
listen to my voice from now on
Now start jerking your cock to
the speed of this [fap fap]
Make sure you follow
the speed of the
[fap fap]
Too slow or too fast is considered a violation
and will not give you a comfortable ejaculation
If you get to the point where you can't help but ejaculate,
you must not slow down the speed of jerking off either
Only the strength of the grip
on the cock can be reduced
and then adjust while
trying to hold back
If you get it, turn
on the initial speed
If you're a brother, you can
still do this easily, right?
I'd rather say I'm impatient and
want to start jerking off sooner~?
But, of course, this
is also forbidden~
You can't start jerking
off until I say so!
So, let's get started!
Hey, you have to do it
at this speed, okay?
Let's do it!
[Koshikosh] You hear that?
As long as this goes on,
brother can't stop oh.
Depending on my mood, make
you cum repeatedly inch stop
It's okay, you'll have the most comfortable
ejaculation waiting for you at the end.
So, just jerk your dick hard~
How about that? [06:23.20]How's that? [06:23.20]You're so anxious
about not being able to control your own speed, aren't you?
But if this goes on forever,
you'll never be able to resist!
I think you're still
in a good position now
It's going to be more than that, so stay
tuned! [06:45.24]There's more to come!
How do you like to be bullied?
Want to be abused?
Or do you like your penis to be
repeatedly stopped over and over again?
I can help you with
any kind of play!
But, for now, you need
to focus on your cock!
It's going to be fun~
It's still early
Just keep doing it as long
as you can hear [shikushiku]
What's wrong? Your face
You're not saying that you're
used to this speed, are you?
no shame, this speed
is still easy for you
anxious? [09:45.91] wishing
you could go faster?
I don't have a problem, but
don't regret it, brother
Can I go back after speeding
up in a place like this?
Yes, then ask me to help
you increase your speed
Come on, repeat after me
[Cocky Shikon Shikon,
please be more intense]
Here, you try it
I can't help it, brother, I've shown you mercy
at first, but I'm still letting me bully you
I can't help it, from now on,
the speed is going to increase
I was going to keep this speed up and
let you get a little more anxious
But since it's my brother's
request, I'm going to speed up
It's the second stage of Shikon
Shikon that you've been waiting for
Before this I didn't know how fast this
stage of Shikon Shikon would be either
You're a fool to
ask for more speed
That stupid brother,
enjoy the pleasure
No more mercy for you
I can't do it without jerking
off as hard as I can!
No rewards if you ejaculate without
permission and disobey my orders
If you don't ejaculate comfortably, it
might turn out to be a bad ejaculation
How about your brother's favorite costume?
Is it cute?
Still think it's... Scary?
[13:04.48] Both of them are right
I'll give my brother the
most blessed ejaculation ~
And I'll bully you to
death in the process
And make you feel scared
Cum in shame at the end
and have your head broken
I feel like I've been jerking off
less and less since a while ago?
Although the grip
is said to be free
But it's so early in the
morning, you can't let it out!
You're so cool when you're cool, and you're
so messed up when your cum is coming out
increase the force of your jerking off,
that's the manly thing to do, let me see it
Then maybe I'll speed up
my shikushiku for you
I'm already working hard, but
I told you at the beginning
this is to make brother anxious ejaculation
when the brain is completely broken 。。。。。
Ejaculation management oh
So it seems that brother
is used to this speed
come on let's get the
koshikosh speed up!
Let's move on to the
creamiest of ejaculations~
Brother, make sure you
work hard, I'll be happy
Love being chastised by girls dressed
like this, instructions for cocks
perverted jitterbug brother
Enjoy my [17:00.20]loving
reprimand
Okay, Shikeshik is
picking up speed
It's necessary for you to
cum as much as you want
It will make you feel good
or something, how can it be
even though you already
know I'm screwed
Now all I can do is jerk
my cock as hard as I can
because you're trying to hold back cumming,
so maybe you're doing all you can?
no matter what, unauthorized
ejaculation is forbidden
I'll be watching, come on
By the way, brother, masturbation like this is completely
different from what you normally do, isn't it?
I'm sure you can't be a normal person
after being ordered around by a girl.
But I still want to look at you,
you're a jitterbug, you can't help it
I can't help it though
If it wasn't for a girl like me, no
one would have done that for you!
Brother, where is the most
sensitive part of your penis?
Is it the rod? The nipple?
Or the urethral opening?
In men, nipples can be pleasurable for some
guys, too. [20:47.22] What about your nipples?
It would be a waste not to bully the
nipples while we have the chance
but brother will follow my
instructions and bully the nipples
I want to bully you even more,
come on, come on come on
little cock is about to
cum, about to cry out?
clearly a boy
wanting to cum so
badly out of my cock
but I can't yet
I want you to thank me for
all the help I've given you
and want to bully my
poor brother even more
That's all that matters
Come on, you repeat what I say
[Thank you for
picking on my penis]
Try saying it
It's very cute, thank you
I can't cum even if I want to, but it
would be nice to be ordered to do so
Yes, I can... I'll make
my cute brother cum...
It's hard to top such
a fast shiko shiko
I'll let you cum, but you have to
hold back until I give you permission
Happy to start
jerking off again~
I've tried so hard to
hold back until here
I've had to look like I'm about
to cum a few times though
It must have been an illusion, because
my brother held on well until here
It's hard to be scolded by
me all the time, isn't it?
but I keep scolding like that and
my brother's penis seems to like it
Ah~ this brother really likes to be
bullied by girls, like a jitterbug
You must be very happy too
You're jerking off so fast, you're about
to reach your ejaculation threshold
But not yet, listen
to my instructions
Do you really understand? [26:48.42] Do you really understand?
I'm the reason why my brother is working so hard!
If you keep this up, you're going
to be the ultimate ejaculation dick
If you don't make an effort, you'll fail
if you're not bullied to this extent!
So let's engrave the pleasure
of cumming in your mind
Being bullied into cumming
by a girl younger than you
then, finally.
if you hold back for 30 seconds,
you'll cum in a puffy way
then you will be given
the permission to do so
That's great, the ejaculation you've
been waiting for will be ready soon
I'm glad I've endured it so long
Maybe the patience
juice is overflowing
Forgive you, come on,
you've been patient so far
Finally, I'm going to count down
to 3 seconds and I'm going to cum!
A BIUBIU reward for those
who have held out this far
It's sad to be a man though
but I'm really happy to
have you playing with me
So, the countdown is coming!
In this state, I think you're
going to BIU BIU right away
Cum out!
0!
Yes 0 Oh, brother
That's it?
Can you shoot more?
After all this patience, that
must be more than enough
Let's spit out all the cum
we've accumulated for so long
Come on, come on
Hey, it's all out...
Good job, brother
Not bad for putting up with it
for so long, are you tired?
Well, there's still a little
time left, so rest up brother
I'll tidy up a little... once again,
I've worked hard... brother...
peichisan personal handiwork