Episode 1 Uncle play
☆On the way home from school, when Konomi sees "Ojisan",
she energetically runs up to him.
She jumps into the arms of "Ojisan" with a charming appearance.
(00:01) Ah,
I forgot my homework today and got scolded by my teacher...
I honestly told him that I forgot my homework, so why are you angry with me, teacher? Hmmm?
"Oh! "I'm an uncle!" Hey! "Uncle!" "Run!" "Ehehe, I got stuck."
☆ Konomi clings to the "uncle"
who cares about the eyes around him.
With a friendly smile on his face,
he brazenly tried to make me carry my luggage.
(00:32) Well, uncle is uncle.
Mother's younger brother... is it a cousin? Oh, I don't know. Well, after all, he's a lot older than me.
You've got a beard, and you're strong, aren't you?
What? "No, indoor shoes." It's heavy.
☆ Konomi puts pressure on the "uncle" with a hateful tone.
Seeing the “uncle”
cringing, he relaxes his expression with satisfaction.
(01:02)……Oh! "Are you sure?" If you treat me like that,
you'll get hurt, okay? Look, look, an old man sticks to a girl like this
and stretches it under his nose...it's dangerous.
Fushinshader, or Papakatsu? "Because you're going to get arrested, uncle...
Nihihi, thank you!" "You're always not honest."
You can't do that with her, can you?
☆Suddenly, Konomi's face distorts with a disgust
that doesn't match her age.
There is an old hut ahead of the line of sight, and although it is not very strong,
it pulls on the arm of the "old man" with a force that makes it impossible to say yes or no.
(01:39) Well, it might be "Betsuri Yuu" without her, but... Look, uncle.
Can you see it? The usual hut, the old little hut on the way home from school that no one knew was there.
Shall we go together? ……Ah, like that again, I pretend to hate it, but even if I pull my arm, I don’t try to resist.
Ehe, did you come? "Is your lover a lover?" "I'm not here, so it's okay if I do something bad or naughty...♪"
☆When
the rusty door closes, Konomi takes a deep breath and turns around.
In the lower abdomen, male
reproductive organs that should not have existed
were showing their ferocious shapes on the cloth of the trousers.
(02:32) …… Gachan ♪ Nihihi, the door has closed ♪ In the dimly lit hut in the evening,
my uncle and I are alone …….
Yo♪ Uncle becomes a girl, and I become an uncle.
It's a very fun uncle play♪☆ Konomi walks up to "uncle".
Her gait is unsteady,
but her feverish eyes tell her that her swollen penis won't let her go.
(03:00) No way~?
"I won't allow you to hate or run away, and I can't." Is your uncle
a girl? "There's no way you can beat an adult uncle, right?" In front of my...mmm, uncle♪,
there's a piece of cloth in front of my trousers,
and it's puffed up like an adult male doing naughty things...ohhhhhh・Po ♪ Wow,
erotic ♪ ☆ Konomi's voice,
which reminds me of a middle-aged man, begins to seep into her attitude,
and her pretend play takes on a sense of authenticity.
I feel
a damp breath on my flank being hugged,
dulling the thoughts of "old man".
(03:46) Hmm, hehe♪ Hey, hey, hey, my uncle's cock is startled♪ He's trembling,
but you stare at me like that, and you're frustrated that you haven't been loved by your boyfriend,
can you? See, when it comes to these thighs,
even though they're wearing pants, they're smooth and whippy ♪ Ah
♪ It's not enough just stroking them ♪ Ha...
Hug me... I'll stroke you with my penis♪ I'll do it for you♪
☆ Konomi moves her hips with a vivid sigh and rubs her penis.
Supporting my weight with my toes and changing the strength of my unsteady pressure,
there were sultry voices mixed in here and there.
(04:33) Whew......
uh, hoo ♪ uh, uh, fu, uh, huh ♪ huh ♪ huh huh huh uh huh ♪ hehe he was pressed against my thigh Well,
the shape of the man's penis, the shape of the man's penis,
the shape of the neck that spreads out like a kana ♪ gi gui
gui ♪ and the umbrella with the neck that spreads out...
hmm, huh ♪ Pukupuku ♪ and the swollen back muscles ♪ Zudon ♪ , um ♪ fat, meat pole too...
all under the uncle's trousers, under the girl's panties with Bear's print,
bakin ♪ bakin ♪ erect ♪ uncle cock ……N, Phew♪☆Konomi speaks in an unnaturally low and muffled voice.
More than anything else, the protruding penis conveys a sense of truth
that cannot be dismissed by childish fantasies.
(05:36) Cutie-chan, huh♪ Cutie-chan, huh, huh, huh♪
Why is my uncle's cock
getting so big that my panties are cramped? (06:06) Right now,
the old man is with the dog, oh, hoho♪ Haa...
ah, ♪ the dog is hanging on the table leg and so on♪ ♪Wow,
wow, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh ♪ After the dog squealed
and the dog left ♪ Phew ♪ The place where the dog's penis
hit me was sticky ♪ White and sticky soup
stuck to me ♪
☆ From the mouth of a lively girl,
blatant and depressing animal lust flows out one after another.
The situation itself creates an extra immoral excitement.
(06:52) That soup, uh, hmm ♪ My cock is so hot
♪ I'm getting an erection...
eh eh eh eh eh eh eh eh ♪ when the excitement is at its peak,
ni ♪ It pops out from the hole at the tip of its cock♪
♪ I'm so energetic ♪
What's more, when you pour a lot of that healthy sticky stuff into the girl's crotch hole ♪ Pyuru pyuru pyuru ♪ Pyup pyup pyuru ♪ ♪ A healthy baby is born.
It's coming♪ Nihihi♪☆ Konomi spits out words that are filled with horrifying libido, in a romantic tone that feels like a confession in a way.
Narcissistic with the words makes the penis warp
again.
(07:46) Hmm... fufu ♪ fu, uhhh ♪ That's why ♪ Ojisan too...
Cutie, come visit me with an erection cock in your crotch hole ♪ Pyuppyu, nntsu ♪ I want to see the white slime ♪ What's going on ♪ Nfu, fufufu, kuuuuu...
um, ♪ Ah, confessing while pushing the cock ♪ How sexy it is, ah...
my cock is getting stiff and hard... erect I, hee hee♪☆Konomi looks like she's no longer looking at "Ojisan" even though she's talking to her.
He rubs his penis with minimal efficient movements and exhales intermittently.
(08:22)
Huh ♪ Huh ♪ Thighs are so smooth ♪ They're so smooth that I can't take a cock ♪ Bim, um,
um ♪ N, um ♪ Tight on my soft thighs ♪ I stick my big cock to it, rub it, rub it, Fua, um ♪ Uh~~...
chuki ♪ (08:48) Haha, ah, um ♪ Huh, uh...~ ♪ Thick thigh ♪ Thigh ♪ U, fu ♪ Slurp, ♪ Slurp, hm ♪ Slurp, slap, slap ♪ I'm moving forward, haaaa... manko ♪ manko manko mankooo...
fufufufu ♪ h, Um ♪ Like this, like this, do, nn, kk ♪ Insert the tip of the cock, chupo chupo, kupokupo, kugu ♪
Haa,
ha, ♪ Echi ♪ Echi ♪ Echiechiechiechi~……Uuuuuu♪☆ After a strong convulsion,
Konomi speaks to "Ojisan" as if she's come to her senses.
. However, the high fever did not go away, and a lullaby tone appeared in his voice.
(09:33) ……U, ♪ ♪ Oh,
oh ♪ …… Ah, Ha, I'm sorry ♪ Uncle, I think I was concentrating too much on my cock ♪ I'm sorry, cutie-chan, Echi ♪ Erection cock on my thighs, Kakukaku ♪ Goshi, goshi,
huh ♪ Sorry, huh ♪ My thighs are rubbing against my cock, Uncle Kintama ♪ Bubbly ♪ Bubbly , oh oh
♪ gg ♪ gg gu ♪ come on ♪ ♪ in the middle of the balls
♪ ehhhhhhh ♪ bang ♪ I'm sorry for making my work heavy Whew♪
☆ Konomi continues to be frightened and clumsy in order not to reach her climax.
The cheeks,
which were originally strongly reddish, were dyed even more red with shame, and the scrotum was boiled. (10:22) Ah...
it's embarrassing♪ Embarrassing, hmm♪ Hmmm, I'm going straight to the cock♪ I'm going straight, ruh, huh♪ But, hmmm♪ My uncle's heart Seeds ♪ It looks like it's going to spill out, so I'm hesitant...
I'm hesitant ♪ Ah, ah, ♪ I slowly shake my hips, fu, uh ♪ It's embarrassing to be seen by a cutie, but Feelings, nnnnnn♪
☆ Contrary to the situation,
Konomi's finger calmly extends to the crotch of "Uncle".
Konomi smiled at the weak voice that leaked out when she suddenly stroked her bulge.
(11:00) Hmm, heh ♪ But man...
I want you to feel good too, huh ♪ Look here, touch the front of your trousers...
"Hyan ♪" is so cute My voice came out ♪ Ah, ah ♪ From a while ago,
the uncle started masturbating using the cutie's thighs ♪ At the zipper of the trousers that bulged out ♪ Once more, huh Nade,
nn, kuuu♪ fufu♪☆ Konomi uses her girlish cuteness as a base to arouse the excitement of the 'uncle'.
Pretend to be innocent and grope the crotch.
(11:42) That's right ♪ cutie-chan
too, uh, yeah ♪ I'm going to bang ♪ You're the uncle who just happened to have a plump and thick cock, but look, you see, the fingers are girl's squishy ♪ Voluptuous ♪ Round fingers...
♪ (12:07) That's why, she's like an innocent relative, a girl who doesn't know anything about naughty things, but has a perfectly round butt ♪ flat breasts ♪ full body ♪ But, "Uncle,
what's this?", I poked your erection through your pants, thumped it ♪ Pinched it with my fingertips and rubbed it lightly ♪ That's what it is ♪ If you do something...
yes, you'll get an erection~ ♪ Kana's grown up again? "So cute♪"
☆ Konomi asks "Uncle" to masturbate like himself.
Inviting you down the path of depravity with a provocative voice that exposes your sexual desire.
(12:49) Huh, hm♪ It's okay♪ It's okay...
Even if you're an old man, if you're a cutie, you'll be rubbed on your dick♪Eh,
eh, huh~~~♪ Right now I'm going to ejaculate~~~♪ I mean, I'm going to start fiddling around with my panties,
so let's play pranks on my crotch together with my cutie♪ Let's get comfortable♪
☆ Konomi reprimands the "uncle"
who tried to start male masturbation.
Instead, it was presented in a deeply humiliating way,
If you follow the instructions, you can no longer get out of this "play".
(13:19) Come on, stretch out your arms on the delicious bulge between your crotch...
Ah, come on♪ Isn't that right? That's because it's a boy's masturbation ♪ A cute girl with such plump thighs is definitely a girl...
If you stroke Kuri-chan with your palms and fingers, saying, "Good girl, good girl~♪"
☆
Konomi looks at the masturbation of "uncle" while speaking of naked sexual circumstances and sticky kindness.
The heat accumulated in the penis makes the rod go up and down.
(14:13) Good boy ♪ Good boy ♪ Swiping Kuri-chan from the top of her pants ♪ You're good at it ♪ You're able to masturbate by yourself, that's great It feels so good~♪ If you're a penis,
you'll be able to tell the part of your neck that's sharp♪When you rub the step, your spine will shivers
and you'll say, "Huh~~~~~~~~" ♪ ♪ I'm constantly teasing you ♪ (14:55) My uncle is also with me ♪ Every morning, once in the bathroom
♪ Secretly once in the bath ♪ Before going to bed, once in the futon
♪ Uncle's cock swells up ♪ I play with it ♪ But when the stick of my cock becomes thicker ♪ I rub the thick flesh of my neck ♪ I rub it...
wow ♪ A lot of it comes out... The trash can in my uncle's room is full of semen that accidentally jumped out of a tissue
and a cutie's pussy♪
☆ Konomi resumes the movement of her waist to comfort herself.
I feel like I'm about to be swayed by the "uncle" that I feel in my whole body, and I strengthen my arms that hug me.
(15:41) Nfu, uh, yeah ♪ Excited...
I'm so excited, Kana ♪ As soon as I found out that Uncle was thinking about you and was doing it, uh,
uh ♪ Hurry up It's gone ♪ It's okay ♪ Try to be stronger ♪ Raise your voice more, Kuri-chan feels good ♪ Tell your uncle ♪ Scrub ♪ An-an ♪ An-an ♪ ♪
(16:16) ah, ah...
♪ ah, no, it's too naughty ♪ um, um ♪ I want to mix with the old man too, fu, uh ♪ Look at me like this, hugging me tight with my heel floating, cute
I put my weight on the child's whip thighs, uh, ugh ♪ Oh, cute girl's masturbation is intense,
♪ Tight thighs ♪ Grinding, grimming, um ♪ Pushing the uncle's cock, ku , uu ♪ hmm ♪ I'm not going to lose ♪
☆ The slippery cloth
rubbed against the penis with the previous juice, and Konomi's moaning voice was mixed.
I unintentionally spill saliva, slurp it up and smile.
(16:59), uh
♪ already ♪ Ponzugabi, Nugu, Fu ~ tsu ♪kuku, uh, nu, na, nu, tip, huh.
♪Glass head...it's slippery and rubbing, hey, hey♪ Gui♪ Gui♪ It's getting bigger...
Uh♪ Fufu♪ Uh, huh♪ Cutie is also slimy♪ Kana that's been doing it♪ Ehe, hehe, njuru ♪ Ah, drool ♪ Kukcha, ha, ah... Ehehehe♪☆ Konomi suddenly stiffens her body and flatters her flushed cheeks.
With a distorted smile, I fixed my eyes on "Ojisan".
Arms that hug tightly, wheezing breathing tell the climax coming.
(17:38)
Oh! …… Haa ♪ Ha, ah, ha …… ♪ Oh,
I'm sorry ♪ I surprised you, Kana, uh
♪ Hey, cutie ♪ Ah, you know ♪ Never, never from Uncle Kintama Uh,
huh ♪ Because the hot semen has started ♪ It's going up inside the cock with a gurgling sound, so I'm not listening, but ng, gu ♪
☆ Konomi pesters "uncle" to climax at the same time as himself.
Contrary to the content, an innocent smile and a lively voice create a helplessly obscene atmosphere.
(18:12) ……I'll come with my uncle, Kana ♪ Nihihi ♪ Haha ♪ I breathed heavily and rubbed my penis hard, umm ♪ It was full of slimy From the cock hole,
pyuppyuu, pyuuuu~♪ I want you to leak a lot of muddy masturbation juice♪
☆
Konomi begins to move her hips even faster after receiving the approval of "Ojisan".
I
pushed my crotch so much that my thighs were distorted, and let out a rough snort.
(18:44) …… All right ♪ You're a good boy ♪ All right,
you're going to leak a lot, too ♪ Put your cutie's legs firmly between your knees...
crotch, tight, U, fu ♪ From now on, ah, ah ♪ N ♪ The shape of the cock that makes you feel good ♪ You're feeling it firmly, Kana ♪ N, fu ♪ The cutie, too, stroking it...
wow ♪ It's hot, it's jumpy, it's naughty ♪ Uncle's waist, woo ♪ Randomly starts moving, wow,
uh, uh ♪
(19:29)
Uh ♪ Phew ♪ Phew ♪ Fu, uu ♪ Muchimuchi thighs, Echi ♪ Echi, Echiechi, N, N~♪ Coming ♪ Come, Ruu,
Naaa ♪ Thighs by chance
It's rubbed, it's loosened,
teeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
Gyu, gyu,
fu, uuuu♪
☆ Konomi
climaxes as she rubs her penis once.
Even in the pleasure of turning the whites of my eyes, I can't take my eyes off the writhing expression of "uncle".
(19:56) Oh, ah, hah ♪ Get up and come ♪ Uh, wooh ♪ Oh, oh oh oh
♪ Inside my cock, it's hot enough to burn me, nn, nn♪ Otsuyu ♪
Uhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
The cock, oh... it's so thick♪ I'm so fat♪
(20:19)
Igu ♪ Cock ♪ Cock ♪ Cock ♪
Kaa, the cutie Kuri-chan haa♪ ♪ I can do it well, ru, I wonder, ah,
nn♪
Are you scared? I can do it, uh, fu ♪, ah ♪ Let's go out with my uncle ♪ I'm going to have a voice and a lot of juice.
… Get out, get out, get out, za, men, get out, er, ru~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
☆ Unbefitting of his age, along with a vulgar voice like that of a middle-aged man,
Konomi shoots out semen one after another.
I also forgot to suck up the saliva
flowing out of the corners of my mouth.
(20:49)
……Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa ♪
Get out,
get out, get out, eh ♪ Ngu ♪
Dobyu ♪ Dobyu ♪ Dobyu, woo ♪ oo ♪ oo ♪ I let out a dirty old man voice, fu-gu ♪ again Ah~~~~♪
☆ When the climax ends,
Konomi regains her original innocent tone and smiles mischievously.
However, the heat of the penis does not cool down, and semen spouts out intermittently.
(21:19) Uh ♪ Uh...
fuu~ ♪ Oh ♪ Oh ♪ It felt so good ♪ Eh? When you ejaculate, it's over playing uncle ♪ You've already finished playing Pyuppyyu, right? Also,
if you stretch your toes out ♪ ♪ Woo ♪ ♪ The soup left in your erection will come out ♪ Doesn't it look amazing? Praise me.
It's great that you ejaculated a lot♪ Say, stroke me, hehehe♪
☆When I think about it, Konomi whispers in the ear of "Uncle".
Without waiting for those words, the penis had already expanded.
(22:13) Oh, I feel uncomfortable with my pants.
It's dirty because it's soup made from the cock, it's kind of warm, and it smells weird...
Ah, uncle. Lend me your ears♪(22:35)……Hello♪ I'm an old man♪ Kuri-chan is lively,
it felt good Kana♪ In my panties, sometimes the soup sticks to my penis, it's disgusting♪ It's dirty as it is Go home with your panties...
let's exchange them like usual ♪ Panties ♪ Swap uncle and cutie's panties and wrap them around your penis...
but when your penis gets big, you get stuck , I can't wear it ♪ When I have to do a little bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of