Episode 3 Baby play
☆ Konomi caught a cold from her "uncle" because of what she did the other day.
However, the symptoms are very mild, and he points out that he is forced to rest. (00:01)……Ah, the thermometer rang. Hope your fever goes down! ……Uhhh, it's not going down~.
Well, even though I promised to hang out with my friends, my mom told me not to do it while I had a fever...
☆ Just when Konomi gave an off-topic remark, the next moment, a smile appeared on her stomach.
Suddenly pretending to cough on purpose and clinging to "Ojisan".
(00:27) Hey, uncle, I wonder why it's giving me a cold. I just poked my cock in and banged ♪ Pyuppyu~♪. Originally, the uncle invited me with a cheeky feeling, right? But why am I... ah, that's right.
came up with a good thing! "Fufufu... ugh." Hoho, Hoho. Kyu, it seems that the fever has suddenly risen. Uh, wow~, it's Gourujii~! "Uncle, come here, come closer, bring your face closer." Oh, here we come. Hey, you're here...
Hello, it's an uncle♪☆Konomi, who brings his face closer, becomes the usual "uncle play" and asks for a caress to the local area with a sweet voice.
(01:23) Hmmm...Hey, cutie♪ Uncle, I caught a cold and have a fever...No, I have a forehead,
but can you see it♪I'm wearing a futon On the body, below the navel ♪ Huh? Kana, what's inside, moko ♪ Lift up the futon, ah ♪ Look at me...
twitch ♪ twitch ♪ twitch ♪ This thing goes up and down like a living thing, muhihi ♪ It's twitching over there , Uncle is very painful ♪ Cutie is a kind girl, so when you get excited, you make it easy ...
♪
☆ Konomi deftly lifts her hips while lying on her back and rubs the bulge on the hand of the "uncle".
Letting out an annoyed breath, it desires direct stimulation. (02:17) Flipping over the futon...
wow♪ My pajama pants are so stretched out in my crotch! But if I try to take it out like that, the cloth will get caught~... Mmho ♪ Oh yeah, uhhh ♪ When I hold my head down, the hard stick bows down, huh ♪ That's it ♪ Put the trousers and underpants together T-Aha♪ Sliding, slipping~......
Beep♪
☆ The penis that was taken out is sharp and the tip is already wet with honey. Konomi swings the rod playfully, wraps herself in a towel and exhales in ecstasy.
(03:01) Kuhoho♪ Playing naughty things with the uncle's lower abdomen♪ A fat, fat, hot penis♪ Well,
the moment his pants popped out♪ It was so intense The scent of the male is scattered, and the plump glans and the gouged-out neck are soaked with sweat, and the stuffy erections are soaked in sweat.
, I'm embarrassed to see a cutie look at my raw dick♪ I'm going to leak a little bit of juice Kana ♪ Cutie is drooling and I'm going to go out ♪ (03:51) If I don't get it, my body will get cold and my uncle's cold will get worse ♪ Come on,
let's bring a towel ♪ Muhi ♪ My hands curled up and I approached you ♪ But it would be embarrassing if I was touched From, purupuru ♪ I shake my erection
stick and run away with my selfish cock ♪ So that I can't escape ~ ♪ Gyuu ♪ Ahhh ♪ Ah ♪ Straight meat, ugh guh ♪ With a cutie's towel
handjob, Uguhi ♪ Dirty Ahegao voice and sticky uncle cowper ♪
☆ Konomi stretches her nose and smiles at the pleasant sensation of friction.
The juice squirts out one after another,
and the room fills with a long roar.
(04:41)
Whoa~♪
Ohhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh ohhhhh, old
man, I'm wrapped up in the fluffy fabric of the towel.
Oh ♪ Blood vessels, hmm ♪ Spoiled by a fluffy towel, Fuhya ♪ Ah, uh
♪ You don't have to be so angry ♪ You don't have to work hard and get an erection ♪ Muhihi, hhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
☆Then, Konomi
suddenly spits out words without context and brings her face closer to the chest of "Uncle".
With his free hand, he explores the hem of his clothes and tries to expose the soft skin of the "uncle".
(05:28) Hm... ♪ But if you keep going like this, you'll become dehydrated ♪ N, gu, um ♪ Ha, I need to drink more water and nutrients than my cock is pumping...
… Ah ♪ You look like a cutie, ah, hmm ♪ A girl's breasts produce very nutritious milk ♪ I know an old man ♪ Noo ♪ Cheeks ♪ Because it's a baby
Sometimes it's a lot of chupa chupa ♪ That's why, ah, ah ♪ I'm going to give the uncle baby a lot of cutie milk ♪
☆ Konomi sees that "Uncle's" nipples are already erect and twists her cheeks spitefully.
However, for a short time, I couldn't stand it and munched on the dull luster of the granulation.
(06:16) Raise your upper body lightly, and...
Hey, let's pinch the hem of the upper clothes and turn up the shirt, okay?
Hm ♪ What is this? ♪ I'm in heat,
Kana ♪ Your face and nipples are bright red ♪ Muhihi ♪ That's a perverted child's big nipples, with your uncle's plump lips...
huh, puh ♪
☆ Konomi sucked strongly into her chest for a moment, then released her mouth with an exaggerated noise.
Show the "uncle" who is breathing from the impact,
twisting his tongue in disgust and repeating the suction many times.
(07:15) Jyu, jyu, uu~~♪ chu, chuchu, chumuuu...ppa♪ npaa~naaa~...hehihi♪
sweet♪ cutie's nipples ♪ Bab babu ♪ (07:44) But the milk didn't pop out ♪ cute Ko-chan, I've breastfed you before ♪ ……Ah~, it's my first time ♪ So, look...
Look at your uncle's mouth ♪ He's drooling around his tongue and he's messing around.
Ah ♪ I'm going to fiddle with my cutie's mother's nipples with this kind of naughty tongue movement ♪ How do you know?
Puchuu ♪☆ Konomi looks up at "Uncle" with lustful eyes
while rolling her nipples in her mouth.
It greedily picks around the nipple and softens the entire subcutaneous tissue.
(08:33) mm, ppchuru, nn♪ Ah~,
reru, nn, nn♪ Npichaa ♪ Uaaa~ ♪ Let's put it out? Let's get some milk out ♪ With a wide, rough tongue, let's go ♪ Trace around the perfectly round nipples, Ah
♪ Piccha, Piccha ♪ With the tip of your tongue ♪ Tap the shape of your nipples ♪ I'll fix it for you ♪ Nkuchu, pup, ah ♪ Haaah...
Then I'll massage the areola and nipples together with my lips, and I'll definitely loosen up the mammary glands,
huh ♪ Kupu, mmumyu, mokyu, muhyuu, cchuuu♪
☆But Konomi doesn't forget to shake her own penis and make her point.
I smile enchantedly at the sensation of my penis
standing up and stretching.
(09:37)
Ohhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh Wobin
♪ I
can't stand it, I can't stand it.
Next time, haa♪ light cock stick♪ nigiri♪
nhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Muhihi, hee
hee, hee
hee ♪
☆ Konomi puts her hand on the hand of "Uncle" and leads it to the sweaty scrotum.
The baby talk uttered by the
cat's stroking voice and the scrotum wet with oil make an obscene contrast.
(10:18) There's nothing I can do about it♪
I'll teach you how to properly clean your penis from an uncle baby to a mom with stupid nipples♪Here
you go, stack your hands on top of each other, and go further down ……Hah ♪ Put it on the palm of your hand, tap, tap ♪ Nwahi ♪ Bend your fingers lightly,
moni, moni ♪ hehihi ♪ Big and plump plump whip ♪ No, no, ♪ Seed bags...
Ehihi ♪ Packed with plenty of uncle's seeds, Mowa ♪ Mowa ♪ Sweaty ball bags
♪ I want my mom to clean it ♪ I want you to do it, ♪
☆ Every time a light force is applied to the meat bag, the spine goes numb, and Konomi lets out a rough
snort.
The babbling that is sandwiched between them as if remembering sounds rather disgusting like a middle-aged man's baby play.
(11:17) Pua ♪ kuah, ah ♪ Lightly onigiri,
ugh, ugh ♪ fufu ♪ While doing that, a line of wrinkles running through the bag,
oooo Nn ♪ Kuk ♪ Babu ♪ Wipe off the accumulated sweat and greasy sweat, hii ♪ Wipe, wipe ♪ Ah,
hum, chu ♪ Nbu, pua ♪ Nfu, nfu, nfu ♪ Nfu , fuhihi ♪ Every time I'm taken care of, I'll take care of you
♪
My eyes are upside down, ♪ ♪ ♪
☆Egg-sized testicles leave the owner's will and pulsate powerfully, lighting the depths of Konomi's waist.
Just like Konomi's relieved expression as she chewed on her milk, the epidermis of her scrotum spread loosely on the palm of the "uncle".
(11:55) Oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, my cutie ♪ My dear mother's palm, dehehehe ♪ Doku ♪ Doku doku ♪ Uncle Kintama, oh
♪ It's brave, it's pulsating, mm, kupu, tchururu ♪ Hmmm ♪ When I hold my nipples like this again, oh ho ♪ It's getting heavier and heavier...
Haa Ah ♪ My testicles are getting more and more full with baby juice, babu ♪ Babu babu ♪
☆ Konomi repeatedly pulsates her scrotum and speaks out her desires that are too blatant.
A short, choked voice piled up, and even the color of love appeared in his stagnant eyes.
(12:38) I can understand what a dizzying baby is thinking right now, haha ♪ muhihii... reproductive ♪ reproductive ♪ shove a thick cock into the female's wet hole ♪ sloppy ♪ bururi
A lot of vaginal cum shot ♪ I want to give birth to a baby by pouring my genes into it ♪ Oh, oh ♪ Oh
oh ♪ Hum, puchu, chu, jeuu ♪ Paa ♪ Even though I'm a baby uncle who wants to drink breasts ♪ Being able to make a baby is a wonder~, ehhhhh♪ By the way,
who do you want to give the baby to? Put your mouth on the nipple of "Uncle" and suck it up.
The rhythm of the penis no longer stops, and the buttocks of the words melt away.
(13:35) Kuchu, ppu, ruru, nah ♪ Oh, oh ho ho ♪ oh
♪ Fair ♪ In the middle of the bag, no ho ♪ Scrub the seams Wiping up, huh ♪ Ah, na -na, na -na ♪ Kinta Mata towel dried while sinking with the testicles with the desire to be conceived.
I wonder if it's coming ♪ Muchu, pupu, chuuuu ♪ Nee~tsu ♪ If you put it in your nipple mouth like this, you'll gasp sweetly ♪ I'm so worried about my uncle,
my cock is jerky ♪
☆ Make your waist stiffen once and feel the premonition of climax.
The penis moves up and down without even touching it, and breathing like crawling on the ground clearly expresses the reproductive desire.
(14:28)
No! ? Whew, Whew ♪ Whew,
Whew ♪ Ho, the cock really jumps ♪ I'm like...
The bottom of the testicles, Whew ♪ From, the path of sperm to the cock's bell mouth is straight.
It happened ♪
☆ An atmosphere of immorality created by the unreasonable baby talk and the arrogant attitude of a middle-aged man.
Konomi's penis stubbornly raises his sickle neck, presses the meat rod into the hands of "uncle" and asks for friction.
(14:46) Ah, ah ♪ wait, mama ♪ Let go of that furry-smelling ball,
let your uncle have an erection and take care of him ♪ Don't worry ♪ Hmm fufu ♪ Hurry up ♪ Uncle's cock rod goes up and down ♪ Boom ♪ It's going up and down ♪ I can't squirt seed juice unless I'm breastfeeding my mom ♪ My cock selfishly says,
and he's a male breed cat in his balls Because I'm going to do it ♪ That's why I'm doing a black fat
mara, at my mom's hand,
Nigi, Hihii~♪ Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
☆At
the same time,
Konomi exposed her strong desire to monopolize the nipples of her "uncle".
Tamper with sensitive areas in every possible way.
The bodies of the two react sensitively to stimuli, creating a chain reaction of pleasure.
(15:34) Woo ♪ Woo ♪ I want to get some milk out...
I want to drink milk. Mr. Uh, Ufu ♪ Kukukuku ♪ I can't give it to anything other than my uncle ♪ I reach out, I reach out, my fingers, my fingers,
uhu -kun ♪ , oooo♪ Grasped tightly, heh~♪ Mama's nipples and uncle's cock, guuuu♪ They're tied together with milk♪ milk♪ urging each other, ahhh, hahah, how cute♪☆ Konomi does not forget to order this and that for her own penis while making the chest of "Uncle" covered with saliva.
The pleasant sensation that awaits me in a few moments, and my eyes are already moist, and I have a nice smile on my face.
(16:18) mmhiii♪ oh, oh, my cock won't stop freaking out, babuu ♪ hyu, hmm, flat, puchuru, nchubah♪ Uh ♪ I have to tip more ♪ ah ah ♪ ...
mama ♪ mama ♪ chuu, uu ♪ Make a little with your thumb and forefinger, uncle baby Michimichi ♪ Don't wrap it around the meaty neck ♪ Oh ♪ Oh, ku, it's done, oh ♪ Uha, oh, it's up and down, chukochukochuko ♪ Move it... ♪
☆ The intense sensation of directly rubbing the red peeled mucous membrane,
Konomi endures by sucking on the nipple of "uncle".
Cowper does not stop from the penis.
(17:07)
Ah... ♪ guh, gugu, uu ♪ Kufu~~ ♪ I can breathe, ah ♪
ka, ka, kakka, kakka, gills of potash ♪ Puri ♪ Puri, hei ♪ Turn it over,
Oh, my cock, it's going crazy, u, ng♪ Ka, Ku, Kuaa♪ Stimulate my neck with a little bit, kiki, and a pinch♪ It's too tight, my nipples
already♪
Apuchu, Pechuru, Nba ♪ Amu, chuchu ♪ I can't stand it if I don't take care of my cutie's nipples.
Randomly sucking on the nipple of "uncle".
She appeals for pleasure in a feeble tone,
but her words remain irreverent.
(17:43) chu, chu, chu, chu, picha, pp♪ Oh,
uncle's neck ♪ It's already broken
♪ Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh Scratch a lot, nchubu ♪ ovulation
♪ I have to let you go,
but um, kuchupuu ♪ Heaa ♪ I'm a little bit ♪ I was told, hhya, lucky ♪hi ~~n♪ While crying, ah, guguu, fufuu♪
Cowper juice leaking trickles,
nbuchu, uuuu♪ I've turned into a ywamushi baby Ochinpo uncle...♪
☆ Konomi continues to lick her nipples while pestering her to caress her penis.
The sharp red-black flesh roots and the attitude of claiming to be a baby and seeking consideration are too contradictory
and blasphemous.
(18:25) Haa~~♪ Don't bully me~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ Aaaa♪ Ah,
fuuu♪ Toddler toddling and hochiibabu♪ Even though I want to have a cock,
I'm stuck with my neck all the time, gihi♪ I feel sorry for being bullied♪ Okay, okay♪ Hey, I'll cover it with Mr.
Glans Strike it, heeeeeee♪ Strike it♪ Strike it, muchup, it's soooooo...
and give me some milk, muhihi♪
☆ Konomi wriths her hips and rejoices at the long-awaited stimulation that covers the entire glans.
The roaring voice was nothing more than the sound of air escaping,
and it was hardly audible.
(19:05)
Hyuuu~♪ Hyuuu~♪ Nhyuu♪ This is no good♪
Pukupuku glans ♪ Well,
I'm wrapped in your hand, Nkyuu ♪ Kukyukyu ♪
The smooth glans mucous membrane, hmmo ♪ The cock hole and the back muscles are rubbed together at once, oooooooooooooooooooooooooo♪
Npuhyu ♪ Oh, my butt ♪ Fluffy ♪ Mouth cancer ♪ I'm open,
I'm going to show you ♪ Ah, uh~♪ Ahhh~♪
A cute uncle can't do it~Don't look at the weak glans acme face...♪
☆ Konomi smiles at "Ojisan" with a sulky face with tears and a runny
nose.
The voice that talks about the path to ejaculation makes you feel proud, but the content is the male driven by lust.
(19:43) So, uncle, I'm a baby,
but I'm going to do my best~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ ♪ Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, mama, when the uncle gives a signal, he's messing around
♪ I'm stroking the baby's male glans ♪ Uncle, you know, the nipples are licking hard
I'm doing it, so I can't talk to you♪ Nnn♪
Well, then...
let, eh, no♪
☆ Konomi presses her lips against the nipple of "uncle" at the same time as the hand that wraps around the glans is filled with strength.
The sound of the tongue and nipple intertwining becomes louder, and the two climb to the climax.
(20:23)
Nchu, chubu, chuuu, nn, nnnn~♪
Kick, the glans is rubbing, nchumuu♪ Ahchui♪ Amu, nmu, nreluru♪
Hmm, I, Igu♪ Mumyu, Nchuuu♪
Kintama's slimy skin, aaa♪ 　It sticks perfectly to the testicles.
Ppu hoo ♪ Push it out, uh, churu, bufu ♪ Ta, seeds ♪ Seed juice on mom's pussy,
nnn ♪
Buryuburyu♪ A heavy seeding sound resounds, ryu...
chuuuuu♪☆ The palms of the hands crush the glans, and the lips crush the nipples, and Konomi and the "uncle" reach ecstasy.
Konomi sucks up her nipples as if she were really breast milk
and shoots out semen from her loose urethra.
(21:01) No,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no! Mir from the hole, kuu, nchuchuchu♪ N, ah♪
Mama is going to give milk too, the old man squeezes his nipples with his lips, ugh, ugh ♪
Igu, Igu, guguguu, nmuchu♪ Miyu, Kutsu♪ Kupchu, Kuppu♪
miyuku miyuku miyu ku
☆ Only the sound of the penis pulsing strongly, the sound of the semen being shot, and the sound of sucking the nipple resound in the room.
The occasional wheezing tells the deadly depth of pleasure.
(21:41)
……chuuuuuu, chuu, chuu, puchuuuu♪ N, kuhi♪ Get out, ru, huhuu♪
Oh, oh ♪ Mama ♪ Maa ♪ Well, it's still milk ♪
Boobs ♪ Chin, po, chu, chu chu, chu ♪ Oh oh ♪ Osuki milk ♪
Plenty, milk, chuuuu……♪
☆ Konomi sweetly recounts the pleasure of ejaculation, but does not try to stop her tongue crawling on the chest of "Uncle".
Even ridiculing his own foolishness, he enjoys the trembling that remains in his meat rod.
(22:04) Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh If you ask your mom
to rub it,
the seeds will come out differently than if you rub it yourself.
Let's do it ♪ After all, uncle, your nipples are ticking ♪ When you roll with the tip of your tongue ~, ro, le le ♪ Look ♪ You have a cute voice,
oh, hoo ♪ I'm a big cock ♪ I'm going to do the leftover milk ♪ I'm going to do it ♪
Babu ♪ Babu Babu ♪ Chuu, chuuu ♪
☆ Konomi,
who has been exhausted by ejaculation on top of fever, is suddenly attacked by sleepiness.
Konomi begins to take a deep breath, leaving an embarrassing smile on the panicked "uncle".
(23:05) Puh, Huh ♪ Teka, smell ♪ kun, kun, uh,
uh, kusasa ♪ A little uncle ~ It's because they won't give it to me.
Oh, I'm getting sleepy. Come to think of it, there's something in there...
Uncle, you can clean up properly, right? I need to get a lot of sleep and get well...Ah,
my cock
is sooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooow,owooooooooo'o,'o'ooo~♪'
Suu, suu,
nn♪ Ssuu, suu...