Episode 4 Mother's play
☆ Konomi firmly grabs the shoulder of the "old man" and opens his mouth.
Lick and moisten your own lips
and violate your ears with sexual desire that is too blatant.
(00:04)
Haa
♪ Haa ♪ Haha ♪ I've caught you ♪ If you grab my shoulders like this,
you won't be able to run away ♪ In the first place, there's no way an uncle will run away from me ♪ Njururu, ppicha ♪ Because uncle said,
Because I'm going to do naughty things with my uncle right away, my fever won't go down at all, so if I don't masturbate or have sex for a week, I can use my uncle's pussy as much as I want♪ Pre-serious intentions that do not take into consideration such as reply from the beginning.
Let out a sweet voice just for this and seduce the "uncle". ( 00:45) Hey, bro♪ Let's have sex♪ Let's have sex♪ Eh, let's have sex♪ Girls are seducing me for sex♪ My blood vessels are tightly packed in my trousers, my cock is erect♪
Ehehe ♪ Dose Uncle, Mo Kyun Kyun ♪ You're doing it, right? That's good♪ I'll put my cock inside♪ I'll rape you all the way♪
Kneading me with soft meat, I'll raise the offspring from a futanari ball that's throbbing and throbbing, and I'll blow it out of my urethra~~~~~~ ♪ Hey, I'm going to cum seeding ♪ ☆ Konomi orders him to push down the "uncle" softly and expose his private parts with his own hands.
Gradually, the greasy tone of "Uncle's play" leaked out in his voice, and vulgar laughter began to leak out.
(01:42) Fufu... Let's prepare for sex♪ It's called foreplay♪ So that you can make your cock feel good, let's soften your pussy hole~ ♪ First of all, posture ♪ Push your shoulders, and from a sitting position, lay down your upper body and lie down on your back.
Let The penis pushes up the cloth of the trousers, and the forward running is clearly blurred. (02:13) Okay, uncle, please move in front of your pussy.
Don't take it off♪ Just hook your finger on the waist of your pants and slide them~...
♪ (02:40) Wow♪ You're wearing cute pants, aren't you? Girl's panties with a smiley bear printed on them♪ I exchanged them with my uncle, and he's wearing them properly♪ I'm so happy♪☆ Konomi lightly caresses the crotch of the "uncle" and accumulates a frustrating horny feeling.
. The words that flow with sighs blur the thoughts of "Ojisan". (03:00) Yeah, yeah, Kuri-chan lifts her head and says, "I'm great, I'm great, I'm great, so I'll stroke you...
Oh, my God! Soup is seeping out, mufufu ♪ That's right ♪ Kuri-chan, pick-pick ♪ Every time I shake, the meat around my crotch is squeaky ♪ N-fu ♪ ......
The hole in the buttocks Also, Kupa ♪ Kupaa ♪ Ha ♪ Ha ♪ I want to have sex with my uncle
♪ It feels good when I put my cock in ♪ I'm half open under the bear's panties ♪ I'm doing a sexual appeal ♪ Hey, hey ♪ ☆ When Konomi exposes her private part to "Uncle", she snorts in pleasure.
I deliberately bring my face closer to arouse shame. (03:51) Hmm, fufu♪ Before your pants get soaking wet, why don't you let the cock and the pussy meet? It's strange~♪ Bi-kun♪ Bi-kun♪ Even though Oskuri-chan is pulsing so hard, he looks so good, heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh hey
hey i want my pink meat to be dug up again and again Then, the smell of female estrus drifts in the air, and hide-and-seek beneath the cutie's simmering ketsuman hole.
Konomi herself is the one who is most excited, using obscene expressions one by one. (04:40) How can I get my loose anus to be picked? Stand up, open your arms in the shape of a par, and hold your knees. Dare more, hehe♪ I feel like I'm going to show off the other side of me by chance to my uncle.
Make sure that you understand that it is and obey even your heart. On the other hand, Konomi's throat, which is a "male", makes a low growl like a beast. (05:37) Uh ♪ Haa ♪ Kufufu, Uhihi ♪ Fuu ♪ Fuuu ♪ Cute baby...
I wonder if you know how much power you're throwing around right now ♪Kuri-chan and I happen to have a pussy hole♪ While showing off all together, ugh ♪ And lift your crotch higher than your head ♪ Here's the hole where your cock goes in ♪ Hot Bock-san is here ♪ Uh,
Ugh, gugu ♪ How many uncle's twin balls ♪ Seeds, eh ♪ If you inflate it, you'll feel better, uh, hey ♪ ☆ Konomi took out her already sharp penis and put it in her meat hole. get closer.
The penis drips hot dew from the tip and leaks no less hot breath. (06:20) Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey
hey hey hey hey hey hey look When I had my vagina scratched, I passed out ♪ I'm going to do it ♪ I'm squishy ♪ My cowper was pushed out from the open cock hole
♪ Push ♪ Push ♪ Heh heh ♪ Cutie's anal, uncle's endurance juice and let me drink it ♪ It's cracked and tightened ♪ It's cute♪ Konomi sinks the red-hot glans.
The feel of the muddy flesh crumbled his expression, and his gasping sounded ridiculously long. (07:04) Then the uncle puts his hands on the cutie's thighs, sticks out his hips, tee, um, uh...
look♪ He curls up and looks at his crotch. When I pointed it at me... I could see it ♪ My uncle's glans, ku, kufu, ugh ♪ My soggy anus chupachupa ♪ I sucked, uh, uh ♪ I'm flattering you ♪ U, ho ♪ Uncle, standing on tiptoe straight ahead, chin
tip and anal hole, ku, kuku ♪ I'm sticking to you ♪ If I lose my balance, my cock, oooo...
I'll get in, boo, woo ♪ Hehehe Eh ♪ ☆ When Konomi's stubbornness sticks straight into the "uncle"'s butthole, the two of them are writhing in pleasure that pierces their spines.
While the body is leaning back, only the local area is in close contact.
( 07:53) Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhssesesinthepuffybuttocksoftheuncle,
cutie, boohhhhhhhh...
I'm going in
♪ I'm going to get my cock in, all at once...
Zubo, fuuuuu~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~♪ ♪ It's narrow, it's tight, it's fuuu ♪ No, ♪ My uncle's cock is from the tip to the root,
hoo ♪ Give me a hug ♪ Uhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh It's warm♪ It's soft, it's warm♪ It's simmering, eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee Ah
♪ Jupo ♪ Jupo ♪ Hiii ♪ Deep kiss ♪ I'm about to do it, hoooooo ♪ ☆ The body of the "old man" who reacts obscenely without being conscious of it is attacked, and a slovenly moan is poured out.
Konomi keeps beating her hips. (08:54) Wait, Taku ♪ I'll be honest when my big cock is pushed in ♪ Ah ♪ Even though I'm going to do it, oh oh ♪ oh ♪ oh ♪ I'm really good at the butthole ♪ My uncle's hips, I pulled it ♪ Buku ♪ It swelled up...
Haha ♪ The moment I felt like my head was going to fall out, there was a moment, heh heh ♪ Anus, oh ♪ My sphincter muscle tight, tight ♪ Tight ♪ My mucous membranes are numb ♪ Oh ♪ My penis is all the way to the back of my vagina.
Put on. Selfish words that replace lust with love make the penis stand up again. (09:30) So, wow ♪ It's still not enough ♪ Uncle, ♪ I want to make my cutie cry a lot ♪ So, I endure my favorite cock and spread the seeds in my testicles.
I've packed it all together ♪...... I'll show you how wonderful it is to love each other between a male and a female, with your cutie's fresh body♪ ♪ Kintama is also excited, thud ♪ I'm making seed milk with lots of love.
A piston with more weight on it breaks down the male vagina with force. (10:09) Hey, put your hands on both sides of your unprotected tummy, put your hands on each side of your unprotected tummy,
and step on your heels firmly next to your cutie's butt ♪ To finish, uncle ♪ Put more force into your butt hole, oh oh oh ♪ Ochinpo ♪ Baki ♪ Sharpen it, ah, ah...
I understand ♪ Now, just the glans ♪ In addition, a long cock rod in the pussy hole at once, suu ♪ Let's go ♪ Four-way seeding press ♪ Let's go ♪ ☆ As usual,
Konomi's thick gasping and powerful extraction that doesn't match her age. Speech becomes more extreme. Saliva flows from the smiling mouth and stains the "old man".
(10:57) Zubo♪ Uh, gugutsu♪ Zubo, Zubo, Zubo♪ Ua♪ Ah, haha♪ That's amazing♪ Deep, hey♪ Kuhi, hee, hee ♪ I'm sorry ♪ Yotsuba animal sex ♪ The cock is snoring like crazy ♪ I've stopped being an old man ♪ Stop standing on two legs,
front legs, back legs, and big meaty cock legs in the middle ♪ Heh heh ♪ Give me an erection with all my might, a beast piston ♪ Digging in the pussy, ah
♪ The pussy is happy when it obeys the cock ♪ I'll make you understand with beastly sex, guguuuuu ♪☆ Konomi suddenly stops her hips and notices that a certain point in the vagina of "uncle" has become rigid.
Pretend to be empty and rub the red-hot glans. (11:40) Seed pu ♪ Seed pu ♪ Seeding press, zunn ♪ Woo hoo ♪ Huh, ah...
that cutie's body, twitching from eyelid to toe with dick pozupo I'm cramping, but ♪ I love my uncle in my stomach ♪ I'm trembling, ah, ah ♪ Look, this is nupu ...
♪The tip of the uncle's cock is crunchy♪ Don't be discreet, Nku♪ Something's hitting me... ♪☆Konomi mercilessly pushes the prostate of the "uncle" with his penis.
The miserable voice of "Ojisan" echoes, and Konomi's eyes distort with pleasure. (12:25) Remove half of your cock~ Oh, here it is♪ Huh? Cutie ♪ Why are you looking so frightened Kana ♪ Uncle, there's just power at the base of your tongue...
uh, nggu ♪ Enter, te ♪ The glans that are stretched hard, guriguri, gurii, ku Heh ♪ …… Muho ho ♪ I'm going to let out a naughty voice ♪ Kuri-chan's backside ♪ The female juice is pooling and it swells up ... ...
The prostate gland ♪ I dug it up, and the tip of my chin is stiff, stiff, ugh ♪ Rolling When it's done, oh ♪ heh heh heh heh heh ♪ I want you to hear that feeble voice of defeat again na♪ Konomi.
The sadistic feeling that treats "uncles" as vulgar is blurred in every part of his words. (13:20) You see, this posture is suitable for the deep buttocks digging piston ♪ just now, but like this, lift your heels and wiggle your buttocks ...
♪ Oh ♪ Ha ♪ Ah ♪ I have an erection even though I'm a female ♪ I have a lazy prostate, gorigori gorigori, ugh, fugugu ♪ haha ♪ directly pick ♪ pick ♪ I'm also good at drilling, ya
♪ ☆Konomi doesn't try to slow down her hip swings even though she speaks kindly.
Change the angle of extraction and corner the prostate. (13:49) Oh ♪ I know ♪ When my prostate is messed with, my buttocks get tight ♪ It's so tight, it's sucked by a vicious erection, and oh ♪ The thickness of your neck is also crisp.
I can't forget my uncle's cock, I don't want to be dug and fucked. That's the only thing I can think of, so I'm going to be addicted to digging my ass, so I'm going to let you have a sensitive acme switch and evacuate over there.
Drive the "uncle" into a despairing sensuality with a nasty voice. (14:33) But that's no good♪ It's a lovey-dovey copulation.
♪ Hmm, uh ♪ Hey, hold your knees and stretch them out to your crotch... What's going on there? Uh ♪ On top of that...
Funyafunya Kuri-chan ♪ Hmmm ♪ My prostate is crunchy, hee hee, hee ♪ Twisting his plump body to match, it's so adorable ~ ♪☆ Even the "old man's" penis is under his control, and he is polite and courteous.
Konomi teaches how to masturbate. As long as he is being violated by a long penis, the "uncle" can't resist anything. (15:19) Hmm ♪ Hmm ♪ I'm going to use my cutie's finger to do that again,
hard, bang ♪ Mmmhihi ♪ ♪ Hmm, huh, huh ♪ What do you do when you tease Kuri-chan? Ngu, hey ♪ Delicate fingertips, fluttering ♪ Fluffy ♪ Sensitive tip, squeaky ♪ N, ho ho ♪ Ahhh ♪ Good ♪ Dekakuri-chan is really big ♪ ☆ Exactly Konomi spills
a smile of delight at the feeling of the prostate that has emerged. Grind the weak points of "uncle" without taming. (16:03) Then, muhoho♪ I ended up in a rectal pussy...
Even though it's originally a baby's room, it's a bad boy's prostate that keeps accumulating all the juice that comes out of his cock♪ Nfufuu...
Erection Penikuri-chan Even through the mucous membranes of his thick butt folds, he clings tightly to the glans of the uncle. It even sounds like there is.
However, the hip gesture that pokes the prostate of the "old man" is relentless, and the contradiction rots the thoughts of the "old man". (16:37) Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ,
gyu-gyuu, ng-gu-♪ I'm going to tighten my vaginal hole, hmm-hey♪ Munching my cock with hot butt meat and tightening it, oh, seed♪ ♪ The glans is crushed, gugu ♪ Cute girl's pussy, hole ♪ I want the rich cock milk of an uncle,
I feel ♪ This pussy ♪ Pukupuku prostate, ♪ ☆ Mucus Konomi never forgets to approach the "uncle" with a sweet tone, even though she is overwhelmed by the excitement brought about by the love affair.
I arbitrarily inflate my silly delusions and inflate my penis. (17:21) Hey ♪ I mean, why is this cutie ♪ ♪ I wonder if he's doing this kind of prostate ♪ Mo, mo, maybe...
I'll be able to have sex with my uncle in a week ♪ I'll have my cock eat the female hole ♪ I love you so much, I'll give it a go ♪ Also, I'll give it a try ♪ I'll put up with it, zou... Piledriver copulation Kana, who grew up with a delusional prostate...
♪☆ Konomi now understands that "uncle" has become a slave to be manipulated by pleasure. Konomi is irresistibly fun to pierce her buttocks and move "uncle" at will.
(17:59) Look, shake your head ♪ I wanted to have sex with you ♪ Say ♪ My fingers and toys make my prostate itch all the time, so I'll poke you with my uncle's raw cock ♪ I wanted to feel refreshed,
so my prostate was swollen and swelled up~♪ What♪ Zun♪ No, no, no, no! … ♪☆ Konomi's cheeks smile in a convenient dream.
The base of the penis, the back of the waist, is thick and hot, making Konomi's throat creak.
(18:30) Whoa♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa Zun♪ fuuuuu♪ Uuuuu♪ I got cancer in my prostate, dehehe♪ Boy's uncle's baby in the womb, Uuu♪ I can't wait to conceive, so I'm all alone in my anus hole♪ Paku, ufu~
♪It spreads to the diameter of your uncle's cock,
and then it closes, uhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh He reveals his own lust in a greasy tone.
Contrary to that, the color of love lights up in her eyes, and perverted ecstasy runs through her spine. (19:09) Hmm ♪ Hmm ♪ Haa ♪ Kuhihi ♪ Uncle, I'm so happy ♪ I'm so happy ♪ I'm so happy ♪ Hmm ♪ Kintama It's throaty♪ I can't stop, Jahuu♪ Oh,
even an old man wanted to have sex with a fresh cutie like a girl who just learned to have sex♪ Ohhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh Konomi
tries to exchange kisses in an unreasonable posture.
Even the suffocation is converted into pleasure, and the boiling spirit climbs the penis. (19:45) But, lah...
I'm pregnant♪ Let's try, cutie, chaan♪ゅ ゅ ゅ ゅ ゅ ゅ ゅ き き ゛ ゛ う う う ゛ ゛ ゛ ゛ ゛ ゛ ゛ 疼 疼 疼 疼 疼 に に に に に に に に に に に に に に に に に に に に に に に に に に に に に に に に に に に に 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 、 ♪ Oh
ho ho hoo ♪ Muddy and greasy ♪ Child seed ♪ Seed, juice ♪ Ah, ah, baby milk Hee hee ♪ Konomi pours out words full of self-righteous and self-righteous desires and hits her waist.
The saliva-soaked kisses and the drilling of thick penises crush resistance. (20:25) I'm going to give birth to a baby♪ Look, your mouth, ♪ Open it ♪ Zupozupo nailing piston, nfu ♪ While kissing vows ♪ So, muhihi ♪ Promise of pregnancy ♪ Let's do it,
huh, ha, ha ♪ Hiya, ah ♪ Lean out your upper body, eh ♪ Open your mouth, jerk, ah ♪ … ee,
eh ♪ Drooling, drooling, huh, ah ~, Pupchu ♪ ☆ Konomi licks the saliva that goes around the mouth of "Uncle" without fail, making it more and more saliva-covered. The sound of flesh clashing against each other echoes high, and the words are smeared with inferiority.
(21:02) nbuchu, cchu, nmuaaa♪ nhohoho, oooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo♪ Mmm, puch, petchaaa♪ Mmmm, cutie-chan♪ If you open your mouth like that~♪, you'll be drooling♪ It's dirty,
so the old man will lick it off Ru, kucha ♪ bang ♪ heh heh, the ketsupussy is so tight, teh nn♪ hmh ♪ pan ♪ pan ♪ Even though the piston inside my uncle's vagina catches me, it's sooooooooooooooooooo ♪ ☆ Konomi sucks up her tongue,
sucks up her breath, and immerses herself in joy as she voluntarily swears to the "uncle" with each kiss.
The penis is so tall that it reaches its climax with just one thought. (21:45) chu, chupu ♪ vaginal ejaculation ♪ nn, bubu, umchu ♪ fertilization, yeah~♪
apu, kuchu, nzuzu ♪ on the floor ♪ nn, tsu Gu♪ Pucha, rerun♪ You're pregnant♪ Petcha♪ Nn, u♪ Pregnant month♪ Chu, chu, chuu…… ♪ Pappa…… ♪ Hihi fu ♪ Hihi fu ♪ Hehehehehe......
Get out, give birth♪ ☆ Konomi's eyes shine with the heat of the semen that boils the inside of the urethra, firmly solidifying the posture of "uncle" and continuing to shoot down the penis.
(22:12) Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh Ugh ♪ Gugu ♪ Shrinking testicles ♪ Dobu-dobu, ho ho ♪ Oh ♪ Ah ♪ It's hot ♪ It's hot and sticky, heh ♪ The inside of my cock is burning, ugh , Seed juice ♪ Ka ♪ Cutie, more ♪ Kuri-chan is bullying, deeee...
♪ Ehi ♪ Mesuiki juice pyu ~~ ♪ Shiyo, hey hey ♪ Kuhihi ♪☆Konomi goes half frantic as she yells and swears.
Leaving the last word, when the lips overlap, the penis makes the flesh pulsate greatly, and the semen shoots out from the tip.
(22:44) Uh ♪ Pupchu ♪ I swear ♪ I swear it's so hot ♪ So, yeah ♪ I'm going to put it out in the middle of a cute sperm ♪ Pup, kuchu, ah
♪ Plump fat Aiming for the prostate, it's ok, gi, gigi ♪ I swear, I, Igu ♪ Uuu ♪ N♪ ♪ I'm impregnated ♪ Butt ♪ Digging ♪ Creampie ♪ Kko, ho ♪ I vowed to conceive a healthy baby with rich uncle genes.
Um, cchu, juju, cjuruuu~~~~♪
☆At
the climax, Konomi's body loses strength other than supporting the limbs,
An unintelligent gasp comes out of my mouth.
It shakes its empty hips, but its tightly bound genitals do not move.
(23:17) …… ug ♪ bueeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee ~ ♪ The prostate too, eh ♪ It's so hard ♪ Uuu ♪ Glans head, thump, thump ♪ Huh ♪ Well,
it's still out, ryu ♪ Se, sperm, ah ♪ I want to kiss you while you kiss me♪
☆ Konomi and the "uncle" breathed heavily at Koetsu's deep breath, occasionally touching each other's lips.
Konomi laughs with a strange tone mixed with Konomi himself and "uncle play". (23:44) Ah~~♪ I'm sooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo♪ I'll talk as many times as I want ♪ Huh ho ho ♪ Don't listen to the uncle's masturbation all the time ♪ U ho ♪ Ah,
this will make the teacher angry again ♪ Come on ♪ Let's turn an adult into a pregnant idiot who is addicted to shit Kemasen ♪ I mean, amuchu, kupuchu,
ppuah ♪ But I can't pull out my cock ♪ Ah, I'm going out, I'm feeling, I'm going to go out ♪☆ Suddenly, the voice is the same,
but it's more than "uncle play" Konomi approaches "Uncle" in a tone full of madness.
His eyes had lost their light, and his penis was raging again with ferocious heat.
(24:23) Ah, my ejaculation has stopped... hey hey uncle.
pregnant? pregnant? pregnant? "You're pregnant, aren't you?" "Why aren't you pregnant?" "Are you stupid?"
A younger girl with a big cock picks
her buttocks, and while she cries
like, "Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh"
Is it
a pussy taputapu?
"You have no choice but to get pregnant?" "I gave you so many seeds, ♪ too, why aren't you pregnant?"
☆Konomi deceives with laughter.
An unnaturally bright voice paralyzes the brain of "uncle".
Konomi's red lips pressed against her cheek were as cold as ice.
(25:09) Hahaha♪ Sorry♪ Were you scared?
But I can't do it ♪ I've been playing "uncle play" all the time, and I really wanted to use my seed to get him pregnant ♪ Will I get pregnant next time I have sex? "Will I get pregnant the next time I have sex?" "Don't you understand?" Hmm...
well then, be careful ♪ If you're alone with me, I'll definitely rape you and absolutely impregnate you ♪ Eheh, I'm not lying ♪ Look, stick out your cheeks ♪ "Near kiss", Shigeru... Konomi's baby, definitely give birth, Oji-san♪