one day
started
I'm in charge today.
Thank you.
That customer, this shop
Have you been here several times? Is it just one point?
I'm still about two weeks old
The training is finally over and the customer is my first customer.
It's the first time we're together
I'm sorry that
you came all the way here.
you can do it don't worry
Well then, let me start with an explanation.
You chose the course recommendation
Okay, my recommendation
is faster,
isn't it?
Then let's start
What should I do
Let's start with the easy stuff first
It's a nail topping
It's all about the sound, but this is surprisingly good
i might be the best
then let's start
To go
I'll try it
separately
it's over
how was it
next time
Um, next
is sand.
It's Oiso sand
This is really a child's toy
Do you know that this is sand that you can play with
even in your room?
That's right, let's have fun with him
free
tightly
It's very much like
dividing the soil of a cat.
is that ok
yes
After all, it feels like
Who would have thought to cut
my father
I'm relieved
yes suriyan
It feels like
Well then, let's do it one more time.
It's amazing that it doesn't come with
You can make soil in your room
surprisingly fun
Then I'll do it again
with the left side
next time.
Slowly, slowly,
it's over
I don't
have many chances
to ask how it was
It's a sound that can't even be called nostalgic, but I'd be happy if you liked it
I'll do something new then
This time too, it's the one that's over
then what do you think
you don't know
This is a melamine sponge impregnated with slime.
It feels like a monkey
I thought that too, but you thought about it.
There are many strange things in the world
It's expensive, so Zaku goes in.
It feels like sand
It sounds different
It's a mix of rough sounds and spicy food sounds.
I don't understand
It's a Toyo knife,
so it's not dangerous,
but please stay still.
yeah i'm going
because it's painful
I don't think I hear it
very often
But that sort of thing is surprisingly popular.
I actually
should i
cut here
always go there
up to
the array
Shall we start with the opposite
left ear
I will
be surprised
hey
It's fun to cut raw silk sponge It's hard to cut
I have a strange feeling like I'm cutting spicy food, I wonder what it is
I wonder if it's fun
I didn't say anything strange, but it has nothing to do with the customer,
so please don't worry about it.
I have to say
it myself
Ah Mi-chan goes there
often too
See you soon
three
yes
it's over
how was it
Crunchy sponge somehow relaxed
I'm glad I did it I'm glad
Huh, maybe I've loosened up
a bit too
Customers are friendly, so you can rest assured
Today was really good for the first time
Yes, I'll clean up far away for now
i'm not mom
what happened
Are you
suddenly tired
every day?
I have one more
Please relax a little more
Next is the end.
Finally, listen to the sound
of the river.
Please listen slowly
yes
Sorry I made you wait
Let's do it then
today
oh the other side
too
Are you healed by the song of the bubble?
customer is vacant
correct
What's wrong
please don't
lie
is it nothing
I will continue
for a while
no
customer
I can hear you properly
I'm happy
It makes me happy to have my husband enjoy a lot,
but I guess it's a blessing
It's not that big of a deal
It's big, so
I put a lid on it.
This is the end of the recommendation
for the kettle.
thank you for your hard work
How was it?
I'm sure you were able to hear it
with a very fresh feeling.
i had a lot of
fun too
I was your first customer.
It's very easy to do,
and it's
a little regrettable.
can you come again
please
With this, the first condolence telegram was completed.
Ah, but I don't have to be the only one
Mie or nothing
Not everyone does the same thing in that treatment,
everyone programs different sounds.
So try to nominate like this
It seems that finding the sound you like is one way to enjoy it.
I want the audience to enjoy the sound purely.
So why don't you show another child next time you come?
try it
I wonder if this is a good place to recommend
There's a girl who's been really popular lately, and she's called Ai-chan.
She came into the store a little earlier than me.
I heard that she has a lot of repeats and she's a really cute girl
He's also a really good boy
with a great personality.
I'm getting along well with you
Tell me about various things, such as the store.
oh try to nominate
I've had them do it too, and the sounds were all good.
There are many things that are quite stimulating, but I like it.
It may be your favorite sound.
yes i am waiting
What do you think about Kama's efforts today?
Thank you for your hard work