Welcome brother Nice to meet you Nice to meet you
Brother, brother, first time here, second time
I see
I'm so old that I suddenly heard that
when I met you
I'll leave it to your imagination if you think it's an elementary school student
brother to the owner
How can you ask a girl about her age with a nervous look on her face?
You said it was the second time
Who did Noko-chan do for the first time today?
I like Ayu
I know you like both brothers, don't you?
The only people who come to a store like this are lolicons.
Don't worry, perverted brother I
It's true that you're
a money-taker.
Do 23, such as picking at a child who has just finished training.
There aren't
many people
who do that
kind of thing.
But for the first time I nominated the doorknob Kana-chan
I know why you showed me
A child who likes
younger children
Today, Kana-chan's customer in Ito
City
I will do my best to serve you today
Today is a very
stimulating course,
you're a big brother
You quietly fell in love with smr after the first treatment.
that's fine
Get used to it at first
what does
this mean
The only
thing that's in
it is the lotion.
Shakashaka right left
Football
sound conversion
right ear
Mr. Miss.
i'm going
up
football soccer
krut football
make up
time of water
Men don't do this very often.
Uncles say that they heard it for the first time there.
you like squid
That's why I do this first in any course
because I want you to relax
It's getting more and more exciting
from now on
Onii-san said that the first time was Kana-chan
Well then, I'll take it easy today
It's a very exciting course
It's Ama-chan's introduction, so let's take it slow
then then
The change
will come
out
this squishy
there was when i was
a kid
it's a
child's toy
This is a book and this is
It's all about croissant food
There are many
other things,
but for now,
I want to play
with these kids,
and this is big.
Listen slowly and be
conscious of
the sound
left ear
lose weight
yoniji
talk
right ear too
popular games
Nikkei
average
what
Because I want you
to listen to
a lot of machines
No, what's close today
I'll only stop if you tell me, but it's nothing
then leave it like this
Kita Dojima older
brother
yes
It was
the end
squeeze
Let's get this kid
out of the way,
then next time
gloves this is
the last
Even if the gloves are gloves,
they're rubber gloves, the kind that doctors wear.
wii hidden
Let's go
It's become difficult to hear the voice of time
papa papa papa papa papa papa papa
scary
scary scary scary
What is Power
Bomb
stomach
no no no
no
Why are you treated like a baby
when you're
like a big brother
i hate it
Satsuki
Even though I love to return baby
pretend you don't
notice
Onii-san, this is an ear refreshment shop that only has children up to junior high school students.
There are other shops, but
why would anyone go out of their way to come here?
Everyone just wants to be spoiled by a girl who's like a child
Brother really thinks so too
When I was given this village, I thought nothing of it.
I just remembered something, and my older brother
is thinking that he's completely protecting his form
The customer across the street, the customer next door, and everyone else are the same,
so I'm not ashamed
Everyone is like that I won't make fun of you
even if you win
It might be
Rika Ishikawa,
but I'm
sorry
Calm down
felt
I feel that all naked
people become quiet
It was the end
rubber gloves
thank you
brother
That's all for
the exciting
composition of Chiba.
I wonder how it was, it must have been a different feeling
Different course, different sound
'Cause when girls change, their ways change
If you think that a heart-pounding MR is a time to heal, you're making a big mistake.
Yes, because there are many ways
Kon-chan is your big brother's favorite
You seem to like first things anyway
You know, it doesn't have to be just one girl to nominate
If you're two, do you have different ways of doing things?
I don't think the two of us have ever made powdered tea together.
If that's the case, I'm sure
if I let
Kana-chan make her debut
asmr next time,
I'm sure
my heart will be really excited.
Today's charge was underground
We are waiting for you
to visit
us again.