Hello from Nii-san today
Thank you for the double nominations today Thank you
Chika-chan, you're really showing me
I told you once before I met you
That's why I was so happy
When the customer's name was called, Chika-chan went,
but she wasn't happy.
Well, it's okay Karakana-chan, first of all, it's a greeting.
I'm rather nervous.
thank you
I will be in charge today
After that, it's a deer. Today we'll do it together.
Kana-chan, it's the first time I've been with someone
Let your grown-up brother take the lead
let's start gently
I will go next
to you
I get nervous when there are other people
I'm sure your brother is with you too
That's right, look at your face
The customer's face is red
This is the face
of a trained adult
I want you to hurry up,
hurry up
Shall I give
lots of challengers
Today's side dish is a course
for the two of us together, right?
There is one for the right ear and the other for the left ear
But we do the same things
Because the people are different, the radio waves and the feeling of the sound are also different.
It's pretty funny I hope you like it
Well, to start with, sukusuku to sukusuku is just like the word,
just sukusuku and whispers.It's surprisingly popular overseas.
I'll do it
Back
Quickly quickly
Round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round,
round, round, round, round, round, round
Round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round
Like, like, like, like,
like, like, like, like, like, like, like
I'll eat
a little more
in September
Quickly
Quickly quickly
Chika Chika
Chika-chan is playing a prank,
right?
Onii-san, it's an important song after March, isn't it?
If you don't want to do something you don't like, you'll get there.
I need a little preparation
Chika-chan yes
carbonated water
Substitute for carbonated water
and kappa
Thank you
carbonic acid
water is marinade
baby
I'll put it
in chorochoro
I'm ready
The sound that calms down like this for a while
It's a crackling crackling intro
Thank you
Rika
Kurume Round
and Round
The alternative song was important
Cool Sound Nampa
in memory of grandma
Ama-chan Maki-chan
no Uta Nogizaka
carbonic acid
It's water diamond cider,
but I don't really think of it
as a sound.
I usually only think about what it tasted like and whether it was delicious or not.
In the past, I used to say that I would go to the store to enjoy this kind of sound.
I'm talking about the Edo period.
It was a time when being too old
was one of the entertainment
A child like this came around
Next is September 4th and the same performance as this child
Kana-chan looks tired, no
It's getting hard to breathe, these boobs
Lucky bag
Ako-chan
I still use cider
stay still again
wrinkled
cider
It's a little different,
it's not
a crackling sound,
but a wrinkling sound.
Mokka
stomach
say something
wrinkled
I wonder if the carbonic
acid is gone soon
It works really well
next and last
Lastly, wrap it up sore-chan
chika-chan yes
sputum
Tapping Tapping Tapping Tapping Tapping
folding
Everyone likes it,
the side of the entrance,
the entrance is here,
this house
is kind
Kindness
Tatter Tatter
Tracing or something
just a little more and more
and more and more and more
even here
Also
Chika-chan, Rika-chan,
something will come out
It's true, but is it big brother auction club?
If so, please let me know my friends
what happened to yochika
I'll do the same
A customer who stopped by
I can't help it
because I'm tired
Kana-chan, I'll teach you
how to turn
off your mouth
and turn on your ears
Don't say it's not that exaggerated
It's not a mouth, but it doesn't matter
anime brother
Then park for a while
Chika-chan's dream
Why are you my important customer?
Don't be weird, it's not weird
It's just because your brother wants you to come
Then I'll do it with you, so let's do it together
Good customer
I was loved
Then
Please tell me
if you don't like it
Kana-chan, I'll leave the start to Kana-chan
Do you get it
can you play
I'm still going
Idol collage
it's time
I ended up in a place with extended service
I wanted to do more calculations, so I can't make it in time
Brother Meyer, thank you for your hard work. I will clean up now.
I can talk with you just a little more
Welcome to your account
I went
Maybe even a joke that was hated is pessimistic
no no no that
what do you mean
i mean i was embarrassed
I don't know
what kind of face you should make
when you're alone with your brother.
Because you're an important customer
I didn't want to make you feel strange, so I ran away
Big brother Kana-chan isn't getting better, right?
I saw your face when you left, even your ears were bright red
Just by looking at your brother,
you acted like you were scared
That's right, I know your brother
A girl who doesn't understand the meaning of a girl who doesn't understand the heart
I get timid when
I'm in front of someone I like
I get scared I don't want to be hated
I'm afraid to meet you outside and run away
It's that kind of creature, so it has a bit of a pulse
I'm sure it was, brother
It's the same as getting a big
dick when someone who likes squirt girls is in front of you.
I thought you were divorced
because you didn't react at all
Even if it's a Lolita
with a touch
Wakana-chan, I'm going to visit the front desk while I'm here.
I'll decide first
It's okay,
Kana-chan is probably interested
I see, you don't want to be hated by Kana-chan, even onii-san.
I'm scared to meet you dressed like that, can't you help it?
Let's get away from each other
with strong people
Shall I do it
for you?