Thank you for your nomination
Yeah, lately you've been showing me a lot about love
I thought this guy was one of a kind
I know, you've also nominated a lot of fools
Brother, brother, I wonder
if it's about the deer
It's not like I fell in love with you exactly the same
Just because you made me feel good
I'm just worried about love
Wakana-chan is straight in my head, but people are flirtatious
I think you'll want to make a lot of girls feel good about you
Maybe I did, but I wonder if it's my brother
because nothing happens
It doesn't happen with Ai and Nara Kana,
who are nominated because they want to be comforted
in the basement
something might happen
The older brother who denied it, after all
It feels good to be honest
with everyone about the flatness of an adult man
Even if I'm honest underground
Your brother wants to find out everything he's hiding in the basement, so you nominate him, right?
Love can be painful,
but it's because you won't deny it
I've been making you grow up for eight days
I noticed
A long time ago, not just today
From the day after
I gave you that time
love knows all
And I won't deny that kind of older brother
I get horny for a twelve-year-old girl
I can't help it
No one can stand listening to the dizzying sounds in their head
while sniffing the smell of a girl
who has just welcomed the president from such a close distance.
All customers feel the same
hand out or not
I want you to comfort me again
I gave it to you last time and before that, but now I want to do it again
It's not going
well
But if your brother loses confidence, you'll be in trouble, so it's fine
I'll do it for you today, too
Lately it's
fast
I'm going to be depressed soon
What happened today? I'll listen to whatever you have to say
But it seems like this kid wants to hear the story first
Well, I'm drenched in endurance soup today
what happened i bought too much
you have a lot of proclivities
you went
You've been playing too flashy lately
Even before this, your brother was really loud, wasn't he?
It seems like he's a little suspicious of the ceiling and everyone else
This is because it's dangerous
if you make a sound like
you're shaking too much
Today, under the pretext of enjoying this sound,
I wonder if I can hide the fact that I'm whispering
thank you very much
Doesn't this require lotion?
First of all, don't use Omuta
This song makes everyone doubt
It won't change no matter how much time passes
A voice that sounds like you've been touched for the first time A cute voice
The shop has a strange atmosphere.
Why don't you turn your back on your brother
who isn't satisfied
Yeah, everyone's starting to care
Come Komu-chan Switch Yes, you should be able to deceive
If you can stand your voice,
you can stand it
adult man
did you go
There's a weak spot in my chest
how do you feel today
yes
I couldn't speak well today
It's been like that since then
oh cute
I'm sure you want to have fun talking with your brother.
But after all, I've become more conscious of my brother since then,
and it's a little scary
But you look really happy when your brother's mission comes
Even after working with my brother, he comes home with a big smile on his face.
Your brother is giving you that love and comforting you.
It can't be helped if I waited while being ethical
From now on, Kana-chan and Tux
And I have to dig deep inside
At that time, I completely fell in love with Kin-chan.
If you suddenly show me, I'll do it honestly
it's from email
If you show your older brother's male
part to a child who doesn't realize it
I have to cover it up
san is not
bad
Nearly 1,000 sour
junior high school students were entangled
i know love
It's a natural reaction as an adult male
I'm not ashamed, so show me
what should i do unsan feels good
it did
the same thing
i was at home
yes i think i'm making some progress
yeah yeah yeah
Tell me what
happened
Yes, it's fine
to look at the elementary
and middle school girls' sinks, right?
Kana-chan isn't here, so you don't have to put up with it
punch
i want to see
cute panties
Look, it's about Kana-chan, isn't it?
be absent
too good
Let's keep talking like that, let's hear it
yes i heard it
I don't want you to have nipples because you'll get loud.
Mr. Fujii, how are you feeling right now?
yes
super strong
Yes Yes
I can't stand it
let's hear
brother's feelings
let's eat
yes
ok what happened
short time
Oh let it flow, manager
What's wrong Kana-chan
yes
yes yes
Nesan
No way,
Kin-chan is coming, so
I don't want Kana-chan
to find out
that I keep twitching
and twitching
for whatever reason.
I know that if I puff up the tip, I'll get bigger,
but why did I make it even more ticking than usual?
It can't be helped if you get excited and get excited
When this kid feels the thrill, he thinks he wants to have a baby
Is that why Kim was about to be found out?
I wanted to throw up baby
I was very happy with each one.
I should have
just spit it out like that,
but I'm in trouble because I added it.
I have to finish it early
Let's go now, don't worry about the noise
Kana-chan because everyone finds out
I know what to do
brought
it's okay to go now
Today too, show me how cool
I am
No no no
brother peeing
feels good
It's okay to throw everything out
Of course everyone finds out, so it feels good until the end
Peeing cue
I hate that I've exhausted everything
I'm going to make a loud voice because Kana-chan, who I don't like, is gone
I don't care if other people do it to me, Ai-chan,
I'm not defiant I think you probably noticed
that Ai was doing naughty things with a customer,
but I don't think you know that the other person is your brother
I don't know who the people in the store are serving customers.
So even if it's okay,
be careful not to be found when you pay the bill.
I won't help you until later