I haven't started the course
Haven't you gotten bigger
since you
asked the customer
to make them smaller?
Every time
I move,
I get stiff
you knew it well
It was beautiful
I understand if it's okay
with curry
I don't use slimy for the time being today
Are you saying that you want to leave the lodge?
Such
was slimy
to
Nanda-chan
It's time to toast
No problem
It won't hurt, so I'll make you feel good
I'm going to bed early
From the beginning to the root to the tip
can be molded at once
hey
It's easy to spread,
so it's coming.
I'm so happy
But I know
you're expecting
him
It's easy to understand
with customers,
so what do you want other customers to do?
Make a ring with your fingers and protrude at the top
I want you to play it I understand
It would have been nice
if someone could have
pointed a finger at me
If you do your best, you won't be able to get it out.
If you can't go out unless you feel a lot more comfortable,
I'll make you feel a lot more comfortable
After the customer's tip becomes a shaved bun,
if you squeeze the protruding part with your finger,
it's like you're forced to take it.
To tell the truth, it's been January
A customer and I have hidden my clothes.
I had a hard time getting rid of the marks before this too.
The customer must have used kimchi to express it.
I'm happy to be happy, so please don't make that face
horror
The face that seems to be comfortable with
that song erased
I want to see that, show me a lot
Make yourself feel better,
tick tick
it's becoming
Something has accumulated more than usual today
Even though I'm about to spit it out
It's a pity that I can't get out of it
unless it feels good
But it will take time, so you can feel a lot better
Even if it gets wet, it doesn't feel like a waste
I might be a little bit smaller, but are you a mom?
Thank you for wanting to make
customers feel comfortable
for as long as possible
Thank you
I can give you plenty today
Over the tip of the chinchin mountain chinchin
I feel like I'm sensitive because I see it when I ride it again
But if I narrow it down at the end, I want to do it right away with the customer
You leaked your pee
I'm going to make a request for you again today, won't you?
Because I'm a strong boy
Even if I say that, it won't come out right away Wrap it in your palm
Another autumn
salmon good
thing
I'm trying to do it
What do you think your sister would think if you could sit down and run away?
Think about it, Koma-chan, right?
I tried not to be a lolicon
Ika Ika
Ika
Little by little,
I left
it felt good
I was able to put up with Nee-chan again
As a reward, I'll give you one hand on your roots,
so you might not be able to escape
customer
It's okay to be happy
as much as you like
please don't hold back
do you fall in love
Penis feeling
good feeling
I have to endure
a good voice
Hey, I'll give you a little
cookie cookie I caused trouble for other customers
quick
I can put up
with the voices of the customers
when I'm inside.
isn't it amazing
The front is very shiny, but
This is what I brought, so I'm canceling
keep it
like this
Is it early?
I already fell
asleep
I can't help it because it feels so good
Let's put up with a lot of voices and let the chin-chin grandi repeat
Dad can please you as much as you want
I like customers
who are selfish
tell me
something
I was gradually warped like this
I feel something powerful,
but it's amazing
it's going to be like this
Can I talk about this becoming Chico-chan?
Great reaction
What happened to Unchinchin-san?
I want to keep it a secret, just the two of us together
I don't want to be seen when I say
I don't want you to know about Kuma-chan
No matter how big, stiff and strong it is, it won't walk at all
cool
Big sister, you can always show me how cool you are
Feeling a little disgusted, let's do something happy again
It's nice
to have more sound
work while
feeling
I'm going
to stop this
from now on
Shall we try it sooner?
You seemed to like it earlier
I know how
you feel
not leaking
But I'll do my best
and endure,
Unchi-chan's voice
is amazing
do your best, do your best
keep it up
more and more
I'm getting old,
can anyone
put it
out?
Please give me
a chance
Doraemon
it's getting sweeter
I'm glad that it came out well Papa, let's love it
I'll do my best, do my best
Keep your voice down
on TV
Pikmin healed
can't hit
Thank you for your hard work
Curry makes me
a little
bit smaller
It's painful to become full-bodied