ok ok france
hello hello customers
Onii-san today is Ai and Kana-chan's double
thank you
Thank you
Um, the two of us were just talking about what we should do.
Yeah, I've done double pages many times,
so I thought I'd try something a little different.
Kana-chan, the older brother who Ai-chan blamed for love
My older brother wants to do something that pleases me, so I'll lick his ears
I'm not going
that far
Onii-san, something good will surely happen after this is over
Prepare properly and nothing will happen.
I knew I should start with ham ham
I will go
yes
I see
For real
yes sisters next
Umm, the guy
who will support you
in your ear
during terrorism, huh?
did the point
Well then, will you heal the guy
who will hold the tip of the next terrorist
attack at Fuji?
yes
I was holding
of
click it
yeah yeah
yes yes
And this
yes
It was
the ear spot
Next time, I'll crush my reactions like anxiety
I'll get closer and do it with a round eye
Even if it tickles me,
I'll endure it, yes
Oh, yes
yes
It was dog
play
Next time I'll do that Kokubun in my ears
Yeah, yeah, he's the guy who buys clothes
all the way in.
yes
it was deep
Well then, next time,
you'll really understand
the features of Torinami-ageru
and the lower ototsu
at the entrance of the ear.
to go
yes
Rough
Oh yeah, the next one is the last
Stop it once more
my ears get soggy
reduce
I don't think so
Is that so
Yes Yes
yeah yeah yeah
it's over
lonesome cleaning
devoted
It's okay to blow away like this
Takayuki
don't wait
Kana-chan and Hihara
big brother
Nekana-chan really got
big again
what should i do in this situation
Kana-chan, who doesn't really know what to do,
has already seen her brother's father.
You don't have to be complicated, and I'll stand up for you, so let's be together
Anything called money
is salt if you do it