1 ♀ Girlfriend's sweet blowjob
So, next time I'm off, I'm definitely going to see this.
I'm looking forward to it
Hmm?
What's wrong? You're so shy staring at me
Nah, I told you I'd be shy
Want a kiss?
You want a kiss, don't you?
Yes
Nah, come again~
Nah, just a kiss?
It's big...
There you are...
You've got a little erection there
What should I do?
Do you want to do it?
But...
my sister might be coming home soon
I know
So...
do it with this
You like to use your mouth a lot, don't you?
Can I just use my mouth
Well...take it off
You see... it's twitching
Are you ready?
So, I'm going to start licking
It's so hard
Are you comfortable?
It's okay if it's harder
The glans is so big
You want to be sucked?
Nah?
You want to?
I'll show you
Hmm?
Don't keep looking at me, I'm too shy to look good like this
Eh? You look sexy? I'm so shy.
Patience juice...
You want more? It's okay, go ahead.
No more? Then I'll continue.
It's coming out again...
I'll swallow deeper
Wrap your throat tightly around the glans...
You like that, don't you?
It's a bit uncomfortable but it's okay
If it makes you feel good, I'll do it for you
I'll try my best
It's starting to twitch
The rod is playing around in my mouth
It's still trembling
like we're having sex.
Is it comfortable?
Enjoy it more
trembling, trembling, trembling, trembling, trembling, trembling, trembling
Going?
It's a bit uncomfortable but my mouth is already sticky
want me to help you come?
Nah "wanna go, wanna go" kind of look
What should I do?
What to do?
You want to come? You can have an orgasm!
I want to see you come
I'll look at you, with my face this way
It's shy though...
Yeah, that's it
Are you going? That's fine.
Let's get it all in
That's a lot...
drink it down
Was it good?
I shot a lot.
I'm happy
It's a little hot to be doing this
I'm craving ice cream
Do you want to go to the convenience store?
Yeah, it's fine, it's fine
I'm sure I'd like to rest now after
cumming
I'll get it myself, you can wait here
It might take a while...
I'll leave it to you
No one should be home at this hour
But I'll try to be back early
I'm going out