2 ♂ Sister's seductive masturbation
Sayu-chan? Hmm? Ale?
Hello there
That... you're Sayu's boyfriend, right?
Eh~ That's right
First time meeting
You two are dating, right?
She hasn't brought you here before
It's a bit of a rarity
Say, did you just make out?
It doesn't say you can't do it.
Try not to make any noise.
The neighbours next door will care
Nah?
Nah? Don't look at me like you're hiding.
You're really handsome
You see, he and I are related by blood, and we see boys in the same way.
Your body is not easy to describe, it's just right
Nah, what do you think of me?
I'm always told I look like my sister.
Do I really?
Hmm?
Well, it's okay if you come closer to check it out
Look...
What do you think?
The eyes, the nose, the thickness of the lips...
You'll be nervous if you're this close
After all, it's the first time we've met
You can feel it in your breath
The eyes are fleeing again
Don't be shy, look away
Nah, you want to try a kiss
Just a little bit, I'd like to try
It's okay, I won't tell anyone
I'll keep it a secret, secretly
No?
If you don't want to, just stay away.
If Sayu finds out, you'll be accused of cheating
Look, if you don't get out of the way, you'll be kissed for real
Nah, is that okay?
Look
Ah, I really got it...
You're wrong for not running away
Do it again? There's no excuse this time, okay?
My heart is racing... do the next thing
Stick your tongue out
Kissing for a long time
Alle?
You seem to be very aroused
A lot of semen?
Nah?
It's getting hard...
I just touched it
Why is that?
Nah?
Why is it erect?
Did a kiss alone turn on the switch?
This is clearly Sayu's room
I can't help you...
So... take it off
If you want me to take it off for you, it's not impossible
After all, you'll be seen by Sayu with your erection
To avoid suspicion of cheating, cum out and turn back to your old self, otherwise...
right?
You see
Make a quick decision and take your bottom off
If you don't hurry, Sayu will be back
Come on, hurry up!
You can't take it off yourself?
You're not a child anymore, you're not!
Look
One...two...
Wow, it's so hard
So that's how sexual it is
I'm shying away from it...
So cute
Alle?
Ah, there's a stain on my underwear.
Ah~ you two were making out
Eh~ you're still so energetic after having sex
Sayu is so pathetic
You've had sex with your girlfriend, but you're excited about someone else
That's not good
You're a bad boy, aren't you?
But yeah, I'm happy
Let me suck on your tongue
I'll hold your erection there
The rod is so hot
but it's not enough
tongue, this time you suck it
So skilled, so comfortable
Want to get jerked off?
Nah, this hard thing wants to be rubbed erotically, doesn't it?
Yes
But you have to keep it a secret from Sayu, right?
You can do it...
You're a good boy
Ah, keeping secrets from your girlfriend is still a bad boy
Well, who cares?
I'll give you a jerk off
That's great.
I just got a little shiver
You're expecting too much
Did it feel good? I get complimented on my hands all the time
No, it's fine if there's no one around to make a sound
I love a good pant
Don't hold back, let me hear you
But you have a girlfriend and you don't say no
That's not right, you know?
My sister's boyfriend~
I do understand that you're happy to have your rod jerked around
But you can't forget that you're a bad boy just because you come and cum!
You want to move yourself?
you want to move yourself?
as if to say "want to want to want"
really slutty
So slowly speed up
Here's your reward
Just now, you're panting so erotically
Is it hard to hold back your rod?
It's okay to scream a little more
like this "Ahhhhhhhh"
huh?
Don't you always gasp when you're doing it with Sayu?
It's very comfortable if you scream, I promise
There's no need to hold back
Ahhhhhh
Look, the rod feels good, the rod feels good
I'm not sure if it's a good idea to hide it from my girlfriend.
right?
But what if Sayu comes back at this time?
It's painful to stop when it's about to get more comfortable, isn't it?
But it's better than if I've already started cumming
Then you won't be able to clean up right away and you won't be able to make up excuses
Is "I was just masturbating" an acceptable excuse?
At my girlfriend's house without permission...
I think I'd be considered a pervert
Do you have to stop in the middle of it? I'm just kidding.
Can't do it, can you? I get it
Your heart is beating like crazy, and it's getting more comfortable, and you can't stop feeling that way, can you?
It can become more enjoyable
Okay, let's move on to the next stage
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
You're starting to feel the urge to cum
I'm hiding it from my girlfriend
I know I can't let my balls cum at this time
Ahh~
No, I can't do that, I can't think about cumming, I can't think about it, I can't think about it.
but it's so good, so good, so good
I can't help it if I'm being hand-fucked without my girlfriend.
Oh
Nah, the semen is coming up?
You've got a voice!
I'm so turned on!
I'm not going to reveal it, but it's so nice, isn't it?
Do you like it?
hola can't cum can't cum can't cum
you can't cum in the absence of your girlfriend
boyfriend~
Don't cum!
Oh, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look.
It's so dangerous!
The patience juice is flowing a lot
Let's squeeze it out
So much
You're so horny, boyfriend
It's delicious
Do you want to make more?
Do you want to cum?
What a slutty look
wanting to cum so badly with the white stuff
Your boyfriend is worse than I thought
He's not thinking about Sayu at all
I can't leave Sayu's future in your hands.
I'm just kidding!
It's more than that now
I think the most important thing is to become comfortable
Yes, make your rod worse
Getting more and more comfortable
want to cum biubiu
hola, keep doing it!
with the other hand, put your hands together
It's a little technique that creates a sense of backbone
Hold it tight when you're comfortable and tell me about it, huh?
Your hand is so hot
So...let's get started
hola, draw the cum back up to your balls
rubbing and jerking hard
so good!
making the rod feel slightly sore and ready to cum
It's almost time to cum or Sayu will be back
Cum all the way out before they find out
Hold the rod tightly
and lift my balls up
about to go?
I'm sweating all over
Going?
You're going?
So, please, I'm begging you
Say "Make me come"
and tell me shyly
hola one...two...
I can't hear you
There's no one around, speak louder
hola Here we go... one... two...
so cute
but not yet
inch stop
The rod twitches and twitches...
It's hard on the rod, isn't it? It's hard to hold the semen back, isn't it?
I'm pausing because you look so cute
Forgive me
You'll forgive me, won't you?
So...can I cum this time?
hola here we go!
Here comes the excitement
It's impossible to jerk off like that without cum coming up
The other hand is being held tightly by you
Dangerous?
semen is coming out?
haven't shown Saya how you look now
It's a shame to show your tender rod like this
hola, be patient, be patient, be patient
It's not time to ejaculate yet
already?
you're going to ejaculate?
I said no
A man can't pee his trousers
You can't cum!
inch stop
Wow, it's jerking again
If I hadn't held the root, I would have come
Is that the limit?
Okay then
So, it's been a long time coming
I'll let you cum
I said "Cum" so I can stop holding back
Get as comfortable as you want to be
So, hola, clasp your hands together again
jerking the rod hard
jerking it to get all the semen out
It's so good, it's almost out
Yes, you can... make a lovely panting sound for me to hear
"I'm going to cum, I'm going to cum" like that
with the shy voice of Sayu on your back, shout it out
hola "I'm going to cum, I'm going to cum," the semen is already flowing up
I can't, I can't, I'm going, I'm going *n
Yes, come out, boyfriend
The semen that should have been ejaculated to your girlfriend, ejaculate it all out
hola here we go one...two...
Come on!
hola, cum!
there goes *n
biu*n
still cumming...
gone gone gone
cumming out
Look at that...
so much
It's the evil smell of cheating
Oh no, use the toilet paper there...
Put your underwear on!
So, goodbye, boyfriend