4 Sister exposes male body
Sayu-sau?
Uh! What's wrong brother?
Ah, you two are busy... sorry
Why are you acting like this at home again?
Eh?
It's more comfortable this way. I can't help it.
Hello again
Eh? You two have met before?
We met in the corridor before, just to say hello
Oh...
Is it okay if I borrow your boyfriend? I'm going to the grocery store, and I need to pick up a conversation on the way or something.
Borrow? He's not an object.
What does it matter?
I've done my job, I'm free now, I can hear it.
Ugh... you're home... that's bad
Whatever you want. Are you going?
Then take care on your way
What? And be careful on the road?
Literally
Well...okay, okay...I'll lend it to me first...
Let's go, boyfriend
I'll wait downstairs in the car and come down when I'm done with my clothes
You told me that when we met before, that's my brother, not my sister
The sister I told you about before was another ordinary person, and that's what she looked like
He's a man of both sexes, so be really careful
Well, I think it's okay though
I'll be waiting for you~