5 ♂ Double-barrelled
hey presto
Nah? Let's talk a bit more before we go home
If we go home, you'll be taken by Sayu
huh?
Did you hear her say something
but being called brother should have revealed it
Nah?
It's embarrassing that you don't say anything
Boyfriend, huh?
You have mixed feelings?
I've been treated like a sister before and I've become comfortable
That's really complicated
but I'm not trying to hide it from you
I just haven't had the chance to tell you that I'm a man
Besides, my boyfriend is really handsome and I wanted to try him out
I'm not lying
Boyfriend, you were actually very comfortable, weren't you?
I was jerking off with my hand...
like this
I'm sorry, you still don't like men?
If you hate it, I'll stop
I don't want to force you
Nah? What do you think?
hesitating?
If you're hesitating...
just kiss like we did before and confirm our feelings?
If you don't want to, just hide your face
Is that okay?
I'll kiss you.
Kiss again...
I'm willing, even if I'm a man
Oh, I'm so happy
Then I can't put you back
Nah? I'm getting a hard-on there...
You know what I mean?
Although I'd like to touch you there
but I also want you to touch me there
I'm fine with just taking off my bottom half...
Take it off?
Let's get comfortable together ~ na?
Wow, you're getting hard too
We're both the same
So...you hold my hola, boyfriend
Hold it tightly~
I really like men more than women
I'm holding you there too
I'm holding someone else's rod while I'm holding my own
You can't do that if you're not both men
Is it exciting?
Look at my face if you're going to wilt
Because of the makeup, you'd think I was a woman
Oh
I'm not being rude, but I'd like to say I look better than Sayu
I think your boyfriend thinks so too
That's why I was so easily seduced before
hola, let's jerk off together
At the beginning, go slower
Sorry, I haven't cum in a week
so it's a bit sensitive
It's so nice~
What does your boyfriend think?
There's no need to hold back the sound
After all, it's in the car
Here I think I can make as much noise as I want
It's nice to have no worries, isn't it?
I masturbate in the car a lot
So, that's... maybe you don't understand
the smell of semen maybe you can still smell it
So shy...
so comfortable
How about kissing and doing it at the same time?
Move your hands faster
You want to get more comfortable too, don't you?
hola keep the same speed
Boyfriend, you're so skilled
Why are you so good at it?
Is it because you masturbate a lot?
If not, how come you're so...
the force and the technique are just right
It's addictive...
but I'm the one seducing you and I look weak
It's annoying
when I'm so much older
Hmm?
But boyfriend, you've already cum once today with Sayu, right?
In that case, you're cheating
Nah, that's tricky
Stop your hand
The second time around, the orgasm must be slow
You know what boys say, don't you?
Like I said, I haven't had sex in a week
hola so I'm the only one who's going to do it first
Got it?
I don't like it when you don't get to the same stage
Nah?
I'm going to jerk off really hard
Is that good?
The sound is coming out a bit
louder
Don't be so shy, huh?
I love it when men pant
Nah nah like to get jerked off here?
Then I'll lick it for you
The rod jumps a little
So... next...
Do you feel this one?
I'll give you a good jerk off
whispering in your ear while you're at it
It's a little dangerous
I'm getting a little soft
so... hold my rod again
this time, both of them together
Hold both rods and jerk them together
Nah?
Yeah, I like that.
hola, hold it
Oh no, it's so erotic just looking at it
Well, we've both got a lot of patience juice flowing
I'm so shy
Put that on the rod...
Yeah... that's it...
Yeah... just jerk it like that
like you would if you were masturbating...
jerking off hard
It's so good
glans against glans
It's a special feeling
my head is going to spin out
Harder...hold it harder too
Let's squeeze the patience juice and get comfortable at the same time
This...crap...
I can't... I think I'm going to cum
I'm getting my balls up
Stop your hand
Hold on a second
it's trembling
My boyfriend's is twitching too
The semen is flowing up
huh
We're both on the verge of cumming.
Nah? Let's change hands
I'll do it this time
hola
That's awesome, that's hot
both of their rods are about to cum
but we can't cum yet
Hmm?
Wouldn't it be better if we played a little longer?
It would be a shame to cum right away in such an erotic game
Like this, the patience juice is mingling
Doing what girls can't do...
and become more comfortable, right?
Nah?
It's so wet and slippery.
I'm losing strength in my back
Let's kiss
It's so good
My boyfriend's face is so engrossed
I guess it's the same for me
So...let's start jerking off
I can't cum yet
Hold off on cumming for now
so good... jerking off together is so good
so comfortable what is this?
it's the feeling of the rod making the rod feel good
my balls are already lifting up
No, I can't cum
I'm holding back too
Let's hold it together
but I'm about to cum
Oh no
I almost came
My boyfriend's seems a little bit easier
really
You're going to become as close to cumming as I am
I told you, you're so cunning
The patience juice is flowing thickly
the kind of white liquid that's almost coming out
slowly approaching that state
Get ready to cum together, eh?
It's so easy to just jerk your boyfriend off there
It's getting better and better...
Imagine cumming without telling your girlfriend
my rod is getting hard
It's awesome~
going for it?
and the cute sounds are getting louder
no cumming yet
I'll stop when I'm about to come out
huh?
Oh no? It's coming out?
Want to cum biu?
So... stop right here
it's shaking so much
I'm at the end of my rope
just like me
So the final stage...
I'll let my boyfriend grab both of them with one hand
and then I'll grab them with both hands~
Harder, harder, harder, harder
Just like that until you cum
A sticky, thick, two-person load of cum in my hand
Yeah, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it.
It's like I'm going to cum soon
You have to cum at the same time
hola moves violently
Ahh~ like this~
Oh no, I'm going to cum... I'm going to cum...
Another semen rushed up
I can't... I can't... I can't...
Let's come together, both of us!
You want to cum?
You can do it.
I'm cumming...ahhhhh
It's a mess
because I've been saving up for a long time and I've shot a lot
My boyfriend came a lot too
Did you feel good?
Ah, it's been a long time
I might be suspicious
Let's just pack up and go home, eh?
Next time you come to my house, let me know
I'll try to be home
Well, even if I have to hide it from Sayu
Let's exchange contact information later
hola, come clean up
There are tissues there, help me
Ah, wait a minute
The last...
huh?