6 ♂ Invasion of the hindquarters
hehehehe Thank you so much for taking Sayu home
She's already asleep and probably won't wake up until morning
The kid can't hold her liquor, but she always likes to drink a lot
as if to make you remember how much she can drink
Next time you drink, see if you can persuade her
Well, but...
It's a great help.
Thank you, gentle boyfriend
Nah? You're going to sleep afterwards anyway.
Don't you want to do something nice before you go back?
Something nice...
You haven't had sex today, have you?
Why don't you do it with me instead of masturbating alone?
And now that the rest of the family is gone
I'd like to do that too...
Yeah? Let's do it~
Not with my hand today, I'll let you stick it in here
You want to put your rod in there, don't you?
You don't like it if it's not a woman's pussy?
My pussy is fine too
It's very comfortable...
I'll clench you tightly
It's definitely good, huh?
You've got an erection, I know.
What would it feel like to penetrate a man's ass?
You must be thinking about it, right?
hola, get undressed and lie down
I'll sit on top and move myself
All naked, all naked, come on!
I'm ready too
What the hell, I'm getting an erection
You're still drunk? Don't wilt on the way
Not only might I get hurt, but I don't like flaccid rods.
I'll put a condom on you
with your mouth
There you go
Just a second...
This is a lubricator for your ass
for easy insertion... this way...
to make it wet and slippery
It's supposed to be applied for a while
but I wanted to taste my boyfriend sooner
so I'm putting it in
Slowly, I'm not so loose there...
Hold on a second
It seems to be working
Put it in...
further in...
all in
How's that? Isn't it tighter than Sayu's pussy?
Nah?
Let's kiss before we can move
hola suck my tongue like a rod
It's so good...
so good at oral sex
But I wish I had a real blowjob
So...this time it's my turn
The rod is getting used to it by and large
I feel like I can move it
I'm going to move it up and down
That's good, that's good
Just the right size
How does your boyfriend feel?
My ass hole, is it comfortable?
It's tight... is it like I'm getting drained of cum?
I'll pump you good
Not a drop left
The rod is so good
Move faster
That's great
I love my boyfriend's rod
It's too selfish to just give it to Sayu
That's definitely too selfish
You'll have to share half of it with me afterwards
After all, we're brother and sister, and this little request...it's okay, right?
I'm sure your boyfriend would like to experience the pussy of a man and a woman too
Right?
But you'll definitely like my pussy better after a few times
Because I know what's most comfortable for my boyfriend
I'm a man after all
my rod is hard inside me and it's ramming everywhere
It doesn't wilt at all
Happy to have sex in your ass, aren't you?
So cute with that look of enjoyment on your face
I'll make you feel better, it's okay if your brain gets confused
No need to be patient
So comfortable
Kisses again
More slobber
Stay close and move
so that you can get to the very top, so nice
The prostate is rubbing against the rod
here...
It's moving!
It's coming inside...
Ahhhh
I can't...
My boyfriend's rod is so good, I can't hold back
If you want to come, you have to do it together!
It'll make my ass tighter and more comfortable
Go on...do it
I can't do it anymore
I can't hold back any longer
Is your boyfriend still okay?
The rod isn't twitching and it seems to be relaxing
I'm always a little angry...
Then clench it tighter...
jerking you off with your ass hole
Oh shit, I feel like I'm going to come even faster
Oh my god!
but yeah, my boyfriend's already twitching a bit there
That was nice just now
I'm so happy
Then let's move closer together
I'll hold back the pleasure and wiggle, but boyfriend, feel free to get comfortable
I'm thrusting in and out of my ass, and I'm shaking more.
Oh no, I'm going!
The rod is throbbing and throbbing
Isn't that nice?
My girlfriend is sleeping next door
I'm about to ejaculate while making love
Cheating on my dick
spasming so lustfully
saying "I'm cumming, I'm cumming"
Nah? Do you want to cum?
getting milked by my ass and wanting to cum hot and creamy?
You can
You've left Sayu behind, and you're already thinking about cumming, right?
Let's cum!
Cum in my girlfriend's brother's ass
Cum in your girlfriend's brother's ass
I'm sure it'll give you a better ejaculation experience than Sayu
Leave it to me, eh?
hola, I'm going to move hard!
so good, my rod is so hard, so good
my head is about to get lighter...
so good
I want to come with you...
I want to be more patient
Oh no, I'm going to die, my ass is going to come
I can't get my pussy to come
I can't, I'm going, I'm going
Boyfriend, come too... together... swing your waist together
Cumming out biu
hola, move your waist
Cum in
this feels... I can't... I can't
I'm going
I can't help it, I can't
I'm going to come
I'm coming
I just screamed so loudly
It's good that Sayu's not awake...
Was it good?
Did you feel good?
Is it nice to have sex in my ass?
It's a shame to pull it out...
just leave it like that for a while
It's so nice
It's been a long time since I've found someone who's so good together, it's great
We'll have to do it again too