7 ♂ Masturbating pseudo-vagina while giving a blowjob
Nah? Boyfriend, that...
Do you have the strength to do it again?
I came once, but I haven't come yet
I always feel like I'm feeling it again when I'm snuggled up like this
Nah?
Okay?
Yeah...it's a little hard to take away your boyfriend's "virginity"
I get it
So... is it okay to use your mouth?
I like the feeling of swallowing to the very bottom and having a little bit of pain in my throat, don't I?
And while I'm doing that, I'm also masturbating
Just watch your boyfriend, okay?
I can't sleep today if I don't have a good time
Nah?
Please, can we?
So...your boyfriend is sitting on the bed like this
I'll sit on the floor
This way, it's easier to touch the rod, right?
So...can I lick it now?
I need to get it erect soon
It's getting hard, even though it still smells like a condom.
How does it feel in my mouth?
Warm and comfortable?
I can't seem to feel it without licking it
Nah?
How's that?
It's good, hard, and the glans is so big
It's nice, isn't it?
I can't... I can't stand it anymore
I want to jerk off
Look at my cock...
I'm just giving you a lick and I'm getting an erection
I'm going to start masturbating... please watch me jerk off
It's so nice
I'm sorry... it's so nice to look at a rod and then masturbate
I forgot about your side
I'll take it for you
It's so good
How can I resist masturbating to such a hard thing?
Come again~
Endurance juice, it's delicious
If I'm cumming with such dirty juice...
I can't help but want to jerk off even harder
Really, you're an idiot, boyfriend~
I feel so good
Look at my rod
I'm also getting a lot of patience juice from my rod
hola like this on the glans...
Oh no, oh no
I need some of your boyfriend's too
Putting patience juice on my rod
It's on there, it's sticky
hola both of them mixed together
insert it a bit more, it's a nice throat pussy
The tight texture you're dying to experience, right?
Nah? Boyfriend hola
Look at my rod and get comfortable at the same time
It's nice, isn't it?
I'm also getting comfortable with the rod in my throat
Oh no, I'm going to cum
Look, the rod is trembling
Masturbating with my boyfriend's rod as a snack is great!
It's not good if I come first...
I'll let it go here
So I'll just jerk you off with my throat pussy first
It's starting to shake
You want more of that?
The throat blowjob that Sayu couldn't do
hola, let's do it again!
shuddering so violently...
you're going to cum?
My balls are already up...
I'm about to cum
Yes, come on
So...I'll keep masturbating too
We'll come together at the end
watch me cum so much and cum down my throat too
Hold on a second
I'm going to masturbate
want to lick
Oh no, I'm going to cum soon
I'm probably going to come out
Let's make you come then
Let's cum together and get comfortable
I'm going... I can't
Look at me cumming...
I'll swallow it all
Come on out
Look at that...
Thank you for your hospitality
It's so thick and delicious
there's still some left
Nah? Do you want a taste of mine too?
So many shots
It's okay if you don't eat it all
Just a little bit will do
a little bit on your pinky...
lick this?
Ahh~
Don't look so embarrassed
I'll be sad
It's delicious, isn't it?
Come on, say "delicious"
It's been a long time
It's almost time for you to go home
I'll take you home in my car
It's easier, right?
It's okay, that's all for today, eh?
You get changed and I'll wash my hands
Let's go next door and see Saya's sleeping face
After all, I've done something bad today without her knowledge
I have to apologize
Then you can wait for me