9 ♂ hindquarters violated
Eh, faster than I thought I'd leave
There's no need to be in such a hurry
You want to say goodbye to Sayu and have sex with me that badly?
Oh
Eh?
No, that's it.
Nah?
Really, you're a bad boy.
That's cheating, huh?
By the way, are you ready for this?
I said it's my day to insert
Is it okay?
Of course I'll be gentle with you, but I'd like to ask your opinion
Is it really okay?
I'm not going to push you if you want to be backed in
You're a pervert who wants to be taken out of your vagina
I'm about to be violated at will
but it's okay
Next, I'm going to make love to you
hola, take off your clothes
Lie down
Nah nah it's really okay to eat you
This body of yours
There's something deeply moral about violating your sister's boyfriend that's really exciting
hola come and kiss
My boyfriend's favorite tongue
I'll lick you with this today too
I've been kissing for a long time, and it's even more intense than before.
So...it's my turn to fight back
I'm getting a boner!
What should I do, jerk you off like I always do?
I can't help you, you really like my hands
So I'll give you a little jerk off before I take your pussy away
hola
the panting sound is so cute
Seeing you react like that makes me want to bully you
Do you want to be bullied?
You want more?
The rod feels good, doesn't it?
It's good. It's good.
Nah?
Boyfriend, you're about to get a hard rod in your ass!
Do you understand?
I won't forgive you if you don't swallow my whole erection!
I'm looking forward to it
Well...I'd like to get in early, so let's stop here
Lift your legs up
like a woman making love
Yeah, yeah, just keep it in that humiliating position
to lubricate your ass hole
I'm going to touch it
Too nervous
Just relax a little more
Yeah, yeah
That should do it
So, first put your finger in
If you put a stick in at the beginning, your boyfriend's pussy will be ruined
Oh
hola put your thumb in slowly
Is that okay?
The tip of the finger is swallowed
Again, it's okay... swallow it all
Let the ass hole open and close
It's going in
Eat it all up
What an erotic ass hole
Does it feel special?
pfft pfft pfft pfft pfft pfft sound
but that's just the little thumb, I'll pull it out first
It's sucking so hard
Next is the middle finger
It's thicker than the one just now... can you fit it in?
That's good... it's in... so erotic
Have you ever played with it yourself?
Here you are
It's already swallowed inside
So keep it like that
Let's touch you there
The rod wants to be jerked off again, right?
Nah?
You're getting a quick erection again
So horny
hola, the prostate too...
I can feel it...
and it's erect...
I can find it
It seems to be saying "play with it"
for you to become a woman's body quickly
teasing in two places at once
Nah, my rod and my ass are being violated at the same time
My boyfriend is like a woman with her thighs spread wide apart
You're not going to show that to Sayu, are you?
If they saw that, they'd probably be dumped
But it's okay
Even if that happens, I'll still be your sex partner
The kind of sex partner that would be my top priority
penetration of the rod being penetrated by the rod
gagging on a rod being gagged on a rod
and so on, to train you to be more than a normal girlfriend can satisfy
Well, that's about it now
hola, your ass is already loosening up
almost as much as you want my rod
Let's start thrusting
finger, pull it out
hola, my boyfriend, look at me there
playing with your ass hole is causing me to get an erection there too
hard and stiff
Nah? Can I put it all in?
I'm thicker than normal there
a little worried
But I'm sure you can swallow it all if you're your boyfriend
After all, it's better than inserting my own rod into Sayu's pussy
I'm a big pervert who prefers to be penetrated by my rod
Is that right?
Oh, shit.
I'm going to cum soon if I watch my boyfriend jerk off
I have to hold back...
So, I'm going to put it in
No condom, please forgive me
Because it's my boyfriend's first time
so I want to make a mess in there
It's so tight
a little hard?
You relax a little bit
Breathe in...breathe out...
Well, that seems to do it
hola, one more time
The glans is in
hmmm keep that up
swallow my erect rod inside
That's good.
Just a little more... push harder
until it's inside
It's in
Is it uncomfortable?
You'll get used to it soon.
It's okay.
Until then
I'll jerk you off here
hola Boyfriend's favourite rod
being penetrated and jerked off at the same time
It's a pressure feeling, it's very comfortable
Now it's more comfortable than ever before, isn't it?
Look how much patience is coming out
Putting the juice on the rod
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
My ass is getting so comfortable with the rod in it
Okay, pause
Is my pussy getting used to my rod?
I'm the one who's doing it today
I'll move slowly
Ah, it's so tight
Boyfriend, this is great too
This ass hole
I've never experienced such pleasure
Is it okay?
If it hurts, let me know
It might not feel so good at first
hola I'll jerk you off gently
Like this, remember what it feels like to have a nice ass
It's really tight in there
I'm not even moving, but I'm feeling it
It's like being held at full force, it's so tight
I've only just leaked prostate fluid and I'm already about to ejaculate
but I'm still trying to thrust faster
because I wanted to violate my boyfriend so badly
Oh no, this
A woman can't beat that
this tightness
it's amazing
My boyfriend's cock is also fully erect
It's so horny
Oh no, my balls are up!
No, stop for a moment
That's so good, that's a foul
The rod is trembling
Before we stop, let's kiss
because it's so comfortable and probably more sexual than usual
Next, let's do it together
This way, the rod will be pressed against my belly, and that's the best part, isn't it?
Just move your waist like you did earlier
hola your rod will be stimulated too
your pussy and your rod at the same time
but, as it happens, I'm still feeling it too much
This is so good, I want to rub it as much as I can
This is so good, it's great
I love my boyfriend's ass.
I want to penetrate every day
I love it, it's so good
Your rod is pushing against my belly like crazy
It's bad just to have an erection, isn't it?
wanting to cum?
but if I keep thrusting so comfortably, oh no...
my balls are rising again.
No...
I feel like cumming
What should I do? Is it okay to cum in there?
It's okay to put all my hot stuff in my boyfriend's ass, right?
It's okay, right?
It's gonna be okay, right?
I'll also jerk my boyfriend's erection so hard that you'll cum as much as you want
Cumming together and going blank
hola ass hole clench so I can come comfortably
Tightly. Can you do it?
Yeah, it hurts a little
It's like I'm about to be drained of every last drop
I'm so happy
So, let's have an orgasm
Boyfriend, no!
I'm going to come just for a moment, like this!
My boyfriend's dick is rising up too!
Cum is about to come out
my balls are clenching up
I can't... I'm going to come...
Oh no!
Can I cum?
Can I?
Squeeze all the cum out of your ass and swallow it
hola boyfriend make a mess of my palm too so it's covered in cum, eh?
No, it's coming, it's going, it's going
Let's come together
No, it's coming out
I'm coming out
My boyfriend came so much too
You're so tight when you come, it's like you're draining your balls
I want to experience it again
Thank you for your hospitality
By the way, when will we meet again?
It's okay if it's not a day to play with Sayu, let me know
Like a whole day at a hotel next time? How's that sound?
I'll let you use my ass hole as much as you want
And then we'll trade off, okay?
Hmm?
Why are you hesitating?
If you don't decide on a date for our next meeting, I won't pull out my rod.
My boyfriend is already mine~
I'm not letting go