01 - First sweet kiss hand to hand
Woof~ I'm back
Sorry ~ it took me a while to get back from my club activities today
I'm asking you, Woof, during the time I was at school
Have you been a good housekeeper?
Well, that's great!
Today is exactly one month since Woof came to my house
You're getting used to this room, aren't you?
Also, any comments on the taste of the food?
any toys you want, you can ask me
and I'll get Daddy to get them for you right away
So what's up, Woof?
Woof is a pet
You can't speak in human language
You have to use woof when answering your owner's questions
or ow
Just so that Woof's feelings can be conveyed to me
So call it
If you don't behave, you won't be rewarded today
Come on, give a shout
Well done~ It's great to scream out properly
little woof
With such an expectant look on your face
Do you want a kiss from your master?
Really, Woof is so greedy
But daddy said not to be too indulgent
Let's talk about kisses another time
Let's just touch your head this time
You're such a good boy
That's great
That, little woof
just looking at Woof makes me want to give you more love
I like Woof a lot
Woof's face isn't that handsome either
He's lazy and doesn't like to exercise much
He doesn't have a good memory either
Even so, it's cute
What about me at first
I didn't really have the idea of having a pet
But when I saw your sad face in the shop after being sold
and I thought I had to protect this child
and after that I convinced my mum and dad
and told them that I would take care of you before I bought you back
So, Woof
If you like the kisses you get from your owner
then kiss me all you want I like you that much
Woof has a longing look on his face
Do you want to stick your tongue in some more?
That's a great answer
Even though it's forbidden to do such things before marriage
but I'll make an exception for you
You look like you're salivating
That look, you want more
You don't know what you want
The little woof's mouth is watering
No way!
Woof needs to be a good pet and be able to stand up for himself in any situation
Don't make that face
A pet that misbehaves will be thrown away by its owner
I'm just kidding
Okay
From now on I'll take my time to make Woof a good pet
Until then, you can count on me!
So, I'll clean up the drool from the corners of your mouth with my tongue and lips
Woof, swaying nervously like this
Don't want to kiss anymore or is there some other reason
Woof?
underneath the little woof
also, I'm sorry, it's hard, isn't it?
You don't have to apologize
Woof is a male and a boy
Even though I'm the owner, if you're kissing a girl
It's normal to get excited when you're kissing a girl
little woof
Let me help Woof calm down if I can
After all, it's because of me that she's like this
I've never done anything like that before
It's okay if it's for Woof
What does Xiao Wang think?
That's a great answer
So let me take off Woof's clothes
Little Wang's ...... is great
Well, it's not that bad
It's the first time I've seen it so I'm a bit shocked
It's great to have such a big erection.
You are too
First of all, I used my hand to hold Woof's rod
How does it feel?
Tell me if it's uncomfortable or if it hurts
Great!
Keep squeezing and moving up and down like this, right?
So
How about
Is this speed enough?
faster like that?
with such a comfortable expression
Even if you don't ask, you can tell by the look on your face that it's more comfortable
Great job communicating your feelings to your owner without saying a word!
Great job!
Reward for a job well done
Woof looks very comfortable
tongues intertwined and kissing while being stimulated by her master's hand
Very impressive...
Very impressive that Woof is so comfortable
We'll give you a reward for being a great little woof
More tongue kisses for Woof
I love the look on Woof's face!
The look of melting comfort
white liquid is spilling out of the tip of the woof
It's the kind of stuff that boys get when they're comfortable and they're about to ejaculate
That's right.
I've got this nasty fluid coming out of my hand
Don't look so sorry
I don't care if my hands get dirty but I don't care if I can make Woof feel good
I said, "Woof
put the erotic fluid on your fingers like this
Get it lubricated and then move the head
This will make it more comfortable
The expression looks very comfortable
It feels good to have your master playing with your head with his fingers
I'm so happy that I can make my little woof feel better
It's great to be able to take good care of your pet as an owner
I'm making my hands and mouth comfortable for my little woof
What's wrong with that trembling?
Yeah, I know
Yes, that's it
while tongue kissing
while jerking you off and jerking you off and making you smell horny
Woof comes when he wants to come
It's okay to get more white on your hand
I can't do it anymore... I'm going to cum already?
Cum in my hand
Yes, please ejaculate
I'm cumming in a big way...
I'm getting a white colour from the woof
Don't worry about it, it's great that it's so thick and white
You've done a great job
Here's the reward
Good job
Say, Woof
Make a deal with me
You can't tell mum and dad what I did for Woof today
If you get caught doing such erotic things with your pet
We'll have to throw Woof away
Woof will be disposed of
So that's the deal between us
You'll keep it, right?
Great~ So what do we do next?
Let's play a game of ball toss after a long time
Oh yes
I'm sorry, but I'd like to play with you a little longer.
but it's already time for the appointment with Dad
Woof, can you go home by yourself today?
So as the owner, I'll give you a command
Go back to your cage and get a good night's sleep, woof!