02- Kinky sweet ear licking handjob
Ah, Woof
Sorry, did I wake you up?
I'm here because it's going to be cold and I'm worried about you today
I'm sorry. I wanted you to sleep in the house.
Mum and Dad said it's dangerous not to stay together at night until you're neutered
But I know, Woof wouldn't do anything like that
So ...... to keep Woof warm
Hold on to you
How about
very warm?
Like this
Then hold Woof like this
rub your head it's hard to sleep in a little house like this in the middle of winter
It's great that you've been able to endure it so far
Later, when Mummy and Daddy are asleep
I'll come quietly like this to keep the little woof warm
Forgive me.
Well, that was a good answer.
But... Shh!
It's late at night and if you make a lot of noise, you'll be exposed.
Well, so next time, keep the barking down.
Rub your head, you're good
I'll give Woof a reward
Come on, close your eyes
What's wrong, Woof?
Is it just your lips that don't feel satisfied?
want to intertwine their tongues in a deep kiss
Yes, let me warm you up from the inside out
And twist your body like this
I get it... I'm getting excited again
So you don't have to look sorry, Woof
As an owner, you have a duty to take care of your woof.
So leave it to me
Take off your clothes like you just did
It's so big
Woof, I've been studying a bit myself since I let you back in the hut
ways to make Woof more comfortable
You know what?
And that is
whispering nasty things in Woof's ear
just so you can't make a lot of noise now either
but will do a lot of intense erotic things to you quietly
Woof's cock... no, it's gotten bigger
And it's jumping a bit
Woof, the penis
Do you like being whispered to by girls?
Yes, I do
I know...
so that Woof can get turned on...
hold the rod
Repeat it in your ear as you jerk up and down
How was it? Did I feel good?
Really, don't make a sound, I don't care if it's exposed
I'm already too comfortable to adjust the volume of my voice
Let's do it again, this time quietly
Woof, woof, woof to tell your master you're comfortable
Come on~ woof
Yes, it's great!
I know, like earlier
It's nice to kiss and do it at the same time
but now in a cramped doghouse with the owner close by
while your owner whispers erotic words in your ear to turn you on a little more
Yes, you can!
with a full erection under your master's panting
I'll take care of that nasty rod to the end, too
little woof
You like that, don't you?
I know, I understand
Perverted and nasty little woof that turns you on
Woof
Nasty attack from the master
Don't lose
Meat stick Don't lose~
very comfortable
The approaching spit
nasty snorting
saliva-soaked tongues in your ears that you can't stand
your body and your rod twitching
you feel it
The sensation of your ears being stimulated is very pleasant
Good answer...
I'll give you a reward
Do you feel it?
Bouncy, soft breasts
They're pressing against Woof's body
the first time I touched my breasts, I could feel them even through my clothes
It's exciting, isn't it?
And the feet are intertwined
and the body is close together
listening to the whispers
entwining their feet together
after the breasts are pressed against the body
while enjoying the sweet smell of their master's body alone
the rod is being fondled by the master's hand
of course
and not forgetting the ears
Isn't that great?
I know it is!
Just look at Woof's face and I'll get it all
What's wrong?
while looking like he wants to say something
while leaning over and rubbing his lower body
you don't have to say it, but you don't know what you want to do
No, you can't talk, little woof
Only use your woof to express your thoughts
As long as that's all I can understand
Come on, say it
I understand how the little woof feels
Like earlier
I want to cum on my master's hand
I know
but no
Because if you're raised to be a useless pet who can't even hold back his ejaculation
you won't be able to fulfill your mission as an owner
so you need to be educated
not to be a useless dog that just ejaculates
but to teach them to be able to hold back their ejaculation and to be able to handle themselves
handsome male
And I
like a strong and handsome male
and I
want you to be the male that your master likes
Got it?
In that case
you can't lose to your master's hand
and of course the lips
and panting
and nostrils
Don't lose if you get it
You can't lose the rod, it's your master's order
You can't lose to your master's great handjob
The look on the little woof's face is really cute
I want to cum but I can't because of my master's orders
I'm going to have to push harder because I'm so embarrassed.
faster and more intense hand movements
What's wrong, Woof, holding my body with a tearful face
Are you begging your master to make you cum?
Is it true that you can't hold back anymore?
Yes, I'm trying very hard
rewarding the clever woof for persevering
at the end
like this
I'm going to jerk off with all my might
I can cum after I give the go-ahead...
Here we go
There you go, Meat Boy
Meat stick, meat stick, meat stick, meat stick
It's going, isn't it?
The rod is going, isn't it?
The semen is coming up from the sperm sac
and the rod is going
Is it coming?
Are you gonna cum?
Yes, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, biubiubiu
Woof is so good, he's cumming more than he did before he went to bed
And it's so thick too
Because I've been able to hold on to it, I've been able to cum as much as this comfortably
That's amazing
It's amazing that you can hold out like that, Woof
To the amazing Woof
A rewarding kiss, Woof, for all your hard work
Woof, how does it feel to have me take care of my rod like this?
If your rod gets bigger in the future, let your master calm it down!
And let your master educate you so that you can become a strong male
Yes, I know... and after that if you hear me say, stand up...
that's a sign that your master wants to take care of your rod
undress yourself
Well, it's good to be honest and follow your master's orders
Rub your head
So, Woof, are you going for a walk now to change your mood?
Yeah, a walk... you'll get scolded if you don't walk on the floor in the morning
Now there's no one outside
Even if you walk on the ground, it's fine
Woof will be tired if he walks on the ground too
How about
Yeah, I know
I'll go and bring the rope for the walk...
Just a moment