03 - Shake S Whispering Leg Rape
Woof are you having a hard time with your neck?
I'd like to have a looser one though
but I'm sorry I only have this leash at home
Yeah, that's right.
So the route for today is
to the park near the school
and then back again
Do you think it's okay to take this old route?
Well, let's get going before the sun comes up
Oh, it's cold
Woof, if mum and dad find out about this
I won't get my pocket money this month
Keep it a secret for me!
Oh, that's a good answer
But if you're found out
you'll probably be sent to an institution too
We're in the same boat
Don't be so scared
If you and I don't say anything, we won't be found out
And even if they do
I'll definitely protect you, Woof
I'm asking you, Woof
What do you think of me, what do you think of me as your master?
I asked my mum and dad and made two vows to get them to agree to keep you
The first vow was said before
to make you happy, to educate you properly and to take care of you until the end
So I've thought a lot about making you happy and I've taken care of you a lot
I ask you, little woof
Woof do you think you're happy to have me as your master?
Oh thank you, I'm glad you answered.
Woof, shall we take a short break?
Hugs~
It's okay, no one's watching us
And now we're right in the shadow of the streetlights
It's going to be okay
Woof, open your mouth
Really, Woof, you're getting excited too fast
You're up to my thighs with that thing
It's still out there, you're still excited, aren't you?
Let's see, it's still a while before sunrise, so let's do a shot here
Yeah, that's fine, Woof.
I'm Woof your master
I'll take care of it when Woof's rod gets bigger
That's normal
So, come on?
Really, this pet is a bad boy
Well, I command
Woof, stand up!
Come on, that's the master's order
The master's order is absolute
I told you that when I bought you
Do you think you can disobey them?
Come on, stand up
Take off all your clothes
Take them off
Oh, that's good
You're so good at following your master's orders
But even though it's the master's command
but you're naked outside now
Pervert
I know that!
Woof you're a perverted dog who likes to be scolded by girls
When I was teaching you about your rod
you had a perverted look on your face too
So ...... from now on
I'm going to teach you little woof to be a jitterbug
Oh, your body is shaking a little
So ...... used to make Woof comfortable today
is here, you know?
where your rod has been rubbing against my thighs since a while ago
the right amount of fat, the right amount of soft, white thighs
standing in an absolute field of knee-high socks and skirts
to grip your rod
and turn into a jiggly face
Come on, a pair of thighs against your rod, open the gaping flesh
Put your rod in there
Come on, your thighs are close together.
as if to show how soft the thighs and pussy are
Just a little bit more, just a few millimeters away from touching the rod
Hey, just so you don't have time to enjoy the softness of the thigh meat
One breath deeper
and it makes a lustful sound and the whole thing goes in
How's your thighs and pussy?
Though her body is thin, her white thighs are full of tension
You can't help but pull back when you're held by such thighs, can you?
But when you're pulling back, your breathing is disordered, isn't it?
Oh, you're a jitterbug!
Just move your thighs back and forth like that ......
thighs reverse rape ...... helplessly violated by thigh pussy
It's great to be violated by a full thigh, isn't it?
I'm going to be violated here too
thighs ...... up to the root of the rod ......
keep staking it out making the sound of flesh slapping against flesh
of course while jerking erotically like this
while the ear violates the words
I'm getting turned on too
excited
I'm not allowed to make a sound that a young lady with a good education would never make
nasty snort
directly into her ears and blowing into them
I said, "I'll change the angle of your thigh swing
if you rub it like that, you see?
there's something like fabric rubbing against the rod
You know what that is, don't you? It's my ...... underwear
change this deeper angle and violate the rod with the base of your thighs through your panties
sinking the rod into the lower recess of the panties and rubbing it
so that the thighs can rub against the opening of the glans
the real uncovered pussy through the thin layer of fabric
A virgin pussy that has been mature for over 15 years and is thick
And ...... you get it?
getting wetter and wetter as it keeps rubbing against the rod
and it smells indescribably lustful
the smell of hormones, the scent of the rod
The love juices are already flooding
seeping out of soaked panties
pussy indirectly wetting the rod
Now, you care what you see under your skirt, don't you?
Yes, you can!
Come on, I'll lift up my skirt and show you
Well ...... how about the moment when you lift up your skirt
erotic hormones bursting out from underneath, right?
The sweet, seductive smell of love juices
the rod of the flesh craves it so much that the mind goes blank
All I can think of is the thought of sex
to make you realize that I am the best female
and you look closely at my panties
pure white panties soaked with love juices
with the outline of the seam
Isn't it hard?
It's hard, isn't it?
and you're not a man until you've sown in it
but you can't do anything about it
not only that, but being raped with my thighs
the jiggly juice is flowing all over the place
I want to have sex, I want to have sex, I want to have sex, I want to have sex, I want to have sex
Seeing the pussy in front of me
The love juices from the pussy drenching the rod and making it hard to resist ......
So ...... the end of the line
Tell the jiggly dog I raped a good thing
I'm wearing lace-up panties today
Just a little tug on the lace up sides ......
or even just rub the panties a little bit
my bottom might be completely naked
That's for perverted jiggly dogs who just want to stick their fingers in my pussy and fuck
That's pretty understandable, right?
pushing his waist up between my thighs and pushing his panties off ......
maybe we can get the ties undone and see the uncovered pussy
If the laces of my panties are untied
what would happen if you swung your thighs at the current angle?
then I would have sex with my pussy
Even though you're not allowed to have sex with your master
but if you accidentally put it in, there's nothing you can do about it, is there?
I'll give you a hint...
the right tether is coming loose
Have you ever imagined the moment when a girl's panties come undone?
The moment when the thin piece of cloth that's been wrapped around your pussy all day falls off
the steam bursting out of the sealed pussy
The sweet aroma of pussy fills your nostrils
Can't hold back anymore
With that in mind you keep pushing your hips
vowing to eat your pussy dry
Oh, you're obviously a jerky dog with a scary look in your eyes
Did that get you excited?
Oh well, let's give it a try
I ...... really rape
Savor it, jitterbug
Put your body weight on it roughly and nastily ......
It's time to sprint!
What's wrong with you? What happened to the momentum?
The scary male eyes have faded and all that's left is a raped female
losing to the rape of my thighs
quickly rubbed with love juices, pussy juices, helplessly violated
To finish it off, the neck ......
Oh, planting strawberries... the pet crest of a jitterbug that can't be erased
You're stamped with proof that you belong to your owner
Master's orders are absolute, right?
Come, I give you the command
Show me your shaky face and get ready to cum
Sperm sacs tighten up and make bitchy noises
If you want to be a bitch so badly, I'll give you the power to do it
Come on, say you feel good
Oh, to be raped and say you feel good
That's disgusting
Come on, cum, cum, cum, cum
You can do it...
Go ahead, cum...
cum...
Get violated by the thighs and pussy, raped and start your jerking cum
Come on, cum, cum
Cum, cum, cum, cum
biubiubiubiu ......
huh hard work
don't pull out yet
just hide it in your skirt
Mmm, good boy
Yeah, that's it
How about I tie a bow on the meat pole with my underwear
That last thrust just untied the panties!
What a shame... 10 more seconds and we'd have had a real fuck
You've lost your chance to show off your virility
Oh, that's good, that's good
Try harder next time
By the way, you're shooting a lot
I can't even fit it between my thighs, it's splattering all over the sides
It's staining my black pantyhose white
It's okay, Woof, you don't have to worry about that
Is your side okay?
Do you feel better?
Oh yeah?
pervert
huh
So it's almost time to go back before mum and dad are up
I didn't get a good walk in today, but I'll wait until tomorrow
When I get back from school, I'll make you something even better than what I did today.
Well, Woof, you really want to do that, don't you?
crossed ends
Look forward to it, Woof