04 - Master's Jitterbug Conditioning Painful Foot Fucks
Woof, I'm back~
Did you have a good time watching the house today too?
Yeah! That's great!
Woof!
Here's a reward, boy!
You've been so good waiting for your master to come home.
Nah, Woofie!
Do you remember the promise you made with me?
We talked about it last night on our walk
When we get back from school, we'll do better things with you than we did yesterday
Yeah! So that's why ......
Now as a rule ......
Stand up if you understand
That's right, it's great to have your pants down properly
Well ...... but
it hasn't gotten any bigger yet
It's okay, it can't be helped
I haven't done the horny thing today either
小汪~再稍來过来~
In your ear ......
Tell you ......
My thoughts
Stupid~
na woof
Little woof is ......
Really ......
disgusting
What do you think? You're just a bad head ......
stupid dog who is not smart
So you say you're stupid~
I told you yesterday
What you usually say yesterday
I had an erection by the time I got back
Something that shouldn't bother the master, right?
I've been thinking about it all day at school today
just in case Woof doesn't have an erection to greet me when I get back ......
Let's just throw the woof away
After I get rid of Woof, I'll buy a new pet.
Give all the love you have for Woofie to a new baby and take care of him
Won't you?
No ......
Then you'll have to fawn over me
so that your master doesn't abandon you ......
To fawn over me, to please me
Come on if I scold the little woof
while looking grateful
while barking like a dog
Got it?
Idiot!
That's right, that's right, woof woof!
That's disgusting!
Jitterbug
Shame, right?
Stupid dog
Woof!
Stupid~
How sad, how sad!
To be kept by a young girl and have to fawn over her to survive
How pathetic
Idiot!
Woof!
unknowingly ......
It was small ......
has become hard
There's a good deal of training to become a jitterbug
so that it can be better than yesterday when I did ......
something more comfortable and exciting than yesterday
I'll do it for you now
Come on, thank me
"Thank you for giving me an erection"
"Thank you for scolding me" and fawning over it
Not true
Don't just bark
fold your arms and put them on your chest
And pant like a dog while you're poking your tongue out
Like a real dog
And then you have to look fawning all the while
while barking like a dog
Come on, you try to do it
No, that's wrong
Do it
Little Wang is really ......
disgusting
Come on Woof go sit down over there
Go to the front of the bed ......
Where you can look up at your master
Sit on the floor
Yeah, that's right, great job
as a reward like this ......
Just give the little woof a cold look
Have fun with that
When you get that look in your eyes
Do you know why I let you sit here, Woof?
Today I want to introduce Woof to the cross-tail
Well, it's just like we talked about
So, if you get it, then ......
Here, I'll lend it to you
Cross your fingers
You'll get it when you see it
feet
The owner's thin, beautiful feet in black knee-high socks
What's wrong with that look?
Hey, can't you ......
still think you can make love to your master?
I said, "Woof
Come down here
Yeah, that's right...
Idiot!
For being a pet, a jerky dog
how can you do that?
If you get it ......
just go back and sit down
That's right and
Woof liked it ......
my feet
all the time with that disgusting stare
If you want to see it so badly, look
Just lift it up to your face
Well ...... how about that?
The master's feet are coming right up to his face
Well, it's still five centimeters from your face
Let's get you even closer
Four centimeters
three centimeters
so close that you can feel the warmth even if you're not directly touching
two centimeters
one centimetre
Most of my immediate view is taken up by the back of my feet ......
There you go!
zero centimeters
Because my knee socks are blocking the view becomes black
It's the best when you have your master's foot on your face
I have gym class today
sweat and body heat and the girls' horny hormones
soaked in it
become more than just ......
and even harder than it was just
just now
pervert~
What's wrong?
Getting turned on though ......
but with a pained look
also oh I can't breathe
my nose and my mouth are covered by the backs of my feet
I'll just let you suffocate
Even if I kill you
All Rights for Pets ......
They all belong to me as the owner
Sorry, you're scared, aren't you?
I wouldn't do something like that
Okay, put your feet down now
And then what?
little woof
Do you want to cross your tails or not?
Yes, I guess
Yes, I'll take it!
No
Yeah! That's amazing!
Then grab my feet with both hands from the left and right
Well that's it! Keep it like that ......
Just put it in front of the cock that's making you hard
That's right, just put your cock in the gap between the soles of your feet that are pressed tightly together
Yeah, go ahead and do it
Deeper and deeper
Deeper, you see
Please~
Well done
Successful penetration in the warm pussy of the master's feet
congratulations on virginity graduation
Happy, aren't you, for taking away human rights ......
I'm only being used as a dog
and graduated from virginity
Graduating from virginity with the owner's foot ......
Come on, let's get started
and pussy made of master's feet ......
The first intercourse of the
master
You have to have sex to do that
you move yourself up and down without moving your feet
Do it
Yeah, you're pretty good at it
From heel to toe ......
all day in leather shoes, the soles of the master's well-warmed feet
Let your cock feel it fully
I said, woof
Here, I'll lend it to you
Mmm! It's a mirror.
I'll just leave it here casually
Keep an eye on it
Sitting on the floor ......
jiggly face rubbing his cock while grabbing a girl's leg
Remember this scene well
It's so sad, it's so pathetic
But it's exciting
pulling the glans with your toes
tighten the base of the cock with the sole of your foot
I can't put a finger on it even though I'm being looked at like this
but I'm so excited
I can't stop the flow of jiggly juice
I can't stop having sex with the soles of girls' feet
it's disgusting
Woof, you have to thank your owner for giving you a tail
A "woof" with a fawning expression and a thank you
Come on, do it!
Woof woof~
Idiot!
Here's your reward
And as a reward, I'll lift up my skirt for you
You see
you can see it, can't you?
The same pure white panties as yesterday
Lace-up panties that are just like yesterday
Why don't I undo my panties?
Your reaction speaks for itself
Do you want to see it so badly?
Master's pussy
wet ...... want to see it?
Yes, the straps are coming off
In exchange just close your eyes for a while
Yes, good boy
Then it's ......
The ties are untied
now you can see it if you open your eyes
Master's real pussy
But, no, I can't open my eyes yet.
Well, there's still work to be done
Woof, good boy!
I'll give you a head rub if I reach out
Well, be good
like this ......
Well done~
You can open your eyes now!
I can't see anything
Do you get it already?
I've tied my chubby to Woof's face
You can feel it directly, right?
the warmth of a young girl's freshly removed underwear
and then a look of eroticism
Come on, take a deep breath and feel it
sha~sha~
Taste the scent of the female
S'ha~s'ha~
The smell of freshly removed underwear
Sigh~Sigh~
To give you a thorough taste
because it's so thick, it's like I can't breathe
My mind is going blank
The smell of pussy panties all day long
Every time I breathe, the pleasure keeps coming into my head
like a charm, several times more pleasant than just now
The heat rushes up and down into the testicles
I wanted to make love to my pussy but couldn't...
My head felt strange
The jealousy that has nowhere to go but on the soles of my feet
Come on, let's make love to the soles of our feet
Let the intercourse with the soles of the feet
become more violent, come on
Shoo*n
Let's give it all we've got
Rubbing hard, rubbing hard, rubbing hard to let out the discontent
It's disgusting. It's disgusting.
Whenever I gasp for air from excitement
the scent of panties that had just been in the pussy's place rammed into the nostrils
which rightly turns you on even more
rubbing your cock against the soles of your feet as you drip more jiggly juice
Now the little woof is very humiliating
loser dog, jitter dog
Woof, I told you, because I like handsome, strong males
That's why I trained Woofie, right?
But now Woof
but now Woof has become a masculine androgynous jitterbug
Do you know why?
It's okay for Woof to be handsome or to be a disgraceful jitterbug
because I already have a manly and handsome man
I'll tell you what
And yes, turn your head sideways
Hold your feet like you did before
while shaking the M and crossing the tail
Well, that's amazing
to the little woof ......
Say one good thing
I'm meeting a guy tomorrow
it's the one my dad is going to give me as an engagement
Unlike Woof, he's big and muscular and has the look of a man
And then ...... must have a strong sex drive too
A jiggly dog wearing underwear and rubbing his cock on the bottom of his feet would never be able to compete
handsome man
I fell in love with him just by looking at him
If it was him
This body that Winky is dying for is at his disposal
My pussy is completely open for him
He can cum every day
but unfortunately, Woof can only come with the soles of my feet
There was no intention of showing you pussy to begin with
Usually it's not something you can see, right?
I've been playing with the little woof
Idiot
Come on
Order
Use the bottom of your foot ......
Let's have an orgasm
It's a total jitterbug look
rubbing the soles of your feet while panting in your underwear like that
I'll count down to zero and then I'll come!
You have to obey orders
Hmm? What's wrong?
Is it too comfortable?
Too comfortable?
Couldn't resist until you got to zero? You want me to stop?
I can't... I can't stop fucking... I can't stop doing this... I can't stop cumming...
So, I said to hold it in until the end, so hold it in
Come on, Woof's nipples are squeezing you hard like this
Keep squeezing until you say you'll hold off and come
gradually squeeze harder and harder~ See, you won't stop until you say so
That's it
little woof~
I'm not going to let the jittery woof touch me, though
but I will have real pussy sex with a handsome boy!
I'm not sure I'm happy about that
I can't stop having fun even though I'm not happy about it
I can't stop being happy.
The little woof can only do it with the soles of his feet
Oh, so sad
I'll squeeze your nipples a little tighter
I can't do it anymore?
cum is pushing straight to my balls ready to ejaculate a humiliating jiggly M cum
It's already at 1 oh it's already cumming 1 it's cumming 1 it's cumming 1 1
Come on
0 it's 0 0 0
Cum*n
Don't stop even when you're cumming until you're done
Cum, cum, cum, cum