05-Two's a Thing
Woof, I've shot so much, my feet are covered in it
Stand up and let me untie you
I'm exhausted
Tired? Or is there something surprising?
Well, Woof, come to bed, it's cold on the floor
Hold hands
Nah, what just happened
I'm going to get married by my father
I said we'd meet tomorrow, right?
It was a lie to get Woof excited
I wanted to say that
but it's true, but liking him is a lie
I've only met him a few times, and he's not really my type.
as the opposite sex or otherwise, I don't like
and haven't spoken to each other at all
I'm sorry I've kept it from you, I thought I'd tell you someday
Woof, you said you liked me, so it was hard for me to say it
Even if I did, it's a foregone conclusion, there's no way out
I think you know that, too, Xiao Wang
Most of the males are now hard workers or pleasure pets
Human males are rare
So maybe the average girl can't find a mate and get married
but my family has a history of working with such traditions
if there's no male child, the family will look for an heir
to bring in a son-in-law to keep the family prestigious
It's a custom from the old days, it can't be helped
But to marry someone you don't like and to have children
I hated it, so I talked to my mum and dad about it a lot
but they didn't agree with me
So, when I saw the leftover woof in the shop
I'm going to buy the little woof as a pet
and I made a deal with them as a condition of agreeing to get married
The deal that I made when I bought the woof, as I said before, is one of the two
I thought if I chose the outcome myself, I might be able to accept it
So now I'm going to do what I have to do for my mum and dad
And it's said that it's an honor to marry a man of the noble class
Nah, Woof, can I have a hug, please?
It's so warm
Nah, Woof, I
I really don't want to
I'm actually scared that I don't want to get married
But it's a promise I have to keep
The ceremony is already being prepared and it's too late to do anything about it
Well, next week
Tomorrow's meeting is to discuss the marriage ceremony in advance for next week
If I get married, I'll have to live with him
I won't be able to hold Woof like this anymore
And there's a rule that says girls with male experience can't get married
If they found out, the marriage would be annulled
I'm still a virgin
but whether it's to a man of low enough status to be a pet to deal with sexual desires
or cuddling like this, it's not really a good idea
It's our secret.
Well, thank you.
Nah, Woof, finally, you want to see me naked?
I can't do it, but if you just want to see it, you can.
No? What a gentleman!
Then let's sleep together like this today
Yeah, it's okay. We'll just stay in the room for the day.
And I'll be too restless to sleep alone
Nah, what does Woof think of me?
Like?
Not as a master, but as a girl
No need to shout, Woof, you can talk, no one will hear you.
In human language
Well, thank you. I like Woof too.
Woof, good night!
Woof is asleep
Lovely sleeping face, nah, Woof
I...
I want Woof to come and save me
We'll go far away together...
Just a delusion...
fall asleep
I like you best, Woof