06 - False NTR report on aeroplane cup jerking off
Woof, I'm home... still awake... waiting for me?
thanks sorry it's so late, it's late at night
Well, a lot has happened with the pre-negotiations for the ceremony
Hmm? I'm red in the face? That's right.
I think it's still there. No, it's nothing.
It's more important than that, Woof.
Well, come over here
Lie down and hold
Good boy, good boy, good boy.
Well, about that, I'll say it up front
Everything I'm going to say now is a lie, so you can listen to it without fear.
Woof, today I'm with my betrothed... no, my husband.
have been together for five hours until now
The pre-negotiations were over before it got dark
Mum and Dad, the other parent and the planner had left
My husband and I rested in the hotel
The room only had a big bed and a sofa that could seat two people
We sat side by side on the sofa and talked a lot
about the day, the future, the things we liked, our interests, etc.
although yesterday we said we didn't want to and didn't like each other
I'm sorry, but I'm actually attracted to you
Maybe I was just stubborn before
if it's not the one you choose, you won't want it
so I deliberately touched his hand without thinking
Now that I think about it, is this a temptation?
and then I was squirming face down when suddenly
his hand was on my shoulder
I was a bit shocked, but I was amazed at the slightly more forceful
but manly look
And so, even though I was shy, I leaned in
like that for about 20 minutes, no, maybe 5 minutes
I don't know the time, but when I'm around him and my heart is racing
and he touched my boobs, it was so sudden
I reflexively said no
I tried to take my hand away, but he didn't stop, just like that
being held in the palm of his hand, touching it hard
My head became lighter and lighter as he touched me
and the strength to resist is slightly weaker.
And so, the clothes are removed.
first the shirt, which he unbuttoned with great skill
The white bra leaked out, then his hand went around the back and unhooked the hooks
I may be skinny but I still have boobs so they popped out at once
my breasts like Woof had never seen them before and my lovely pale pink nipples
Like my husband said, they're really sensitive, I think so too.
My breasts are being rubbed a little roughly
my nipples are being gently pinched
and my body shuddered in response to that
the sensitive nipples are hard, hard and erect
I still feel tingly just thinking about it
I've been pinched and rubbed on my tits so many times I'm wet
I hated it, I didn't want it
Not only was my pussy wet, but my face was melting.
You can't imagine it, can you?
The look on your master's face will never be seen by the little woof
But I had a little bit of sense left in me and whispered no
with a little bit of pouting and flattery in my voice, but my husband did stop
I thought, "Great!
but then, just a little bit, I thought, "Is this the end?
but I was wrong... it wasn't the end, it was the beginning
My husband, he just took off his trousers and left his underwear
The boxer briefs are stretched tightly and the shape of Eugene is clearly reflected
The moment I saw that, my body tensed up
It was the first time I'd ever felt that way but I soon understood
It's the fluttering of the uterus, a subconscious response to the female's desire for her genes
My husband was standing in front of the sofa, in front of me.
just in front of my face, not even ten centimeters from my underwear
probably because my head was subconsciously frozen
I just watched in silence as my husband took off his underwear
That image is still fresh in my mind
His Lordship's Ojinjin popped out in a flash
and Woof's big, different stick, like the difference between an adult and a child
It's a very different size, and it's got veins on it.
and the glans was enlarged and very manly
As I looked at my husband's big smelling rod with misty eyes
he said the command to lick me
I had never been ordered by anyone before, although I had ordered Woof...
but the moment of being ordered
I realized myself that I had a feminine look on my face
I came back and I was already kissing and kissing my husband's glans
just like that with soft lips
after so many caresses with my lips
the glans overflowed with a thick juice of patience and the command "lick me" was repeated in my head
so I licked the glans with the tip of my tongue like this
but even after licking it off, the juice kept spilling out
and I licked faster, clockwise around the head
ten times and ten times counterclockwise
and after that, I licked the underside of the rod with my tongue as hard as I could
looking upwards with my eyes while licking my tongue over the fat balls, like this
taking the balls one by one into my mouth and sucking them back and forth
And so they obeyed the command and served them carefully
and finally, finally, open your mouth wide like this
all the way from the glans to the root
a nasty sound like a cow bellowing escaped
Nah, Woof, now comes the best part of the blowjob to listen to
The resentment and shame all added up, the lower half of my body is crying out, right?
So, come on, lift your waist up.
It's anxious
patience juice... no, it's so light compared to your husband's
Are they tears? Tears of shame and resentment?
I'll start with this for you now, eh, aeroplane cup
It's a gift, but it seems to be a good one
Put a drop of lubricant in it
Look, put this against Woof's Ojinjin and insert it
How's that?
It's said to be the more stimulating model.
Is it comfortable? Is it comfortable?
I know it is
A look of virginity and shame
Nah, I just said this cup was a gift, right?
Of course it's from my husband, he said he'd tell Woof about today
I was ordered to do so by my husband
that I should tell him about the day and use this for M's pet sex at the same time
Your husband is so gentle and has lent me to you for your own good
so I've actually lost all interest in the little woof
but at least I'm using a cup to jerk you off to keep my orders
Let's see how far you can go before we pick up
I'm talking about taking all of my husband's rod in my mouth
The stench of male sweat spreads all over my mouth
it was hard to breathe but a trance-like expression escaped
just like that, with my husband's rod in my mouth and my eyes looking upwards
because he only said he'd lick me, I just held it deep and looked at him
and then he said the next command, just "Suck me"
The moment I heard that I bobbed my head at Eugene
the part of my mouth retreating to the glans and then to the root of the rod
not once or twice, but several dozen times in succession
The room echoes with the sound of my blowjob
my mouth gently kissing my tongue over the little wang
my lips that had spoken tenderly to the little woof
are being used in the erotic treatment of men whom I have only met a few times
sucking on command grunting grunting *n
drooling and bobbing his head desperately and licking his tongue vigorously
I'm going to serve my husband's rod in my mouth too
lelolelo licked the glans and the tip of my tongue carefully explored the coronal groove
The day's dirt is moistened with my saliva and wiped off with the tip of my tongue
as carefully as I wash the dirt from the dishes
Of course, I swallow all the dirt and get rid of it
The mouth is used as a commode for the filth
It's supposed to be nasty, but my pussy is oozing with juice
and the blowjob became more intense when I came back to my senses
contracting my mouth and expelling all the air from my mouth...
vacuum blowjob
cheeks tucked in, sucking up and down like an octopus
gurgling*n
sucking like a sprint for my husband's ejaculation
but I'm still very rusty and my husband can't get enough
so he ended up holding my head with both hands and gripping it tightly
being forced to bob up and down
the sound of oral sex echoing
he was using me like an aeroplane cup
You think "How can you do something that rough?"
"I wouldn't have done that if I had"
That's what I thought at the time
but now I look back and I was totally turned on
being forced by a handsome man who was stronger than myself
although I wondered if I would ever be roughly treated like that
but he seems to be cumming so I clench my throat tightly
subconsciously putting on a pouty face to seduce him, as if to say "please come"
and then he says in a manly voice "I'm going to cum"
Woof can cum too, together, at the same time
but you can cum as much as you want in my throat cup
and you can only cum in the cup
Hey Hubby is ready to cum
coming, cumming, totally turned into a female face
I say give me, give me, give me, give me cum, give me thick juices
The pussy is wet and pleading, opening and closing
Coming*n
biululu biubiu*n
the thick juice ejaculates a lot until the last drop is bobbing the head
biubiu*n
all down my throat...
gulp*n it's so thick I'm choking
wee wang also ejaculated... so light biu*n
my balls are empty, woof