07 - Broken Fake NTR Delusional Masturbation
Woof, you've had a hard time
What a pathetic look
Feel like crying now?
Or are you already crying?
Well, it doesn't matter if I'm crying or not
Let me help you pull out your cup
It's really rare
And the rod is even smaller than it was just now
I've got it all wrong so far
I thought Woof's rod was big and he was ejaculating a lot
but I get it, it's not working at all
Nah, what's wrong with Woof?
What's wrong with Woof?
It's not over yet
Well, did I mention that I was with my husband for five hours?
So listen to the rest of the four hours too!
I don't seem to have any energy left
You're right.
So, what's going to happen after that...
Give Woof a hint to pique your interest
It's going to... change your mind
After that ......
I ......
pounced on by my husband
cared for, right?
What will become of me physically and mentally?
Even if you say no, I'll say yes
Be at my command
Followed by...
by my husband's rod shooting into my mouth
After that, I was really uncomfortable
my mouth was full of the fishy taste of semen
thinking that today I'm just caught up in the atmosphere and not in my own mind
So I thought I'd go home and forget about what was going on
It's so rude to think about it now
to my husband
"That's it for today, I'm going home"
Then my husband grabbed my hand, which wanted to go back
kissing...
before I could react
my husband stuck his tongue right in and lingered
tongue kissing...doing the real kissing like a grown up
tongues tangled together and the brain went down
So all the kissing with Woof was just child's play so far
That's when I really realized... that I could only...
with tears streaming down my face while my lips were violated with tongue kisses
but in my heart it was different
I've been unconsciously...
since I took my husband's rod...
I touched my husband's penis a little when I was kissed
I thought, "Is it going to get smaller like a little woof after you've just cum?
but it's not like that at all... it's like a man.
Fingertips caressing it with a girlish charm
then my husband stopped kissing and just pushed me down on the bed with force
It was useless to resist even if I had to, I couldn't fight with boys
And that's how I got my panties off
My ...... that I've been protecting since birth
The most important part of a girl's body ......
The pussy that Woof had never seen before
After my husband saw it I was red in the face
"Don't look!" I begged, but he didn't stop.
"I didn't want to do this" I said in a small, almost crying, lovely voice
and he ignored it
Do you know why?
Because ......
the pussy was already dripping wet
No matter what the words say, my pussy is craving my husband's big rod
My husband sees through all this
So, that's it, to make it easier for the pussy to use...
What's the word for it?
What's the normal position?
And it was in that position, with my husband's legs up.
My body is softer
my head was being used as a support point and my body was being pulled up
my pussy felt like a fixed cup
from the top down, feet, chest, belly button, pits
My erotic parts were all visible
in the most humiliating positions
And so, the rod...the hard rod pressed up against the slit of my pussy
Ah, just a little more... just a little more pressure and it's going in.
But then I forcefully resisted from the inside and said "Stop it!"
Yeah... the image of Xiao Wang came to mind
Woof's cute little body
He's honest, but he's really gentle and he likes me a lot
All these things come to mind
Woof is a pet, but I love her and she's the most important person to me
So I said it last night, right?
"Help me"
if you had responded properly to my request for help
even if it was a lie, it wouldn't have been like this
I know, you weren't asleep at that time.
You were just pretending to be asleep
Scared and not brave
So, will you listen to me again now?
little woof
"Can you save me?"
Thank you
But...
it's too late
Woof, I'm sorry.
Now my pussy entrance is covered in your husband's cum
because I was ordered to "not wipe it off"
You already know that, don't you, after I said "Stop it! After
my husband said in a manly voice, "I'm going in!
I replied, "Yes!"
At the moment I replied to my husband, I thrust in with a snort and a puff
The rod was inserted tightly inside
shortly after the hymen was pierced, and immediately...
like a pussy stirring, it began to piston violently
The vicious glans was like digging into a pussy
It's the first time but it feels good
The body's too good together, it's too sensual
The dirty sow's face that I would never let Woof see
smugly
Oooh, that's good, that's good, that's good
Don't look, little woof, don't look at your master's sow face
Nah, little woof
You're feeling it again, aren't you?
Feel the shame of being useless
It's okay
jerk yourself off
not even able to use a cup and have sex alone miserably
while listening to his master being internally ejaculated by other men...
while masturbating
Hey
That's an order!
That's fine
And
I can't hold back
When I talk about having real sex with my husband, it reminds me of that time...
so...
fingers in the pussy
I'll masturbate with Woof too
so good hubby's rod is so good
The sound of the snapping and stroking of the pussy echoes through the bedroom
Even though I tried to curl up and escape, it was no use
as my feet are grabbed and used as an internal commode
unable to move freely
so the pleasure is all in the voice and face
Faced with a rod that attacked my pussy without mercy
All she can do is "Oh! Oh!" Oh!
making loud, dirty noises and pouting
pouting with open mouths and kisses with outstretched tongues
panting and panting while wagging her tongue around incoherently
her tongue wiggling as if to entice her husband to kiss her
but no... my husband won't give me a kiss
My husband doesn't seem to like Woof very much, so he lets me choose
"who I want to be with"
What else is there to say?
"I don't want that kind of jerky dog, I'll throw it away, I'll throw it away, so kiss me...kiss me
immediately answered
and then he did a thick tongue kiss with me
bodies pressed tightly together, pistoning relentlessly
and kissing at the same time, the mucous membranes both above and below entwined with each other in a voracious search for pleasure
The whole thing about Woof is forgotten, it doesn't matter
I can only feel the pleasure
like this
This erotic kissing has been going on for a long time
Woof is also excited to masturbate with his master's virgin sex as a side dish
It's the best!
I've been giving you a side dish every night since I got married to my husband
I'll let you masturbate in a room where you can hear me and my husband panting from inside sex
with the sound of my panting and the sound of my pussy rubbing against my rod as a side dish for masturbation
from the next room "Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Big rod!" real condomless sex
The best side dish ever!
Come on, I'll let you hear more...
I'm having sex with my husband
My husband's relentless full-on pistoning is coming and so far the thrusts are like preparation exercises
From popping and snapping to banging and becoming more violent
Masturbation is becoming more intense along with the memories of my husband's lovemaking...
pussy violated like this in a messy way
"It's so good, so good," she said, rolling her eyes as she wept
I'm so comfortable that my consciousness is going to disappear
making orgasmic faces
My body and mind are all my husband's things
I feel a big one coming in my pussy
It's coming, it's going, it's going
Woof I'm going to go, let's go together
I'm going to almost get shot inside
"I like my husband so much I like my husband so much" whispering in my ear about being internally ejaculated
my pussy is being pushed so hard I'm going to go, I'm going to go
like*n
love hubby so much love the big rod
Going for it*n
like*n
cumming inside...so much it's overflowing
want to marry you husband want to marry you husband
pussy to get pregnant marry husband