08 - Pure lovemaking with the master
The little woof is having an orgasm
jerking myself off
I came too
while remembering the thick sex with my husband
nah woof
What are you feeling now?
very sad?
Regretful?
Are you?
not shooting anymore?
Then just lie back and I'll just tell you the rest of the story in your ear
It's not over yet
We're not even halfway there
After being ejaculated by my husband...
I already look like a sow who adores her husband
I've been so enthralled by my husband
I'm making a sow's face and asking for more sex
and when I pampered my husband he told me
"If I get another erection, let's do it again"
I then asked my husband for another erection
"Please, please give me cum"
as I licked my balls and pouted
and then my husband got another erection for me
and with that this time the master held my ass tightly from behind
and began to fuck like an animal
Of course it was condomless sex so I came straight in
and then the cum just stuck to the pussy like that...
Being held by my husband while talking about what I've done with Woof so far...
while saying so many bad things about Xiao Wang
To make my husband happy, I've been trying to please him
"I don't need that kind of stuff" and all that
"I'll throw it away once I'm married" or something like that
I actually wanted my husband to hold me until morning, but it was time...
and he came back
My husband said, "Let's keep it until after we're married"
the little wang's face...
I couldn't bear to look at it
being underestimated...
bullied...
It's so bad
It's hard, isn't it?
It's a confusing mix of emotions, isn't it?
Give Wanda one last chance
Try to push me?
I'm...not a virgin anymore
It's okay to have sex
I've already given my husband my first time, it won't affect the marriage
A little bit of welfare for the poor little woof
Come on, let's try?
Jitterbug
It's too hard for a timid jittery dog
Not good...
Come on, then the skirt
And then the panties
You can't violate your master if you don't take them off
Finally, you can see it, pussy
Keeping this up, the glans of Woof's rod is slowly approaching
It's getting bigger
Can you feel it?
The touch of the pussy
It's sticky and warm
Soon... a few centimeters to go...
What's wrong?
Sure enough...
Can't get up the courage?
Head... come closer...
Nah, little woof
You said you'd save me, didn't you?
And now it's still...
Even after being done so badly...
can still...
to me...
reach out to me?
Thank you
Xiao Wang ...... just said something...
were all lies to you
It was said at the beginning, right?
"What I'm saying now is all...
"It's all a lie to you"
It's actually...
It's just that the conversation has been going on for a long time
Nothing was done
There's no semen on here at all, is there?
but...
after getting married...
what was said today
will become true
I can only think of this way...
if it's done straight away like this
the engagement would be annulled
In that case...
what would happen to the little woof...
I've already explained it, haven't I...
Can you do it for me...
to die for me?
Xiao Wang...
I like you the most
Please, please
Come and take away...
my virginity
Thank you
Facing this way...
Don't give me that look
Only now...
two people...
Let's be happy together...
Well ......
That's it... the normal bit is fine
but there are better ones
like this
hands around the neck of the little woof
I'm going to get going, huh?
hugging each other...
sitting on Woof's lap
This ......
called the opposite seat position
The happiest position...
where the bodies are pressed close together
breasts...soft
asses too...soft
like they were trying to crush Woof's body
Nice?
Yeah!
So keep it like that... waist...
Start swinging from side to side
swing, swing, swing
The dance of colour...
you like it when you're treated roughly, don't you?
Your favorite master's pussy is too much for you?
The first taste that no one has ever tasted before
I'm a virgin
until just now...
the look of indulgence all of a sudden
getting used to it
Mmm...pussy's taking on the shape of a little woof
But it's not enough, is it?
Just rubbing my pussy isn't enough
I get it!
Then keep it like this, up and down at the waist...
How about that? Pussy fucking ......
Yeah?
Get more comfortable!
My pussy belongs to Woof alone!
Nah, open your eyes, look at me with your eyes open and have a condomless kiss
That'll make you more excited, right?
That's right, look at me very closely
It's so nice
Both the top and the bottom mucous membranes are rubbing together.
while watching my master's kissing face...
while doing tongue kisses ......
Nah, what's wrong, my waist is shrinking back
Want to escape this pleasure?
No, look... hold on tight...
I can't run away. I have to feel it all over.
Clench your vagina as you hold Woof's body tight
Hold on tight... clench... clench your pussy...
Come tighten up Ojinjin!
Tight, wrinkled pussy
it's like holding the cup so tightly that the air flows out like a vacuum
Nice? Are you happy with your pussy? Or is it...
And I have to add...
ears?
Woof's Ojinjin is so comfortable he can't help but let out an erotic gasp
How erotic is that?
bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang
ear being licked, so erotic
What's wrong?
Even the woof is wiggling?
Want to make me feel good too?
You don't have to try hard to do that
It's enough that Woof is loved by me...
That's the way I like it little woof
But I'm happy that Woof is willing to do it for me
So...let's race?
Which one of us can make the other one pant with their condomless pistoning?
My serious pistoning, waist-breathing...
and more!
What's wrong?
Is the twisting coming to an end?
Jiggly M twerking in a tight pussy in a tight pussy... are you giving up first?
It's okay, it's okay... just don't move
That's it, let's have intimate sex in a real jiggly position
Can't you do it anymore? Woof?
cum gradually pouring from his balls
Inject it all into your master's virgin pussy
It's okay, shoot it out...
Shoot all of Woof's extra thick cum!
Look... both feet around Woof's waist
Hold it firmly in place like this
Cum in the deepest part of your pussy.
Ojinjin and pussy come together
It's time to come, come on, come on
Come all the way in your pussy
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Cumming...cumming inside...
swooshing
I'm cumming a lot
I'm so full of Woof's cum
Good boy, good boy, lying on the bed... are you tired?
Yeah...
That's it for today...
Go to sleep
You see...
breasts...
Come on...
Mmm...
That's it...
sucking on the master's nipple...
sleepy sleepy sleepy~
Good boy~ Good boy~
Good boy, good boy
Woof?
Yeah! What a cute face!
My boobs...
very tasty?
Nah, Woof?
And I...
by the little woof...
like ......
really happy
so...
before trying to get...
Xiao Wang to take it...
my first time
Nah, Xiao Wang
Do you regret it?
Make love to me...
Yeah...
Good night~
Woof!
Most like...