09- Snuggle
Woof
I said, "Woof, get up!
Get up, it's your master's order
Get up
And so it is ......
Then ......
Good morning
No ...... it's not morning
It's 3:30am
In the morning you have to say hello to the whole family
So ...... little woof
Let's run away ...... to a faraway place
I won't let Woof be dealt with
I've said it before, right? I'm going to make you happy little woof
It's the owner's job to take care of the pet to the end
No, it's okay ......
Here you go.
Oh, it's a bank book
The money I got from my New Year's Eve, my pocket money, and my salary from my secret job
That's enough money to live on for a year
I started preparing for it a long time ago
but I never got around to it
But you got up the courage to help me, didn't you?
So ...... now it's my turn to help you
And it's okay
For me, now that I've lost my virginity
there's no place in the world for me anymore
I've renounced my marriage and been disinherited from my family
I am no longer of any value
This has taken a lot of time
a marriage that took so much time and so many hands to make
The bride has run away with her pet on the brink of marriage
What will people think?
People still think that Aoi, such a good boy who knows how to behave, wouldn't do something like that
These people don't know that I've always been a bad boy
I just wanted to be with the person I wanted to be with
It's up to me to decide who I'm going to be with
Mum and Dad think that a woman's happiness is to be an appendage to a man
In their minds, Aoi is a good boy who knows how to behave
and should understand that
They seem to be looking out for me but they never try to understand the real me
So that's all right
Woof, I'm going to make you happy too
Even if you can't do anything, even if you don't do anything
I'll love you for the rest of my life
Little Wang, hold out your hand
Hold hands and it won't be cold anymore, right?
So we should almost go, right?
Let's stay together too
I love you, Woof