EX - Under the Green Sky - No Regrets
I think I made the right choice to come here today
Well, the sky is clear to this point
The refreshing breeze, the endless grassland
I've only seen this kind of scenery in TV shows
There is nothing here
just a whole field of green grass and pure white cumulus clouds ......
No ...... there is still you and me here ......
I ask you
If there is a time machine in this world
could go back to the beginning and make the choice again
I would make the same choice no matter how many times
No matter how many times I would choose to lie with you under this blue sky
and feel the breeze on our cheeks
I hope you'll feel the same way
Ha ha ha Hmm
Together, we'll be twice as happy
Oh, what's the matter, sleepy-eyed
Well, because the sun is so warm
Shall we just take a nap?
Good night
Sweet dreams to you