1. in an abandoned hospital
You're awake
It's no use panicking
You can't escape
Thy body has become
entangled in the thread
Thou art caught in the
net of my concubine
Why hast thou come to this ruin?
Never mind
Thou art the first
prey in half a month
And to be loved well
You look just like me
I'm a face person
I have to eat anyway, but a
handsome, young man is best
I've only had one over
the age of 40 so far
So, what should I do?
Do you have any more wishes?
To beg forgiveness for a moment?
Ha? [01:57.81] Wishing
that I might kill thee?
What? [02:04.98] Have you heard rumours
of me and come to pay tribute?
People are hard to understand
But ...... it would be a
pity to kill thee outright
It's better to wait for
a taste before killing
For the sake of your
initiative to let me eat
Before you die, see me
as I was when I was born
The spider's legs have sprouted from the limbs,
and this is what I looked like when I was born
Well ...... I don't think
you're very scared
Why? Why is your face so red?
Thou ......
very ...... beautiful?
Dost thou say concubine?
What a bummer ......
Tell me, what is thy
trouble Tell me
roar ...... how dare they bully
each other as human beings ......
So thou hast become a victim
of thy fellow man ......
A single epidemic can kill all those
who are not yet 100 years old
but revel in the pleasure
of bullying your own people
What a fool
But I still don't understand
Did you come here because you thought
it would be best if I ate you?
Obviously there are many
other ways to die ......
Did you come here because
you had a desire for me?
Because I'm embarrassed to
court a human female ......
It would be best if I
could have an affair
Even if the worst outcome
is to be eaten by a demon
As long as it's a demoness,
it's a good idea, isn't it?
So, what? [05:41.71] What?
And if I were to do it,
would you not hide from it?
Ha ...... can't laugh ......
No ......
ghosts or whatever it
is it doesn't matter
just the obsession of being
able to have sex with a female
I'm impressed
I'm not comfortable being considered
inferior to humans, though
but the phrase "what is not done
by one's own kind does not hurt"
I don't understand it either
And when thou saw'st me, thou
didst not flee, but lust'dst
I am very fond of thee
Thou art a strange man, too
Thy wishes are not
unfulfilled for thee
Then ......
I ask thee once more
Do you still want to have intercourse
with me, a demon, when you see this limb?
So it is
Does it tickle?
I see
Let me make your wish come true
Slowly, don't hold me so tight
What a cute little guy
I've been dreaming about
the union of my soul
Do you want to do it
with me that badly?
How old do you think I am?
24?
How wrong
I have lived nearly ten
times as long as this
Thou hast said before
that I should kill thee
And which is stronger, thy desire
for death or thy desire for sex?
Let us ask thee here
Oh, to be so good-looking and
to grow something so hideous
Then I'll touch it