2. Licking ears
infused with venom
Body shaking so hard
Getting big again
Funny little guy
This huge thing makes me think it
would be a shame to just eat you
You look like this ...... No
human can excite you like this
Do you want to do it
with me that badly?
Interesting man
I will play with your body
Start with the ears
and violate ......
Do you feel it?
There's venom flowing
in your body now
Don't worry
It is not the poison
that will kill thee
So that thou mayst not think
of it during intercourse
I have cleaned the
inside of thy brain
It is not a bad thing
That thou mayst forget all
that befell thy countrymen
This is also a first
experience for thee ......
Do you not want to make love
to each other comfortably?
Just be glad you were
violated by poison ......
Come on
Let the other ear also
be filled with venom
Melt the inside of
your head ......
Free thee from reality
once and for all
Come and forget all this
Just think of me
The poison has
almost taken effect
Come, take off your clothes
and let the venom trickle
down to your body
How can you be so
white and so slender?
as if this arm would break
with the slightest effort
Come and hold me
I can feel you want to hold me
Be careful not to
break your arms
How's that?
What do you think of the
skin-to-skin contact?
Like this
I'm warm too
half of my body is no
different from a human's
all the same as thine
Is this your first taste of meat?
[08:44.34] Just enjoy it as you please
lovely little one and
shaking all the time
My breasts and thy breasts
always touch each other
Are they soft?
That's great
Be happy
I've filled your body with
this much bodily fluid
Come on, don't think about anything, just
feel the touch of soft and full breasts
Come on, rub your
breasts together
Come on, move your breasts too
nipples touching
What a nasty thing to do
Is it comfortable?
It's so nice
hugging so tightly
like a little kid
so cute
I have the most lustrous and
elastic breasts in my body
How about that? Do you
want to touch them?
You can touch them as
much as you like later
So I'd better ...... hurry up
From the moment thou saidst thou wished to
have intercourse with my concubine ......
From the moment my
body was craved ......
I have wanted it so badly