3. The first night
of intercourse
Can you hear it?
This lustful sound
front feet, groin pussy
quivering and quivering
The way the love juices keep
flowing can't be unnoticed
Yes, it's exactly the
same place as humans
The most sensitive part
of my body is right there
It's already wet, you see
This is a very greedy place
I can't help it
anymore, come and do it
Yes, from the front
Very good
It's only halfway,
but it's great
Don't worry about it,
just keep coming in
Or is it that if you
move, you'll come?
Yes, that's deep enough
Try moving your waist
a little more slowly
If you don't cum, you can
move as much as you want
Yes, that's right
Isn't that a good thing to do?
Instead of saying that
you have a great thing
it's more like that thing
craves the opposite sex
But I will not lose to
thee in this respect
because it's been a long time
since I've performed this act
Canst thou feel thy thing
in it entwined with silk
slimy and making lustful noises
This, ah, to keep the
prey from escaping
spouting spider silk
It's an instinctive reaction
If it's comfortable, the spider
spurts out and wraps itself around it
so that the male doesn't get away,
the spider silk will come out
And if a thick, hard
thing like you comes in
and wants to eat it,
wants to eat it
My body is trembling
while holding thee and watching
that thou be not strangled
If I don't control my strength,
your body will split open
But this is
Thou, thou
but thou dost not fear death
Though I may kill thee,
yet thou craves my body
to stop
Hey, stop, stop, stop
Stop...stop!
Wait!
Wait, I said wait!
I won't kill you... I still
want to be with you...
to be together for a
little while longer
I won't kill thee,
I won't kill thee
Hast thou not come here to die?
Liar
Is not this more energetic
than the average man
spider silk shot out
and the bodily fluids are
coming out in a sticky mess
It's coming out, the silk threads,
the white ones are coming out
There it goes!
There goes *n
Going to go Going to go
I've been made to go by a man who is experiencing
this kind of eroticism for the first time
because you're moving so hard
How violent
Prepare to die by running
through my body here
Very brave, oh
But the spider's threads from
my body are wrapped around it
so that thou canst never escape