4. Sexual intercourse
in a tangle
See, this is a gift to
satisfy my concubine
More saliva in thy ears
Be more addicted to me
Forget your worries
and come to crave me
Be comfortable with the
sensation of your brain melting
Come, why dost thou
not move thy back
It looks like you can't wait
Come on, go wild, indulge
It's so good
Thou shalt indulge
in pleasure too
Well done, oh, well done
Yes, come and try to
take it out on me
I'll take it
It's coming, it's coming
Do you love this body?
I love to do it with
inexperienced men
I can't help but love giving
a man his first pleasure
not to experience the body of a female
of the same race, but to taste this body
After experiencing this
body, there's no going back
of other females
guide the ignorant male
and he will return to me
like a flying insect
trapped in a spider's nest
There is nowhere to go
Thou hast nowhere to go
Thrust deeper and deeper
What a gutsy fellow
What do you care as long as
you can taste a woman's body?
with a single-minded
desire for my body
even for the sake of life
How lovely
I'm so desperate for my
body, I'm being penetrated.
I really can't
beat this pleasure
The spider's body
isn't scared at all?
People are afraid of me
and hate my alien body
Even though I've been
alive for over 200 years
but thou art the first
to not only not fear me
and even courted me
The sight of thee, whose cheeks were red when
she looked at this body, was unforgettable
The way you look at a beautiful
thing with fascination
to the depths
so good there, so good
spider silk, spider
silk, coming out
Sorry
wrapped thou in a
cocoon of spider silk
both sides are white
as explained earlier
but these spiders will wrap themselves
unconsciously around their prey
not painful, but laced with
bodily fluids and slimy
The concubine's love juices will
make the male's mind go wild
Come on, please me
a little longer
The interracial mingling
is funny and interesting
not to have children but simply
to crave and enjoy pleasure
But ah
the female part of my heart
is happy when I'm desired
The arachnid is coming again...
[13:59.10]so good!
I can't believe I'm happy to be
desired by such a weak human being
Arachnid, it's coming
out, it's coming out
I'm almost at my limit too
Will your hot thing come out?
I want it so badly.
Fill my depths with essence
I give you permission, don't you want
to ejaculate in the female body?
I'm coming
almost going first
Let me eat you up
Do you think you will be eaten
after your intercourse with me?
Then eat it, for it is not possible
not to respond to your expectations
Come, ejaculate!
Come out and be eaten by me
It's no use, you
can't pull it out
Your one is wrapped in spider
silk and is becoming one with me
Come, let me move it
Come, do not hold back
Come on, let's get rid of it
Inside my body, come on
I'm going
Be eaten by me... [17:54.84]Say
you want to be eaten by me
You came here to die, didn't you?
What are you stubborn about now?
Go, go, go, go! Thou hast
reached the end of thy rope
Come out, come out
going for it
going to it going to it
Cumming out...
[18:59.37]Cumming out
So, what should I do with you?