5. tranquil and
peaceful sleeping sex
How does it feel to have
intercourse with a concubine?
Is there anything else
you would like to try?
Well, I guess I want
to touch my breasts
I did promise to give thee the
right to touch my breasts
Well, I'll let you touch
them until you're satisfied
But I have one condition
that you remain in this position of union
with me and do not pull out your penis
Just hold me like this and
become one with me, okay?
That's good. [01:28.91]You're wrapped in this spider silk
anyway, and you can't pull it out even if you want to.
Though thou art caught in the thread,
thou canst still move a little
Come to me
and bury thy face in my breast
Are my breasts soft? [02:28.99]Is
it not hard to breathe?
Why stop breathing? Don't
worry about my feelings
Are you shy?
Then let me breathe in your ear
My breath will not be
unpleasant to thee, will it?
Nay, I give thee
leave to breathe
Let me feel thy breath clearly
It tickles
so warm, thou hast a good smell
Thou art shy
Let me lick up all your sweat
so salty~
A "cooing, cooing" sound emanates
from the union of their lower bodies
I am calm, but my body is
still longing for you.
I did not twist my waist, but my body was
sucking and licking that thing inside.
I want to eat you up
Don't worry, you'll
just come out like that
Come on out
Very good, very good.
[11:29.29] That's a good boy.
Fill me with your
essence like this
piu~piu~piu~
so warm, so warm
deep inside my body
Come out all of it,
come out in one gulp
Release all your
desires into my body
I have already ravaged your
head with my saliva...
Thy ears are red
I see that my venom
has little effect
Don't hide
All right, all right
It's rare to find
a human like you
so long eaten by
my bodily fluids
A normal person would
have been a wreck by now
You are very interesting
very worthy of staying with me
And you've swelled up again
still not satisfied after
such a violent encounter?
Twisting, twisting, twisting
With my strength
I can have as many
sex acts as I want
But unfortunately, you don't
have the same strength as I do
For those who are new to sex,
it is even more difficult
Good boy, good boy, let
your body rest now
To eat you up? [18:41.21] I've
completely discouraged such thoughts
Well, after all, most of
them are beyond my reach
so I let them become my
nourishment but thou art special
Why, did you really think
you would be eaten by me?
Dost thou want to be eaten?
[20:31.97] Wishing to die?
Don't look like that!
Come and suck my breasts
This may give you
a little pleasure
That tickles!
Go on, suck it.
That's it
Good boy, good boy,
good boy, good boy
Is this the first time you've
touched a woman's breast?
No, probably the first time
other than breast milk
Good boy, good boy, after
all the fun I had just had
You should be very tired too
Close your eyes, good boy, good boy, and
suck my breasts to your heart's content
How lovely
As if you were healed by me
I seem to be incredibly
healed by you too
O thou who art comfortably buried
with thy head in my breast
probably also felt the bond
between each other deep inside
and thus became peaceful
Why so?
Having witnessed thy
single-minded desire to die
and felt the fleeting
frailty of life
I have experienced a gentleness and peace
that I have never experienced before
My breasts itch
Nay, it seems thou wilt put an end
to thy life in this youthful age
I should say that you
have come to your senses
Or should I say thou art a fool?
What didst thou think?
Even if I die
between my breasts?
Would you not despair even
if your life ended here?
Even if you can no longer be
reconciled to your family?
Though you say it's all right
but sucking desperately
on my nipples
I am not your natural mother
And why didst thou trust thy life to a
concubine whom thou hast not known?
Because I am not a human being?
I see, I see
thou suckest with the tip of thy
tongue constantly teasing the nipple
makes you look relaxed too
so comfortable
Keep sucking
Good boy, good boy,
good boy, good boy
What else do you want
me to do for you?
And I want to be
licked in the ear
But... I can also erase that
unpleasant memory for you
No, that would be too
vulgar after all
Then I will stick my tongue
in your ear as much as I like
My long, slender tongue will reach deep
into your ear with a single breath
Is the licking too intense?
You are sucking my nipples
too, [37:52.09]you big pervert
and with small
jerks of the waist
I'm clearly exhausted
of energy and semen
I'm amazed that you're
still so desperate
Really, that thing is pushing
deep into my privates again
and it is still
so big and strong
I didn't think there was a human
being who wanted to embrace me
It's a funny world, isn't it?
I'd like to be hugged more,
lick my nipples, suck on them
It's so warm~
Let me melt your
consciousness and your brain
I want you to rest
without any worries
Forget, forget, forget all
You're swelling up again,
you big, horny, wolf!
So warm, so comfortable
I feel your sorrow
It's expanding inside my body
and it's almost filling me up
Come on, this sticky spider silk is
going to wrap itself around your penis
I will not let go until I do
My love will envelop thee
My whispering seems
to please thee
Come, let me love
the other ear again
The sound of a spider's silk,
soaked with love juice
and the sound of my private parts scraping
and licking your cock are very nasty
each licking the other's
sensitive parts
but not at all excited inside
but rather calm.
I'm probably experiencing this
for the first time in my life
Even if I bite my nipples,
no milk will come out
Did my calmness provoke
your displeasure?
But I have no intention
of changing my mind
I am able to sleep in comfort
Ohhhh, bite harder
Such an attitude
of yours is lovely
Good boy~ good boy~
I'm like a toddler being soothed
Good boy, good boy, suck on my
breast and forget your troubles
Forget all your worries, whether they
be earthly matters or painful memories
Forget, forget, forget
Sleep, sleep,
sleep, sleep, sleep
Close your eyes
Good boy~ Good boy~
Are you still awake?
Do you want to be my wife?
Think about it...
[55:41.11]Let's rest today